[
  {
    "id": "2",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a solution where users will be directed to a backup static error page if the primary website is unavailable. The primary websites DNS records are hosted in Amazon Route 53 where their domain is pointing to an Application Load Balancer (ALB). Which configuration should the solutions architect use to meet the companys needs while minimizing changes and infrastructure overhead?",
      "answers": [
        "Point a Route 53 alias record to an Amazon CloudFront distribution with the ALB as one of its origins. Then, create custom error pages for the distribution.",
        "Set up a Route 53 active-passive failover configuration. Direct traffic to a static error page hosted within an Amazon S3 bucket when Route 53 health checks determine that the ALB endpoint is unhealthy.",
        "Update the Route 53 record to use a latency-based routing policy. Add the backup static error page hosted within an Amazon S3 bucket to the record so the traffic is sent to the most responsive endpoints.",
        "Set up a Route 53 active-active configuration with the ALB and an Amazon EC2 instance hosting a static error page as endpoints. Route 53 will only send requests to the instance if the health checks fail for the ALB."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Set up a Route 53 active-passive failover configuration. Direct traffic to a static error page hosted within an Amazon S3 bucket when Route 53 health checks determine that the ALB endpoint is unhealthy."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a high performance computing (HPC) workload on Amazon EC2. The EC2 instances need to communicate to each other frequently and require network performance with low latency and high throughput. Which EC2 configuration meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Launch the EC2 instances in a cluster placement group in one Availability Zone.",
        "Launch the EC2 instances in a spread placement group in one Availability Zone.",
        "Launch the EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group in two Regions and peer the VPCs.",
        "Launch the EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group spanning multiple Availability Zones."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Launch the EC2 instances in a cluster placement group in one Availability Zone."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company wants to host a scalable web application on AWS. The application will be accessed by users from different geographic regions of the world. Application users will be able to download and upload unique data up to gigabytes in size. The development team wants a cost-effective solution to minimize upload and download latency and maximize performance. What should a solutions architect do to accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon S3 with Transfer Acceleration to host the application.",
        "Use Amazon S3 with CacheControl headers to host the application.",
        "Use Amazon EC2 with Auto Scaling and Amazon CloudFront to host the application.",
        "Use Amazon EC2 with Auto Scaling and Amazon ElastiCache to host the application."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon S3 with Transfer Acceleration to host the application."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is migrating from an on-premises infrastructure to the AWS Cloud. One of the companys applications stores files on a Windows file server farm that uses Distributed File System Replication (DFSR) to keep data in sync. A solutions architect needs to replace the file server farm. Which service should the solutions architect use? ",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon EFS",
        "Amazon FSx",
        "Amazon S3",
        "AWS Storage Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon FSx"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a legacy application that process data in two parts. The second part of the process takes longer than the first, so the company has decided to rewrite the application as two microservices running on Amazon ECS that can scale independently. How should a solutions architect integrate the microservices?",
      "answers": [
        "Implement code in microservice 1 to send data to an Amazon S3 bucket. Use S3 event notifications to invoke microservice 2.",
        "Implement code in microservice 1 to publish data to an Amazon SNS topic. Implement code in microservice 2 to subscribe to this topic.",
        "Implement code in microservice 1 to send data to Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose. Implement code in microservice 2 to read from Kinesis Data Firehose.",
        "Implement code in microservice 1 to send data to an Amazon SQS queue. Implement code in microservice 2 to process messages from the queue."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Implement code in microservice 1 to send data to an Amazon SQS queue. Implement code in microservice 2 to process messages from the queue."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A company captures clickstream data from multiple websites and analyzes it using batch processing. The data is loaded nightly into Amazon Redshift and is consumed by business analysts. The company wants to move towards near-real-time data processing for timely insights. The solution should process the streaming data with minimal effort and operational overhead. Which combination of AWS services are MOST cost-effective for this solution? (Choose two.) ",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon EC2",
        "AWS Lambda",
        "Amazon Kinesis Data Streams",
        "Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose",
        "Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose",
        "Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys application runs on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). The instances run in an Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling group across multiple Availability Zones. On the first day of every month at midnight, the application becomes much slower when the month-end financial calculation batch executes. This causes the CPU utilization of the EC2 instances to immediately peak to 100%, which disrupts the application. What should a solutions architect recommend to ensure the application is able to handle the workload and avoid downtime?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure an Amazon CloudFront distribution in front of the ALB.",
        "Configure an EC2 Auto Scaling simple scaling policy based on CPU utilization.",
        "Configure an EC2 Auto Scaling scheduled scaling policy based on the monthly schedule.",
        "Configure Amazon ElastiCache to remove some of the workload from the EC2 instances."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure an EC2 Auto Scaling scheduled scaling policy based on the monthly schedule."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A company runs a multi-tier web application that hosts news content. The application runs on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer. The instances run in an EC2 Auto Scaling group across multiple Availability Zones and use an Amazon Aurora database. A solutions architect needs to make the application more resilient to periodic increases in request rates. Which architecture should the solutions architect implement? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Add AWS Shield.",
        "Add Aurora Replica.",
        "Add AWS Direct Connect.",
        "Add AWS Global Accelerator.",
        "Add an Amazon CloudFront distribution in front of the Application Load Balancer."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Add Aurora Replica.",
        "Add an Amazon CloudFront distribution in front of the Application Load Balancer."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An application running on AWS uses an Amazon Aurora Multi-AZ deployment for its database. When evaluating performance metrics, a solutions architect discovered that the database reads are causing high I/O and adding latency to the write requests against the database. What should the solutions architect do to separate the read requests from the write requests?",
      "answers": [
        "Enable read-through caching on the Amazon Aurora database.",
        "Update the application to read from the Multi-AZ standby instance.",
        "Create a read replica and modify the application to use the appropriate endpoint.",
        "Create a second Amazon Aurora database and link it to the primary database as a read replica."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Update the application to read from the Multi-AZ standby instance."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A recently acquired company is required to build its own infrastructure on AWS and migrate multiple applications to the cloud within a month. Each application has approximately 50 TB of data to be transferred. After the migration is complete, this company and its parent company will both require secure network connectivity with consistent throughput from their data centers to the applications. A solutions architect must ensure one-time data migration and ongoing network connectivity. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "AWS Direct Connect for both the initial transfer and ongoing connectivity.",
        "AWS Site-to-Site VPN for both the initial transfer and ongoing connectivity.",
        "AWS Snowball for the initial transfer and AWS Direct Connect for ongoing connectivity.",
        "AWS Snowball for the initial transfer and AWS Site-to-Site VPN for ongoing connectivity."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Snowball for the initial transfer and AWS Direct Connect for ongoing connectivity."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company serves content to its subscribers across the world using an application running on AWS. The application has several Amazon EC2 instances in a private subnet behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). Due to a recent change in copyright restrictions, the chief information officer (CIO) wants to block access for certain countries. Which action will meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Modify the ALB security group to deny incoming traffic from blocked countries.",
        "Modify the security group for EC2 instances to deny incoming traffic from blocked countries.",
        "Use Amazon CloudFront to serve the application and deny access to blocked countries.",
        "Use ALB listener rules to return access denied responses to incoming traffic from blocked countries."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon CloudFront to serve the application and deny access to blocked countries."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "13",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A product team is creating a new application that will store a large amount of data. The data will be analyzed hourly and modified by multiple Amazon EC2 Linux instances. The application team believes the amount of space needed will continue to grow for the next 6 months. Which set of actions should a solutions architect take to support these needs?",
      "answers": [
        "Store the data in an Amazon EBS volume. Mount the EBS volume on the application instances.",
        "Store the data in an Amazon EFS file system. Mount the file system on the application instances.",
        "Store the data in Amazon S3 Glacier. Update the vault policy to allow access to the application instances.",
        "Store the data in Amazon S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA). Update the bucket policy to allow access to the application instances."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Store the data in an Amazon EFS file system. Mount the file system on the application instances."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "14",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is migrating a three-tier application to AWS. The application requires a MySQL database. In the past, the application users reported poor application performance when creating new entries. These performance issues were caused by users generating different real-time reports from the application during working hours. Which solution will improve the performance of the application when it is moved to AWS?",
      "answers": [
        "Import the data into an Amazon DynamoDB table with provisioned capacity. Refactor the application to use DynamoDB for reports.",
        "Create the database on a compute optimized Amazon EC2 instance. Ensure compute resources exceed the on-premises database.",
        "Create an Amazon Aurora MySQL Multi-AZ DB cluster with multiple read replicas. Configure the application reader endpoint for reports.",
        "Create an Amazon Aurora MySQL Multi-AZ DB cluster. Configure the application to use the backup instance of the cluster as an endpoint for the reports."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Amazon Aurora MySQL Multi-AZ DB cluster. Configure the application to use the backup instance of the cluster as an endpoint for the reports."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "15",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is deploying a distributed database on multiple Amazon EC2 instances. The database stores all data on multiple instances so it can withstand the loss of an instance. The database requires block storage with latency and throughput to support several million transactions per second per server. Which storage solution should the solutions architect use?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon EBS",
        "Amazon EC2 instance store",
        "Amazon EFS",
        "Amazon S3"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon EC2 instance store"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "16",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Organizers for a global event want to put daily reports online as static HTML pages. The pages are expected to generate millions of views from users around the world. The files are stored in an Amazon S3 bucket. A solutions architect has been asked to design an efficient and effective solution. Which action should the solutions architect take to accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Generate presigned URLs for the files.",
        "Use cross-Region replication to all Regions.",
        "Use the geoproximity feature of Amazon Route 53.",
        "Use Amazon CloudFront with the S3 bucket as its origin."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon CloudFront with the S3 bucket as its origin."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "17",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a new service behind Amazon API Gateway. The request patterns for the service will be unpredictable and can change suddenly from 0 requests to over 500 per second. The total size of the data that needs to be persisted in a database is currently less than 1 GB with unpredictable future growth. Data can be queried using simple key-value requests. Which combination of AWS services would meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "AWS Fargate",
        "AWS Lambda",
        "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling",
        "MySQL-compatible Amazon Aurora"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Lambda",
        "Amazon DynamoDB"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "18",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A start-up company has a web application based in the us-east-1 Region with multiple Amazon EC2 instances running behind an Application Load Balancer across multiple Availability Zones. As the companys user base grows in the us-west-1 Region, it needs a solution with low latency and high availability. What should a solutions architect do to accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Provision EC2 instances in us-west-1. Switch the Application Load Balancer to a Network Load Balancer to achieve cross-Region load balancing.",
        "Provision EC2 instances and an Application Load Balancer in us-west-1. Make the load balancer distribute the traffic based on the location of the request.",
        "Provision EC2 instances and configure an Application Load Balancer in us-west-1. Create an accelerator in AWS Global Accelerator that uses an endpoint group that includes the load balancer endpoints in both Regions.",
        "Provision EC2 instances and configure an Application Load Balancer in us-west-1. Configure Amazon Route 53 with a weighted routing policy. Create alias records in Route 53 that point to the Application Load Balancer."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Provision EC2 instances and configure an Application Load Balancer in us-west-1. Create an accelerator in AWS Global Accelerator that uses an endpoint group that includes the load balancer endpoints in both Regions."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "19",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a solution to access a catalog of images and provide users with the ability to submit requests to customize images. Image customization parameters will be in any request sent to an AWS API Gateway API. The customized image will be generated on demand, and users will receive a link they can click to view or download their customized image. The solution must be highly available for viewing and customizing images. What is the MOST cost-effective solution to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon EC2 instances to manipulate the original image into the requested customization. Store the original and manipulated images in Amazon S3. Configure an Elastic Load Balancer in front of the EC2 instances.",
        "Use AWS Lambda to manipulate the original image to the requested customization. Store the original and manipulated images in Amazon S3. Configure an Amazon CloudFront distribution with the S3 bucket as the origin.",
        "Use AWS Lambda to manipulate the original image to the requested customization. Store the original images in Amazon S3 and the manipulated images in Amazon DynamoDB. Configure an Elastic Load Balancer in front of the Amazon EC2 instances.",
        "Use Amazon EC2 instances to manipulate the original image into the requested customization. Store the original images in Amazon S3 and the manipulated images in Amazon DynamoDB. Configure an Amazon CloudFront distribution with the S3 bucket as the origin."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use AWS Lambda to manipulate the original image to the requested customization. Store the original and manipulated images in Amazon S3. Configure an Amazon CloudFront distribution with the S3 bucket as the origin."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "20",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is planning to migrate a business-critical dataset to Amazon S3. The current solution design uses a single S3 bucket in the us-east-1 Region with versioning enabled to store the dataset. The companys disaster recovery policy states that all data multiple AWS Regions. How should a solutions architect design the S3 solution?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an additional S3 bucket in another Region and configure cross-Region replication.",
        "Create an additional S3 bucket in another Region and configure cross-origin resource sharing (CORS).",
        "Create an additional S3 bucket with versioning in another Region and configure cross-Region replication.",
        "Create an additional S3 bucket with versioning in another Region and configure cross-origin resource (CORS)."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an additional S3 bucket with versioning in another Region and configure cross-Region replication."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "21",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has application running on Amazon EC2 instances in a VPC. One of the applications needs to call an Amazon S3 API to store and read objects. The companys security policies restrict any internet-bound traffic from the applications. Which action will fulfill these requirements and maintain security?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure an S3 interface endpoint.",
        "Configure an S3 gateway endpoint.",
        "Create an S3 bucket in a private subnet.",
        "Create an S3 bucket in the same Region as the EC2 instance."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure an S3 gateway endpoint."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "22",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys web application uses an Amazon RDS PostgreSQL DB instance to store its application data. During the financial closing period at the start of every month. Accountants run large queries that impact the databases performance due to high usage. The company wants to minimize the impact that the reporting activity has on the web application. What should a solutions architect do to reduce the impact on the database with the LEAST amount of effort?",
      "answers": [
        "Create a read replica and direct reporting traffic to the replica.",
        "Create a Multi-AZ database and direct reporting traffic to the standby.",
        "Create a cross-Region read replica and direct reporting traffic to the replica.",
        "Create an Amazon Redshift database and direct reporting traffic to the Amazon Redshift database."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a read replica and direct reporting traffic to the replica."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "23",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate a high performance computing (HPC) application and data from on-premises to the AWS Cloud. The company uses tiered storage on premises with hot high-performance parallel storage to support the application during periodic runs of the application, and more economical cold storage to hold the data when the application is not actively running. Which combination of solutions should a solutions architect recommend to support the storage needs of the application? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon S3 for cold data storage",
        "Amazon EFS for cold data storage",
        "Amazon S3 for high-performance parallel storage",
        "Amazon FSx for Lustre for high-performance parallel storage",
        "Amazon FSx for Windows for high-performance parallel storage"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon S3 for cold data storage",
        "Amazon FSx for Lustre for high-performance parallel storage"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "24",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A companys application is running on Amazon EC2 instances in a single Region. In the event of a disaster, a solutions architect needs to ensure that the resources can also be deployed to a second Region. Which combination of actions should the solutions architect take to accomplish this? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Detach a volume on an EC2 instance and copy it to Amazon S3.",
        "Launch a new EC2 instance from an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) in a new Region.",
        "Launch a new EC2 instance in a new Region and copy a volume from Amazon S3 to the new instance.",
        "Copy an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) of an EC2 instance and specify a different Region for the destination.",
        "Copy an Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume from Amazon S3 and launch an EC2 instance in the destination Region using that EBS volume."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Launch a new EC2 instance from an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) in a new Region.",
        "Copy an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) of an EC2 instance and specify a different Region for the destination."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "25",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A solutions architect needs to ensure that API calls to Amazon DynamoDB from Amazon EC2 instances in a VPC do not traverse the internet. What should the solutions architect do to accomplish this? (Choose two.) ",
      "answers": [
        "Create a route table entry for the endpoint.",
        "Create a gateway endpoint for DynamoDB.",
        "Create a new DynamoDB table that uses the endpoint.",
        "Create an ENI for the endpoint in each of the subnets of the VPC.",
        "Create a security group entry in the default security group to provide access."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a route table entry for the endpoint.",
        "Create a gateway endpoint for DynamoDB."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "26",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys legacy application is currently relying on a single-instance Amazon RDS MySQL database without encryption. Due to new compliance requirements, all existing and new data in this database must be encrypted. How should this be accomplished?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an Amazon S3 bucket with server-side encryption enabled. Move all the data to Amazon S3. Delete the RDS instance.",
        "Enable RDS Multi-AZ mode with encryption at rest enabled. Perform a failover to the standby instance to delete the original instance.",
        "Take a Snapshot of the RDS instance. Create an encrypted copy of the snapshot. Restore the RDS instance from the encrypted snapshot.",
        "Create an RDS read replica with encryption at rest enabled. Promote the read replica to master and switch the over to the new master. Delete the old RDS instance."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Take a Snapshot of the RDS instance. Create an encrypted copy of the snapshot. Restore the RDS instance from the encrypted snapshot."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "27",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A manufacturing company wants to implement predictive maintenance on its machinery equipment. The company will install thousands of IoT sensors that will send data to AWS in real time. A solutions architect is tasked with implementing a solution that will receive events in an ordered manner for each machinery asset and ensure that data is saved for further processing at a later time. Which solution would be MOST efficient?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon Kinesis Data Streams for real-time events with a partition for each equipment asset. Use Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose to save data to Amazon S3.",
        "Use Amazon Kinesis Data Streams for real-time events with a shard for each equipment asset. Use Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose to save data to Amazon EBS.",
        "Use an Amazon SQS FIFO queue for real-time events with one queue for each equipment asset. Trigger an AWS Lambda function for the SQS queue to save data to Amazon EFS.",
        "Use an Amazon SQS standard queue for real-time events with one queue for each equipment asset. Trigger an AWS Lambda function from the SQS queue to save data to Amazon S3."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon Kinesis Data Streams for real-time events with a partition for each equipment asset. Use Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose to save data to Amazon S3."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "28",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys website runs on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). The website has a mix of dynamic and static content. Users around the globe are reporting that the website is slow. Which set of actions will improve website performance for users worldwide?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an Amazon CloudFront distribution and configure the ALB as an origin. Then update the Amazon Route 53 record to point to the CloudFront distribution.",
        "Create a latency-based Amazon Route 53 record for the ALB. Then launch new EC2 instances with larger instance sizes and register the instances with the ALB.",
        "Launch new EC2 instances hosting the same web application in different Regions closer to the users. Then register instances with the same ALB using cross- Region VPC peering.",
        "Host the website in an Amazon S3 bucket in the Regions closest to the users and delete the ALB and EC2 instances. Then update an Amazon Route 53 record to point to the S3 buckets."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Amazon CloudFront distribution and configure the ALB as an origin. Then update the Amazon Route 53 record to point to the CloudFront distribution."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "29",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has been storing analytics data in an Amazon RDS instance for the past few years. The company asked a solutions architect to find a solution that allows users to access this data using an API. The expectation is that the application will experience periods of inactivity but could receive bursts of traffic within seconds. Which solution should the solutions architect suggest?",
      "answers": [
        "Set up an Amazon API Gateway and use Amazon ECS.",
        "Set up an Amazon API Gateway and use AWS Elastic Beanstalk.",
        "Set up an Amazon API Gateway and use AWS Lambda functions.",
        "Set up an Amazon API Gateway and use Amazon EC2 with Auto Scaling."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Set up an Amazon API Gateway and use AWS Lambda functions."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "30",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company must generate sales reports at the beginning of every month. The reporting process launches 20 Amazon EC2 instances on the first of the month. The process runs for 7 days and cannot be interrupted. The company wants to minimize costs. Which pricing model should the company choose?",
      "answers": [
        "Reserved Instances",
        "Spot Block Instances",
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Scheduled Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["On-Demand Instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "31",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A gaming company has multiple Amazon EC2 instances in a single Availability Zone for its multiplayer game that communicates with users on Layer 4. The chief technology officer (CTO) wants to make the architecture highly available and cost-effective. Which should a solutions architect do to meet these requirements? (Choose two.)? ",
      "answers": [
        "Increase the number of EC2 instances.",
        "Decrease the number of EC2 instances.",
        "Configure a Network Load Balancer in front of the EC2 instances.",
        "Configure an Application Load Balancer in front of the EC2 instances.",
        "Configure an Auto Scaling group to add or remove instances in multiple Availability Zones automatically."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure a Network Load Balancer in front of the EC2 instances.",
        "Configure an Auto Scaling group to add or remove instances in multiple Availability Zones automatically."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "32",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company currently operates a web application backed by an Amazon RDS MySQL database. It has automated backups that are run daily and are not encrypted. A security audit requires future backups to be encrypted and the unencrypted backups to be destroyed. The company will make at least one encrypted backup before destroying the old backups. What should be done to enable encryption for future backups?",
      "answers": [
        "Enable default encryption for the Amazon S3 bucket where backups are stored.",
        "Modify the backup section of the database configuration to toggle the Enable encryption check box.",
        "Create a snapshot of the database. Copy it to an encrypted snapshot. Restore the database from the encrypted snapshot.",
        "Enable an encrypted read replica on RDS for MySQL. Promote the encrypted read replica to primary. Remove the original database instance."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a snapshot of the database. Copy it to an encrypted snapshot. Restore the database from the encrypted snapshot."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "33",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is hosting a website behind multiple Application Load Balancers. The company has different distribution rights for its content around the world. A solutions architect needs to ensure that users are served the correct content without violating distribution rights. Which configuration should the solutions architect choose to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure Amazon CloudFront with AWS WAF.",
        "Configure Application Load Balancers with AWS WAF.",
        "Configure Amazon Route 53 with a geolocation policy.",
        "Configure Amazon Route 53 with a geoproximity routing policy."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure Amazon CloudFront with AWS WAF."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "34",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A solution architect has created a new AWS account and must secure AWS account root user access. Which combination of actions will accomplish this? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Ensure the root user uses a strong password.",
        "Enable multi-factor authentication to the root user.",
        "Store root user access keys in an encrypted Amazon S3 bucket.",
        "Add the root user to a group containing administrative permissions.",
        "Apply the required permissions to the root user with an inline policy document."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Ensure the root user uses a strong password.",
        "Enable multi-factor authentication to the root user."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "35",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect at an ecommerce company wants to back up application log data to Amazon S3. The solutions architect is unsure how frequently the logs will be accessed or which logs will be accessed the most. The company wants to keep costs as low as possible by using the appropriate S3 storage class. Which S3 storage class should be implemented to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "S3 Glacier",
        "S3 Intelligent-Tiering",
        "S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA)",
        "S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["S3 Intelligent-Tiering"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "36",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys website is used to sell products to the public. The site runs on Amazon EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). There is also an Amazon CloudFront distribution, and AWS WAF is being used to protect against SQL injection attacks. The ALB is the origin for the CloudFront distribution. A recent review of security logs revealed an external malicious IP that needs to be blocked from accessing the website. What should a solutions architect do to protect the application?",
      "answers": [
        "Modify the network ACL on the CloudFront distribution to add a deny rule for the malicious IP address.",
        "Modify the configuration of AWS WAF to add an IP match condition to block the malicious IP address.",
        "Modify the network ACL for the EC2 instances in the target groups behind the ALB to deny the malicious IP address.",
        "Modify the security groups for the EC2 instances in the target groups behind the ALB to deny the malicious IP address."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Modify the configuration of AWS WAF to add an IP match condition to block the malicious IP address."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "37",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing an application for a two-step order process. The first step is synchronous and must return to the user with little latency. The second step takes longer, so it will be implemented in a separate component. Orders must be processed exactly once and in the order in which they are received. How should the solutions architect integrate these components?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon SQS FIFO queues.",
        "Use an AWS Lambda function along with Amazon SQS standard queues.",
        "Create an SNS topic and subscribe an Amazon SQS FIFO queue to that topic.",
        "Create an SNS topic and subscribe an Amazon SQS Standard queue to that topic."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an SNS topic and subscribe an Amazon SQS FIFO queue to that topic."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "38",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A web application is deployed in the AWS Cloud. It consists of a two-tier architecture that includes a web layer and a database layer. The web server is vulnerable to cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. What should a solutions architect do to remediate the vulnerability?",
      "answers": [
        "Create a Classic Load Balancer. Put the web layer behind the load balancer and enable AWS WAF.",
        "Create a Network Load Balancer. Put the web layer behind the load balancer and enable AWS WAF.",
        "Create an Application Load Balancer. Put the web layer behind the load balancer and enable AWS WAF.",
        "Create an Application Load Balancer. Put the web layer behind the load balancer and use AWS Shield Standard."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Application Load Balancer. Put the web layer behind the load balancer and enable AWS WAF."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "39",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys website is using an Amazon RDS MySQL Multi-AZ DB instance for its transactional data storage. There are other internal systems that query this DB instance to fetch data for internal batch processing. The RDS DB instance slows down significantly the internal systems fetch data. This impacts the websites read and write performance, and the users experience slow response times. Which solution will improve the websites performance?",
      "answers": [
        "Use an RDS PostgreSQL DB instance instead of a MySQL database.",
        "Use Amazon ElastiCache to cache the query responses for the website.",
        "Add an additional Availability Zone to the current RDS MySQL Multi.AZ DB instance.",
        "Add a read replica to the RDS DB instance and configure the internal systems to query the read replica."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Add a read replica to the RDS DB instance and configure the internal systems to query the read replica."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "40",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An application runs on Amazon EC2 instances across multiple Availability Zones. The instances run in an Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling group behind an Application Load Balancer. The application performs best when the CPU utilization of the EC2 instances is at or near 40%. What should a solutions architect do to maintain the desired performance across all instances in the group? ",
      "answers": [
        "Use a simple scaling policy to dynamically scale the Auto Scaling group.",
        "Use a target tracking policy to dynamically scale the Auto Scaling group.",
        "Use an AWS Lambda function to update the desired Auto Scaling group capacity.",
        "Use scheduled scaling actions to scale up and scale down the Auto Scaling group."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use a target tracking policy to dynamically scale the Auto Scaling group."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "41",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company runs an internal browser-based application. The application runs on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer. The instances run in an Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling group across multiple Availability Zones. The Auto Scaling group scales up to 20 instances during work hours, but scales down to 2 instances overnight. Staff are complaining that the application is very slow when the day begins, although it runs well by mid-morning. How should the scaling be changed to address the staff complaints and keep costs to a minimum?",
      "answers": [
        "Implement a scheduled action that sets the desired capacity to 20 shortly before the office opens.",
        "Implement a step scaling action triggered at a lower CPU threshold, and decrease the cooldown period.",
        "Implement a target tracking action triggered at a lower CPU threshold, and decrease the cooldown period.",
        "Implement a scheduled action that sets the minimum and maximum capacity to 20 shortly before the office opens."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Implement a step scaling action triggered at a lower CPU threshold, and decrease the cooldown period."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "42",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A financial services company has a web application that serves users in the United States and Europe. The application consists of a database tier and a web server tier. The database tier consists of a MySQL database hosted in us-east-1. Amazon Route 53 geoproximity routing is used to direct traffic to instances in the closest Region. A performance review of the system reveals that European users are not receiving the same level of query performance as those in the United States. Which changes should be made to the database tier to improve performance?",
      "answers": [
        "Migrate the database to Amazon RDS for MySQL. Configure Multi-AZ in one of the European Regions.",
        "Migrate the database to Amazon DynamoDB. Use DynamoDB global tables to enable replication to additional Regions.",
        "Deploy MySQL instances in each Region. Deploy an Application Load Balancer in front of MySQL to reduce the load on the primary instance.",
        "Migrate the database to an Amazon Aurora global database in MySQL compatibility mode. Configure read replicas in one of the European Regions."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Migrate the database to an Amazon Aurora global database in MySQL compatibility mode. Configure read replicas in one of the European Regions."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "43",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company hosts a static website on-premises and wants to migrate the website to AWS. The website should load as quickly as possible for users around the world. The company also wants the most cost-effective solution. What should a solutions architect do to accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Copy the website content to an Amazon S3 bucket. Configure the bucket to serve static webpage content. Replicate the S3 bucket to multiple AWS Regions.",
        "Copy the website content to an Amazon S3 bucket. Configure the bucket to serve static webpage content. Configure Amazon CloudFront with the S3 bucket as the origin.",
        "Copy the website content to an Amazon EBS-backed Amazon EC2 instance running Apache HTTP Server. Configure Amazon Route 53 geolocation routing policies to select the closest origin.",
        "Copy the website content to multiple Amazon EBS-backed Amazon EC2 instances running Apache HTTP Server in multiple AWS Regions. Configure Amazon CloudFront geolocation routing policies to select the closest origin."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Copy the website content to an Amazon S3 bucket. Configure the bucket to serve static webpage content. Configure Amazon CloudFront with the S3 bucket as the origin."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "44",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing storage for a high performance computing (HPC) environment based on Amazon Linux. The workload stores and processes a large amount of engineering drawings that require shared storage and heavy computing. Which storage option would be the optimal solution? ",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
        "Amazon FSx for Lustre",
        "Amazon EC2 instance store",
        "Amazon EBS Provisioned IOPS SSD (io1)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon FSx for Lustre"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "45",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is performing an AWS Well-Architected Framework review of an existing workload deployed on AWS. The review identified a public-facing website running on the same Amazon EC2 instance as a Microsoft Active Directory domain controller that was install recently to support other AWS services. A solutions architect needs to recommend a new design that would improve the security of the architecture and minimize the administrative demand on IT staff. What should the solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Use AWS Directory Service to create a managed Active Directory. Uninstall Active Directory on the current EC2 instance.",
        "Create another EC2 instance in the same subnet and reinstall Active Directory on it. Uninstall Active Directory.",
        "Use AWS Directory Service to create an Active Directory connector. Proxy Active Directory requests to the Active domain controller running on the current EC2 instance.",
        "Enable AWS Single Sign-On (AWS SSO) with Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) 2.0 federation with the current Active Directory controller. Modify the EC2 instances security group to deny public access to Active Directory."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use AWS Directory Service to create a managed Active Directory. Uninstall Active Directory on the current EC2 instance."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "46",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company hosts a static website within an Amazon S3 bucket. A solutions architect needs to ensure that data can be recovered in case of accidental deletion. Which action will accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Enable Amazon S3 versioning.",
        "Enable Amazon S3 Intelligent-Tiering.",
        "Enable an Amazon S3 lifecycle policy.",
        "Enable Amazon S3 cross-Region replication."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Enable Amazon S3 versioning."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "47",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys production application runs online transaction processing (OLTP) transactions on an Amazon RDS MySQL DB instance. The company is launching a new reporting tool that will access the same data. The reporting tool must be highly available and not impact the performance of the production application. How can this be achieved?",
      "answers": [
        "Create hourly snapshots of the production RDS DB instance.",
        "Create a Multi-AZ RDS Read Replica of the production RDS DB instance.",
        "Create multiple RDS Read Replicas of the production RDS DB instance. Place the Read Replicas in an Auto Scaling group.",
        "Create a Single-AZ RDS Read Replica of the production RDS DB instance. Create a second Single-AZ RDS Read Replica from the replica."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a Multi-AZ RDS Read Replica of the production RDS DB instance."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "48",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company runs an application in a branch office within a small data closet with no virtualized compute resources. The application data is stored on an NFS volume. Compliance standards require a daily offsite backup of the NFS volume. Which solution meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Install an AWS Storage Gateway file gateway on premises to replicate the data to Amazon S3.",
        "Install an AWS Storage Gateway file gateway hardware appliance on premises to replicate the data to Amazon S3.",
        "Install an AWS Storage Gateway volume gateway with stored volumes on premises to replicate the data to Amazon S3.",
        "Install an AWS Storage Gateway volume gateway with cached volumes on premises to replicate the data to Amazon S3."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Install an AWS Storage Gateway file gateway hardware appliance on premises to replicate the data to Amazon S3."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "49",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys web application is using multiple Linux Amazon EC2 instances and storing data on Amazon EBS volumes. The company is looking for a solution to increase the resiliency of the application in case of a failure and to provide storage that complies with atomicity, consistency, isolation, and durability (ACID). What should a solutions architect do to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Launch the application on EC2 instances in each Availability Zone. Attach EBS volumes to each EC2 instance.",
        "Create an Application Load Balancer with Auto Scaling groups across multiple Availability Zones. Mount an instance store on each EC2 instance.",
        "Create an Application Load Balancer with Auto Scaling groups across multiple Availability Zones. Store data on Amazon EFS and mount a target on each instance.",
        "Create an Application Load Balancer with Auto Scaling groups across multiple Availability Zones. Store data using Amazon S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA)."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Application Load Balancer with Auto Scaling groups across multiple Availability Zones. Store data on Amazon EFS and mount a target on each instance."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "50",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A security team to limit access to specific services or actions in all of the teams AWS accounts. All accounts belong to a large organization in AWS Organizations. The solution must be scalable and there must be a single point where permission can be maintained. What should a solutions architect do to accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an ACL to provide access to the services or actions.",
        "Create a security group to allow accounts and attach it to user groups.",
        "Create cross-account roles in each account to deny access to the services or actions.",
        "Create a service control policy in the root organizational unit to deny access to the services or actions."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a service control policy in the root organizational unit to deny access to the services or actions."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "51",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A data science team requires storage for nightly log processing. The size and number of logs is unknown and will persist for 24 hours only. What is the MOST cost-effective solution? ",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon S3 Glacier",
        "Amazon S3 Standard",
        "Amazon S3 Intelligent-Tiering",
        "Amazon S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon S3 Standard"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "52",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is hosting a web application on AWS using a single Amazon EC2 instance that stores user-uploaded documents in an Amazon EBS volume. For better scalability and availability, the company duplicated the architecture and created a second EC2 instance and EBS volume in another Availability Zone, placing both behind an Application Load Balancer. After completing this change, users reported that each time they refreshed the website, they could see one subset of their documents or the other, but never all of the documents at the same time. What should a solutions architect propose to ensure users see all of their documents at once?",
      "answers": [
        "Copy the data so both EBS volumes contain all the documents.",
        "Configure the Application Load Balancer to direct a user to the server with the documents.",
        "Copy the data from both EBS volumes to Amazon EFS. Modify the application to save new documents to Amazon EFS.",
        "Configure the Application Load Balancer to send the request to both servers. Return each document from the correct server."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Copy the data from both EBS volumes to Amazon EFS. Modify the application to save new documents to Amazon EFS."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "53",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is planning to use Amazon S3 to store images uploaded by its users. The images must be encrypted at rest in Amazon S3. The company does not want to spend time managing and rotating the keys, but it does want to control who can access those keys. What should a solutions architect use to accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Server-Side Encryption with keys stored in an S3 bucket",
        "Server-Side Encryption with Customer-Provided Keys (SSE-C)",
        "Server-Side Encryption with Amazon S3-Managed Keys (SSE-S3)",
        "Server-Side Encryption with AWS KMS-Managed Keys (SSE-KMS)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Server-Side Encryption with AWS KMS-Managed Keys (SSE-KMS)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "54",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is running an ecommerce application on Amazon EC2. The application consists of a stateless web tier that requires a minimum of 10 instances, and a peak of 250 instances to support the applications usage. The application requires 50 instances 80% of the time. Which solution should be used to minimize costs?",
      "answers": [
        "Purchase Reserved Instances to cover 250 instances.",
        "Purchase Reserved Instances to cover 80 instances. Use Spot Instances to cover the remaining instances.",
        "Purchase On-Demand Instances to cover 40 instances. Use Spot Instances to cover the remaining instances.",
        "Purchase Reserved Instances to cover 50 instances. Use On-Demand and Spot Instances to cover the remaining instances."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Purchase Reserved Instances to cover 50 instances. Use On-Demand and Spot Instances to cover the remaining instances."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "55",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A company has deployed an API in a VPC behind an internet-facing Application Load Balancer (ALB). An application that consumes the API as a client is deployed in a second account in private subnets behind a NAT gateway. When requests to the client application increase, the NAT gateway costs are higher than expected. A solutions architect has configured the ALB to be internal. Which combination of architectural changes will reduce the NAT gateway costs? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Configure a VPC peering connection between the two VPCs. Access the API using the private address.",
        "Configure an AWS Direct Connect connection between the two VPCs. Access the API using the private address.",
        "Configure a ClassicLink connection for the API into the client VPC. Access the API using the ClassicLink address.",
        "Configure a PrivateLink connection for the API into the client VPC. Access the API using the PrivateLink address.",
        "Configure an AWS Resource Access Manager connection between the two accounts. Access the API using the private address."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure a VPC peering connection between the two VPCs. Access the API using the private address.",
        "Configure a PrivateLink connection for the API into the client VPC. Access the API using the PrivateLink address."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "56",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is tasked with transferring 750 TB of data from a network-attached file system located at a branch office Amazon S3 Glacier. The solution must avoid saturating the branch offices low-bandwidth internet connection. What is the MOST cost-effective solution?",
      "answers": [
        "Create a site-to-site VPN tunnel to an Amazon S3 bucket and transfer the files directly. Create a bucket VPC endpoint.",
        "Order 10 AWS Snowball appliances and select an S3 Glacier vault as the destination. Create a bucket policy to enforce VPC endpoint.",
        "Mount the network-attached file system to Amazon S3 and copy the files directly. Create a lifecycle policy to S3 objects to Amazon S3 Glacier.",
        "Order 10 AWS Snowball appliances and select an Amazon S3 bucket as the destination. Create a lifecycle policy to transition the S3 objects to Amazon S3 Glacier."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Order 10 AWS Snowball appliances and select an Amazon S3 bucket as the destination. Create a lifecycle policy to transition the S3 objects to Amazon S3 Glacier."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "57",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A company has a two-tier application architecture that runs in public and private subnets. Amazon EC2 instances running the web application are in the public subnet and a database runs on the private subnet. The web application instances and the database are running in a single Availability Zone (AZ). Which combination of steps should a solutions architect take to provide high availability for this architecture? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Create new public and private subnets in the same AZ for high availability.",
        "Create an Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling group and Application Load Balancer spanning multiple AZs.",
        "Add the existing web application instances to an Auto Scaling group behind an Application Load Balancer.",
        "Create new public and private subnets in a new AZ. Create a database using Amazon EC2 in one AZ.",
        "Create new public and private subnets in the same VPC, each in a new AZ. Migrate the database to an Amazon RDS multi-AZ deployment."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling group and Application Load Balancer spanning multiple AZs.",
        "Create new public and private subnets in the same VPC, each in a new AZ. Migrate the database to an Amazon RDS multi-AZ deployment."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "58",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A solutions architect is implementing a document review application using an Amazon S3 bucket for storage. The solution must prevent an accidental deletion of the documents and ensure that all versions of the documents are available. Users must be able to download, modify, and upload documents. Which combination of actions should be taken to meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Enable a read-only bucket ACL.",
        "Enable versioning on the bucket.",
        "Attach an IAM policy to the bucket.",
        "Enable MFA Delete on the bucket.",
        "Encrypt the bucket using AWS KMS."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Enable versioning on the bucket.",
        "Enable MFA Delete on the bucket."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "59",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An application hosted on AWS is experiencing performance problems, and the application vendor wants to perform an analysis of the log file to troubleshoot further. The log file is stored on Amazon S3 and is 10 GB in size. The application owner will make the log file available to the vendor for a limited time. What is the MOST secure way to do this?",
      "answers": [
        "Enable public read on the S3 object and provide the link to the vendor.",
        "Upload the file to Amazon WorkDocs and share the public link with the vendor.",
        "Generate a presigned URL and have the vendor download the log file before it expires.",
        "Create an IAM user for the vendor to provide access to the S3 bucket and the application. Enforce multi-factor authentication."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Generate a presigned URL and have the vendor download the log file before it expires."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "60",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a two-tier web application. The application consists of a public-facing web tier hosted on Amazon EC2 in public subnets. The database tier consists of Microsoft SQL Server running on Amazon EC2 in a private subnet. Security is a high priority for the company. How should security groups be configured in this situation? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Configure the security group for the web tier to allow inbound traffic on port 443 from 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Configure the security group for the web tier to allow outbound traffic on port 443 from 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Configure the security group for the database tier to allow inbound traffic on port 1433 from the security group for the web tier.",
        "Configure the security group for the database tier to allow outbound traffic on ports 443 and 1433 to the security group for the web tier.",
        "Configure the security group for the database tier to allow inbound traffic on ports 443 and 1433 from the security group for the web tier."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure the security group for the web tier to allow inbound traffic on port 443 from 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Configure the security group for the database tier to allow inbound traffic on port 1433 from the security group for the web tier."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "61",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company allows its developers to attach existing IAM policies to existing IAM roles to enable faster experimentation and agility. However, the security operations team is concerned that the developers could attach the existing administrator policy, which would allow the developers to circumvent any other security policies. How should a solutions architect address this issue?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an Amazon SNS topic to send an alert every time a developer creates a new policy.",
        "Use service control policies to disable IAM activity across all account in the organizational unit.",
        "Prevent the developers from attaching any policies and assign all IAM duties to the security operations team.",
        "Set an IAM permissions boundary on the developer IAM role that explicitly denies attaching the administrator policy."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Set an IAM permissions boundary on the developer IAM role that explicitly denies attaching the administrator policy."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "62",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a multi-tier application that runs six front-end web servers in an Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling group in a single Availability Zone behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). A solutions architect needs to modify the infrastructure to be highly available without modifying the application. Which architecture should the solutions architect choose that provides high availability?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an Auto Scaling group that uses three instances across each of two Regions.",
        "Modify the Auto Scaling group to use three instances across each of two Availability Zones.",
        "Create an Auto Scaling template that can be used to quickly create more instances in another Region.",
        "Change the ALB in front of the Amazon EC2 instances in a round-robin configuration to balance traffic to the web tier."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Modify the Auto Scaling group to use three instances across each of two Availability Zones."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "63",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company runs an application on a group of Amazon Linux EC2 instances. The application writes log files using standard API calls. For compliance reasons, all log files must be retained indefinitely and will be analyzed by a reporting tool that must access all files concurrently. Which storage service should a solutions architect use to provide the MOST cost-effective solution?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon EBS",
        "Amazon EFS",
        "Amazon EC2 instance store",
        "Amazon S3"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon S3"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "64",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A media streaming company collects real-time data and stores it in a disk-optimized database system. The company is not getting the expected throughput and wants an in-memory database storage solution that performs faster and provides high availability using data replication. Which database should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon RDS for MySQL",
        "Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL.",
        "Amazon ElastiCache for Redis",
        "Amazon ElastiCache for Memcached"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon ElastiCache for Redis"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "65",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company hosts its product information webpages on AWS. The existing solution uses multiple Amazon C2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer in an Auto Scaling group. The website also uses a custom DNS name and communicates with HTTPS only using a dedicated SSL certificate. The company is planning a new product launch and wants to be sure that users from around the world have the best possible experience on the new website. What should a solutions architect do to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Redesign the application to use Amazon CloudFront.",
        "Redesign the application to use AWS Elastic Beanstalk.",
        "Redesign the application to use a Network Load Balancer.",
        "Redesign the application to use Amazon S3 static website hosting."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Redesign the application to use Amazon CloudFront."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "66",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing the cloud architecture for a new application being deployed on AWS. The process should run in parallel while adding and removing application nodes as needed based on the number of jobs to be processed. The processor application is stateless. The solutions architect must ensure that the application is loosely coupled and the job items are durably stored. Which design should the solutions architect use?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an Amazon SNS topic to send the jobs that need to be processed. Create an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) that consists of the processor application. Create a launch configuration that uses the AMI. Create an Auto Scaling group using the launch configuration. Set the scaling policy for the Auto Scaling group to add and remove nodes based on CPU usage.",
        "Create an Amazon SQS queue to hold the jobs that need to be processed. Create an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) that consists of the processor application. Create a launch configuration that uses the AMI. Create an Auto Scaling group using the launch configuration. Set the scaling policy for the Auto Scaling group to add and remove nodes based on network usage.",
        "Create an Amazon SQS queue to hold the jobs that need to be processed. Create an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) that consists of the processor application. Create a launch template that uses the AMI. Create an Auto Scaling group using the launch template. Set the scaling policy for the Auto Scaling group to add and remove nodes based on the number of items in the SQS queue.",
        "Create an Amazon SNS topic to send the jobs that need to be processed. Create an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) that consists of the processor application. Create a launch template that uses the AMI. Create an Auto Scaling group using the launch template. Set the scaling policy for the Auto Scaling group to add and remove nodes based on the number of messages published to the SNS topic."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Amazon SQS queue to hold the jobs that need to be processed. Create an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) that consists of the processor application. Create a launch template that uses the AMI. Create an Auto Scaling group using the launch template. Set the scaling policy for the Auto Scaling group to add and remove nodes based on the number of items in the SQS queue."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "67",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A marketing company is storing CSV files in an Amazon S3 bucket for statistical analysis. An application on an Amazon EC2 instance needs permission to efficiently process the CSV data stored in the S3 bucket. Which action will MOST securely grant the EC2 instance access to the S3 bucket?",
      "answers": [
        "Attach a resource-based policy to the S3 bucket.",
        "Create an IAM user for the application with specific permissions to the S3 bucket.",
        "Associate an IAM role with least privilege permissions to the EC2 instance profile.",
        "Store AWS credentials directly on the EC2 instance for applications on the instance to use for API calls."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Associate an IAM role with least privilege permissions to the EC2 instance profile."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "68",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has on-premises servers running a relational database. The current database serves high read traffic for users in different locations. The company wants to migrate to AWS with the least amount of effort. The database solution should support disaster recovery and not affect the companys current traffic flow. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Use a database in Amazon RDS with Multi-AZ and at least one read replica.",
        "Use a database in Amazon RDS with Multi-AZ and at least one standby replica.",
        "Use databases hosted on multiple Amazon EC2 instances in different AWS Regions.",
        "Use databases hosted on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer in different Availability Zones."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use a database in Amazon RDS with Multi-AZ and at least one read replica."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "69",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys application is running on Amazon EC2 instances within an Auto Scaling group behind an Elastic Load Balancer. Based on the applications history the company anticipates a spike in traffic during a holiday each year. A solutions architect must design a strategy to ensure that the Auto Scaling group proactively increases capacity to minimize any performance impact on application users. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an Amazon CloudWatch alarm to scale up the EC2 instances when CPU utilization exceeds 90%.",
        "Create a recurring scheduled action to scale up the Auto Scaling group before the expected period of peak demand.",
        "Increase the minimum and maximum number of EC2 instances in the Auto Scaling group during the peak demand period.",
        "Configure an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) notification to send alerts when there are autoscaling EC2_INSTANCE_LAUNCH events."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a recurring scheduled action to scale up the Auto Scaling group before the expected period of peak demand."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "70",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company hosts an application on multiple Amazon EC2 instances. The application processes messages from an Amazon SQS queue, writes for an Amazon  RDS table, and deletes - the message from the queue. Occasional duplicate records are found in the RDS table. The SQS queue does not contain any duplicate messages. What should a solutions architect do to ensure messages are being processed once only?",
      "answers": [
        "Use the CreateQueue API call to create a new queue.",
        "Use the AddPermission API call to add appropriate permissions.",
        "Use the ReceiveMessage API call to set an appropriate wait time.",
        "Use the ChangeMessageVisibility API call to increase the visibility timeout."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use the ChangeMessageVisibility API call to increase the visibility timeout."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "71",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An Amazon EC2 administrator created the following policy associated with an IAM group containing several users:{ Version: 2012-10-17, Statement: [ { Effect: Allow, Action: ec2:TerminateInstances, Resources: *, Condition: { IpAddresses: { aws:SourceIp: 10.100.100.0/24 } } }, { Effect: Deny, Action: ec2:*, Resources: *, Condition: { StringNotEquals: { ec2:Region: us-east-1, } } } ] What is the effect of this policy?",
      "answers": [
        "Users can terminate an EC2 instance in any AWS Region except us-east-1.",
        "Users can terminate an EC2 instance with the IP address 10.100.100.1 in the us-east-1 Region.",
        "Users can terminate an EC2 instance in the us-east-1 Region when the users source IP is 10.100. 100.254.",
        "Users cannot terminate an EC2 instance in the us-east-1 Region when the users source IP is 10.100. 100.254."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Users can terminate an EC2 instance in the us-east-1 Region when the users source IP is 10.100. 100.254."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "72",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is optimizing a website for an upcoming musical event. Videos of the performances will be streamed in real time and then will be available on demand. The event is expected to attract a global online audience. Which service will improve the performance of both the real-time and on-demand steaming?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon CloudFront",
        "AWS Global Accelerator",
        "Amazon Route S3",
        "Amazon S3 Transfer Acceleration"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon CloudFront"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "73",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a three-tier image-sharing application. It uses an Amazon EC2 instance for the front-end layer, another for the backend tier, and a third for the MySQL database. A solutions architect has been tasked with designing a solution that is highly available, and requires the least amount of changes to the application Which solution meets these requirements? ",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon S3 to host the front-end layer and AWS Lambda functions for the backend layer. Move the database to an Amazon DynamoDB table and use Amazon S3 to store and serve users images.",
        "Use load-balanced Multi-AZ AWS Elastic Beanstalk environments for the front-end and backend layers. Move the database to an Amazon RDS instance with multiple read replicas to store and serve users images.",
        "Use Amazon S3 to host the front-end layer and a fleet of Amazon EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group for the backend layer. Move the database to a memory optimized instance type to store and serve users images.",
        "Use load-balanced Multi-AZ AWS Elastic Beanstalk environments for the front-end and backend layers. Move the database to an Amazon RDS instance with a Multi-AZ deployment. Use Amazon S3 to store and serve users images."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use load-balanced Multi-AZ AWS Elastic Beanstalk environments for the front-end and backend layers. Move the database to an Amazon RDS instance with a Multi-AZ deployment. Use Amazon S3 to store and serve users images."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "74",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a system to analyze the performance of financial markets while the markets are closed. The system will run a series of compute- intensive jobs for 4 hours every night. The time to complete the compute jobs is expected to remain constant, and jobs cannot be interrupted once started. Once completed, the system is expected to run for a minimum of 1 year. Which type of Amazon EC2 instances should be used to reduce the cost of the system?",
      "answers": [
        "Spot instances",
        "On-Demand instances",
        "Standard Reserved Instances",
        "Scheduled Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Standard Reserved Instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "75",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company built a food ordering application that captures user data and stores it for future analysis. The applications static front end is deployed on an Amazon EC2 instance. The front-end application sends the requests to the backend application running on separate EC2 instance. The backend application then stores the data in Amazon RDS. What should a solutions architect do to decouple the architecture and make it scalable?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon S3 to serve the front-end application, which sends requests to Amazon EC2 to execute the backend application. The backend application will process and store the data in Amazon RDS.",
        "Use Amazon S3 to serve the front-end application and write requests to an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topic. Subscribe Amazon EC2 instances to the HTTP/HTTPS endpoint of the topic, and process and store the data in Amazon RDS.",
        "Use an EC2 instance to serve the front end and write requests to an Amazon SQS queue. Place the backend instance in an Auto Scaling group, and scale based on the queue depth to process and store the data in Amazon RDS.",
        "Use Amazon S3 to serve the static front-end application and send requests to Amazon API Gateway, which writes the requests to an Amazon SQS queue. Place the backend instances in an Auto Scaling group, and scale based on the queue depth to process and store the data in Amazon RDS."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon S3 to serve the static front-end application and send requests to Amazon API Gateway, which writes the requests to an Amazon SQS queue. Place the backend instances in an Auto Scaling group, and scale based on the queue depth to process and store the data in Amazon RDS."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "76",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect needs to design a managed storage solution for a companys application that includes high-performance machine learning. This application runs on AWS Fargate, and the connected storage needs to have concurrent access to files and deliver high performance. Which storage option should the solutions architect recommend? ",
      "answers": [
        "Create an Amazon S3 bucket for the application and establish an IAM role for Fargate to communicate with Amazon S3.",
        "Create an Amazon FSx for Lustre file share and establish an IAM role that allows Fargate to communicate with FSx for Lustre.",
        "Create an Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) file share and establish an IAM role that allows Fargate to communicate with Amazon EFS.",
        "Create an Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume for the application and establish an IAM role that allows Fargate to communicate with Amazon EBS."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Amazon FSx for Lustre file share and establish an IAM role that allows Fargate to communicate with FSx for Lustre."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "77",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A bicycle sharing company is developing a multi-tier architecture to track the location of its bicycles during peak operating hours. The company wants to use these data points in its existing analytics platform. A solutions architect must determine the most viable multi-tier option to support this architecture. The data points must be accessible from the REST API. Which action meets these requirements for storing and retrieving location data?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon Athena with Amazon S3.",
        "Use Amazon API Gateway with AWS Lambda.",
        "Use Amazon QuickSight with Amazon Redshift.",
        "Use Amazon API Gateway with Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon Athena with Amazon S3."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "78",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a web application that will run on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). The company strictly requires that the application be resilient against malicious internet activity and attacks, and protect against new common vulnerabilities and exposures. What should the solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Leverage Amazon CloudFront with the ALB endpoint as the origin.",
        "Deploy an appropriate managed rule for AWS WAF and associate it with the ALB.",
        "Subscribe to AWS Shield Advanced and ensure common vulnerabilities and exposures are blocked.",
        "Configure network ACLs and security groups to allow only ports 80 and 443 to access the EC2 instances."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy an appropriate managed rule for AWS WAF and associate it with the ALB."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "79",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has an application that calls AWS Lambda functions. A recent code review found database credentials stored in the source code. The database credentials need to be removed from the Lambda source code. The credentials must then be securely stored and rotated on an ongoing basis to meet security policy requirements. What should a solutions architect recommend to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Store the password in AWS CloudHSM. Associate the Lambda function with a role that can retrieve the password from CloudHSM given its key ID.",
        "Store the password in AWS Secrets Manager. Associate the Lambda function with a role that can retrieve the password from Secrets Manager given its secret ID.",
        "Move the database password to an environment variable associated with the Lambda function. Retrieve the password from the environment variable upon execution.",
        "Store the password in AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS). Associate the Lambda function with a role that can retrieve the password from AWS KMS given its key ID."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Store the password in AWS Secrets Manager. Associate the Lambda function with a role that can retrieve the password from Secrets Manager given its secret ID."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "80",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is managing health records on-premises. The company must keep these records indefinitely, disable any modifications to the records once they are stored, and granularly audit access at all levels. The chief technology officer (CTO) is concerned because there are already millions of records not being used by any application, and the current infrastructure is running out of space. The CTO has requested a solutions architect design a solution to move existing data and support future records. Which services can the solutions architect recommend to meet these requirements? ",
      "answers": [
        "Use AWS DataSync to move existing data to AWS. Use Amazon S3 to store existing and new data. Enable Amazon S3 object lock and enable AWS CloudTrail with data events.",
        "Use AWS Storage Gateway to move existing data to AWS. Use Amazon S3 to store existing and new data. Enable Amazon S3 object lock and enable AWS CloudTrail with management events.",
        "Use AWS DataSync to move existing data to AWS. Use Amazon S3 to store existing and new data. Enable Amazon S3 object lock and enable AWS CloudTrail with management events.",
        "Use AWS Storage Gateway to move existing data to AWS. Use Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) to store existing and new data. Enable Amazon S3 object lock and enable Amazon S3 server access logging."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use AWS DataSync to move existing data to AWS. Use Amazon S3 to store existing and new data. Enable Amazon S3 object lock and enable AWS CloudTrail with data events."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "81",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company wants to use Amazon S3 for the secondary copy of its on-premises dataset. The company would rarely need to access this copy. The storage solutions cost should be minimal.\nWhich storage solution meets these requirements?\n",
      "answers": [
        "S3 Standard",
        "S3 Intelligent-Tiering",
        "S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA)",
        "S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "82",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys operations teams have an existing Amazon S3 bucket configured to notify an Amazon SQS queue when new object is created within the bucket. The development team also wants to receive events when new objects are created. The existing operations team workflow must remain intact. Which solution would satisfy these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Create another SQS queue. Update the S3 events in bucket to also update the new queue when a new object is created.",
        "Create a new SQS queue that only allows Amazon S3 to access the queue. Update Amazon S3 update this queue when a new object is created.",
        "Create an Amazon SNS topic and SQS queue for the Update. Update the bucket to send events to the new topic. Updates both queues to poll Amazon SNS.",
        "Create an Amazon SNS topic and SQS queue for the bucket updates. Update the bucket to send events to the new topic Add subscription for both queue in the topic."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Amazon SNS topic and SQS queue for the bucket updates. Update the bucket to send events to the new topic Add subscription for both queue in the topic."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "83",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An application runs on Amazon EC2 instances in private subnets. The application needs to access an Amazon DynamoDB table. What is the MOST secure way to access the table while ensuring that the traffic does not leave the AWS network? ",
      "answers": [
        "Use a VPC endpoint for DynamoDB.",
        "Use a NAT gateway in a public subnet.",
        "Use a NAT instance in a private subnet.",
        "Use the internet gateway attached to the VPC."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use a VPC endpoint for DynamoDB."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "84",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company built an application that lets users check in to places they visit, rank the places, and add reviews about their experiences. The application is successful with a rapid increase in the number of users every month. The chief technology officer fears the database supporting the current Infrastructure may not handle the new load the following month because the single Amazon RDS for MySQL instance has triggered alarms related to resource exhaustion due to read requests. What can a solutions architect recommend to prevent service Interruptions at the database layer with minimal changes to code?",
      "answers": [
        "Create RDS read replicas and redirect read-only traffic to the read replica endpoints. Enable a Multi-AZ deployment.",
        "Create an Amazon EMR cluster and migrate the data to a Hadoop Distributed File System (HDFS) with a replication factor of 3.",
        "Create an Amazon ElastiCache cluster and redirect all read-only traffic to the cluster. Set up the cluster to be deployed in three Availability Zones.",
        "Create an Amazon DynamoDB table to replace the RDS instance and redirect all read-only traffic to the DynamoDB table Enable DynamoDB Accelerator to offload traffic from the main table."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create RDS read replicas and redirect read-only traffic to the read replica endpoints. Enable a Multi-AZ deployment."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "85",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is looking for a solution that can store video archives in AWS from old news footage. The company needs to minimize costs and will rarely need to restore these files. When the files are needed, they must be available in a maximum of five minutes. What is the MOST cost-effective solution?",
      "answers": [
        "Store the video archives in Amazon S3 Glacier and use Expedited retrievals.",
        "Store the video archives in Amazon S3 Glacier and use Standard retrievals.",
        "Store the video archives in Amazon S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA).",
        "Store the video archives in Amazon S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA)."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Store the video archives in Amazon S3 Glacier and use Expedited retrievals."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "86",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has created a VPC with multiple private subnets in multiple Availability Zones (AZs) and one public subnet in one of the AZs. The public subnet is used to launch a NAT gateway. There is instance in the private subnet that use a NAT gateway to connect to the internet. In case of an AZ failure, the company wants to ensure that the instance is not all experiencing internet connectivity issues and that there is a backup plan ready. Which solution should a solutions architect recommend that is MOST highly available? ",
      "answers": [
        "Create a new public subnet with a NAT gateway in the same AZ. Distribute the traffic between the two NAT gateways.",
        "Create an Amazon EC2 NAT instance in a now public subnet. Distribute the traffic between the NAT gateway and the NAT instance.",
        "Create public subnets. In each AZ and launch a NAT gateway in each subnet. Configure the traffic from the private subnets in each AZ to the respective NAT gateway.",
        "Create an Amazon EC2 NAT instance in the same public subnet. Replace the NAT gateway with the NAT instance and associate the instance with an Auto Scaling group with an appropriate scaling policy."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create public subnets. In each AZ and launch a NAT gateway in each subnet. Configure the traffic from the private subnets in each AZ to the respective NAT gateway."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "87",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A healthcare company stores highly sensitive patient records. Compliance requires that multiple copies be stored in different locations. Each record must be stored for 7 years. The company has a service level agreement (SLA) to provide records to government agencies immediately for the first 30 days and then within 4 hours of a request thereafter. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon S3 with cross-Region replication enabled. After 30 days, transition the data to Amazon S3 Glacier using lifecycle policy.",
        "Use Amazon S3 with cross-origin resource sharing (CORS) enabled. After 30 days, transition the data to Amazon S3 Glacier using a lifecycle policy.",
        "Use Amazon S3 with cross-Region replication enabled. After 30 days, transition the data to Amazon S3 Glacier Deep Achieve using a lifecycle policy.",
        "Use Amazon S3 with cross-origin resource sharing (CORS) enabled. After 30 days, transition the data to Amazon S3 Glacier Deep Archive using a lifecycle policy."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon S3 with cross-Region replication enabled. After 30 days, transition the data to Amazon S3 Glacier using lifecycle policy."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "88",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company recently deployed a new auditing system to centralize information about operating system versions, patching, and installed software for Amazon EC2 instances. A solutions architect must ensure all instances provisioned through EC2 Auto Scaling groups successfully send reports to the auditing system as soon as they are launched and terminated. Which solution achieves these goals MOST efficiently?",
      "answers": [
        "Use a scheduled AWS Lambda function and execute a script remotely on all EC2 instances to send data to the audit system.",
        "Use EC2 Auto Scaling lifecycle hooks to execute a custom script to send data to the audit system when instances are launched and terminated.",
        "Use an EC2 Auto Scaling launch configuration to execute a custom script through user data to send data to the audit system when instances are launched and terminated.",
        "Execute a custom script on the instance operating system to send data to the audit system. Configure the script to be executed by the EC2 Auto Scaling group when the instance starts and is terminated."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use EC2 Auto Scaling lifecycle hooks to execute a custom script to send data to the audit system when instances are launched and terminated."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "89",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company recently implemented hybrid cloud connectivity using AWS Direct Connect and is migrating data to Amazon S3. The company is looking for a fully managed solution that will automate and accelerate the replication of data between the on-premises storage systems and AWS storage services. Which solution should a solutions architect recommend to keep the data private? ",
      "answers": [
        "Deploy an AWS DataSync agent tor the on-premises environment. Configure a sync job to replicate the data and connect it with an AWS service endpoint.",
        "Deploy an AWS DataSync agent for the on-premises environment. Schedule a batch job to replicate point-ln-time snapshots to AWS.",
        "Deploy an AWS Storage Gateway volume gateway for the on-premises environment. Configure it to store data locally, and asynchronously back up point-in- time snapshots to AWS.",
        "Deploy an AWS Storage Gateway file gateway for the on-premises environment. Configure it to store data locally, and asynchronously back up point-in-lime snapshots to AWS."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy an AWS DataSync agent tor the on-premises environment. Configure a sync job to replicate the data and connect it with an AWS service endpoint."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "90",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has 150 TB of archived image data stored on-premises that needs to be mowed to the AWS Cloud within the next month. The companys current network connection allows up to 100 Mbps uploads for this purpose during the night only. What is the MOST cost-effective mechanism to move this data and meet the migration deadline?",
      "answers": [
        "Use AWS Snowmobile to ship the data to AWS.",
        "Order multiple AWS Snowball devices to ship the data to AWS.",
        "Enable Amazon S3 Transfer Acceleration and securely upload the data.",
        "Create an Amazon S3 VPC endpoint and establish a VPN to upload the data."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Order multiple AWS Snowball devices to ship the data to AWS."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "91",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A public-facing web application queries a database hosted on an Amazon EC2 instance in a private subnet. A large number of queries involve multiple table joins, and the application performance has been degrading due to an increase in complex queries. The application team will be performing updates to improve performance. What should a solutions architect recommend to the application team? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Cache query data in Amazon SQS",
        "Create a read replica to offload queries",
        "Migrate the database to Amazon Athena",
        "Implement Amazon DynamoDB Accelerator to cache data.",
        "Migrate the database to Amazon RDS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a read replica to offload queries",
        "Migrate the database to Amazon RDS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "92",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is seeing access requests by some suspicious IP addresses. The security team discovers the requests are from different IP addresses under the same CIDR range. What should a solutions architect recommend to the team?",
      "answers": [
        "Add a rule in the inbound table of the security to deny the traffic from that CIDR range.",
        "Add a rule in the outbound table of the security group to deny the traffic from that CIDR range.",
        "Add a deny rule in the inbound table of the network ACL with a lower number than other rules.",
        "Add a deny rule in the outbound table of the network ACL with a lower rule number than other rules."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Add a deny rule in the inbound table of the network ACL with a lower number than other rules."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "93",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company recently expanded globally and wants to make its application accessible to users in those geographic locations. The application is deploying on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load balancer in an Auto Scaling group. The company needs the ability shift traffic from resources in one region to another. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure an Amazon Route 53 latency routing policy.",
        "Configure an Amazon Route 53 geolocation routing policy.",
        "Configure an Amazon Route 53 geoproximity fouling policy.",
        "Configure an Amazon Route 53 multivalue answer routing policy."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure an Amazon Route 53 geoproximity fouling policy."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "94",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company wants to replicate its data to AWS to recover in the event of a disaster. Today, a system administrator has scripts that copy data to a NFS share Individual backup files need to be accessed with low latency by application administrators to deal with errors in processing. What should a solutions architect recommend to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Modify the script to copy data to an Amazon S3 bucket instead of the on-premises NFS share.",
        "Modify the script to copy data to an Amazon S3 Glacier Archive instead of the on-premises NFS share.",
        "Modify the script to copy data to an Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) volume instead of the on-premises NFS share.",
        "Modify the script to copy data to an AWS Storage Gateway for File Gateway virtual appliance instead of the on-premises NFS share."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Modify the script to copy data to an AWS Storage Gateway for File Gateway virtual appliance instead of the on-premises NFS share."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "95",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An application requires a development environment (DEV) and production environment (PROD) for several years. The DEV instances will run for 10 hours each day during normal business hours, while the PROD instances will run 24 hours each day. A solutions architect needs to determine a compute instance purchase strategy to minimize costs. Which solution is the MOST cost-effective?",
      "answers": [
        "DEV with Spot Instances and PROD with On-Demand Instances",
        "DEV with On-Demand Instances and PROD with Spot Instances",
        "DEV with Scheduled Reserved Instances and PROD with Reserved Instances",
        "DEV with On-Demand Instances and PROD with Scheduled Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["DEV with Scheduled Reserved Instances and PROD with Reserved Instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "96",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company runs multiple Amazon EC2 Linux instances in a VPC with applications that use a hierarchical directory structure. The applications need to rapidly and concurrently read and write to shared storage. How can this be achieved?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an Amazon EFS file system and mount it from each EC2 instance.",
        "Create an Amazon S3 bucket and permit access from all the EC2 instances in the VPC.",
        "Create a file system on an Amazon EBS Provisioned IOPS SSD (101) volume. Attach the volume to all the EC2 instances.",
        "Create file systems on Amazon EBS volumes attached to each EC2 instance. Synchronize the Amazon EBS volumes across the different EC2 instances."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Amazon EFS file system and mount it from each EC2 instance."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "97",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect observes that a nightly batch processing job is automatically scaled up for 1 hour before the desired Amazon EC2 capacity is reached. The peak capacity is the same every night and the batch jobs always start at 1 AM. The solutions architect needs to find a cost-effective solution that will allow for the desired EC2 capacity to be reached quickly and allow the Auto Scaling group to scale down after the batch jobs are complete. What should the solutions architect do to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Increase the minimum capacity for the Auto Scaling group.",
        "Increase the maximum capacity for the Auto Scaling group.",
        "Configure scheduled scaling to scale up to the desired compute level.",
        "Change the scaling policy to add more EC2 instances during each scaling operation."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure scheduled scaling to scale up to the desired compute level."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "98",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A Solutions Architect must design a web application that will be hosted on AWS, allowing users to purchase access to premium, shared content that is stored in an S3 bucket. Upon payment, content will be available for download for 14 days before the user is denied access. Which of the following would be the LEAST complicated implementation?",
      "answers": [
        "Use an Amazon CloudFront distribution with an origin access identity (OAI). Configure the distribution with an Amazon S3 origin to provide access to the file through signed URLs. Design a Lambda function to remove data that is older than 14 days.",
        "Use an S3 bucket and provide direct access to the tile Design the application to track purchases in a DynamoDH table. Configure a Lambda function to remove data that is older than 14 days based on a query to Amazon DynamoDB.",
        "Use an Amazon CloudFront distribution with an OAI. Configure the distribution with an Amazon S3 origin to provide access to the file through signed URLs. Design the application to sot an expiration of 14 days for the URL.",
        "Use an Amazon CloudFront distribution with an OAI. Configure the distribution with an Amazon S3 origin to provide access to the file through signed URLs. Design the application to set an expiration of 60 minutes for the URL and recreate the URL as necessary."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use an Amazon CloudFront distribution with an OAI. Configure the distribution with an Amazon S3 origin to provide access to the file through signed URLs. Design the application to sot an expiration of 14 days for the URL."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "99",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a mission-critical web application. It will consist of Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer and a relational database. The database should be highly available and fault tolerant. Which database implementations will meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Redshift",
        "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "Amazon RDS for MySQL",
        "MySQL-compatible Amazon Aurora Multi-AZ",
        "Amazon RDS for SQL Server Standard Edition Multi-AZ"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["MySQL-compatible Amazon Aurora Multi-AZ",
        "Amazon RDS for SQL Server Standard Edition Multi-AZ"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "100",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys web application is running on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer. The company recently changed its policy, which now requires the application to be accessed from one specific country only. Which configuration will meet this requirement? ",
      "answers": [
        "Configure the security group for the EC2 instances.",
        "Configure the security group on the Application Load Balancer.",
        "Configure AWS WAF on the Application Load Balancer in a VPC.",
        "Configure the network ACL for the subnet that contains the EC2 instances."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure AWS WAF on the Application Load Balancer in a VPC."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "101",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solution architect has created two IAM policies: Policy1 and Policy2. Both policies are attached to an IAM group. Policy 1: Allow iam:Get*, iam:List*, kms:List*, ec2:*, ds:*, logs:Get*, logs:Describe* on Resource: *; Policy 2: Deny ds:Delete* on Resource *. A cloud engineer is added as an IAM user to the IAM group. Which action will the cloud engineer be able to perform?",
      "answers": [
        "Deleting IAM users",
        "Deleting directories",
        "Deleting Amazon EC2 instances",
        "Deleting logs from Amazon CloudWatch Logs"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deleting Amazon EC2 instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "102",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has an Amazon EC2 instance running on a private subnet that needs to access a public websites to download patches and updates. The company does not want external websites to see the EC2 instance IP address or initiate connection to it. How can a solution architect achieve this objective?",
      "answers": [
        "Create a site-to-site VPN connection between the private subnet and the network in which the public site is deployed.",
        "Create a NAT gateway in a public subnet. Route outbound traffic from the private subnet through the NAI gateway.",
        "Create a network ACL for the private subnet where the EC2 instance deployed only allows access from the IP address range of the public website.",
        "Create a security group that only allows connections from the IP address range of the public website. Attach the security group to the EC2 instance."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a NAT gateway in a public subnet. Route outbound traffic from the private subnet through the NAI gateway."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "103",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company must migrate 20 TB of data from a data center to the AWS Cloud within 30 days. The company's network bandwidth is limited to 15 Mbps and cannot exceed 70% utilization. What should a solutions architect do to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Use AWS Snowball.",
        "Use AWS DataSync.",
        "Use a secure VPN connection.",
        "Use Amazon S3 Transfer Acceleration."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use AWS Snowball."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "104",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a website running on Amazon EC2 instances across two Availability Zones. The company is expecting spikes in traffic on specific holidays, and wants to provide a consistent user experience. How can a solutions architect meet this requirement? ",
      "answers": [
        "Use step scaling.",
        "Use simple scaling.",
        "Use lifecycle hooks.",
        "Use scheduled scaling."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use scheduled scaling."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "105",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An ecommerce company is running a multi-tier application on AWS. The front-end and backend tiers both run on Amazon EC2, and the database runs on Amazon RDS for MySQL. The backend tier communicates with the RDS instance. There are frequent calls to return identical datasets from the database that are causing performance slowdowns. Which action should be taken to improve the performance of the backend?",
      "answers": [
        "Implement Amazon SNS to store the database calls.",
        "Implement Amazon ElastiCache to cache the large datasets.",
        "Implement an RDS for MySQL read replica to cache database calls.",
        "Implement Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose to stream the calls to the database."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Implement Amazon ElastiCache to cache the large datasets."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "106",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has an on-premises data center that is running out of storage capacity. The company wants to migrate its storage infrastructure to AWS while minimizing bandwidth costs. The solution must allow for immediate retrieval of data at no additional cost. How can these requirements be met?",
      "answers": [
        "Deploy Amazon S3 Glacier Vault and enable expedited retrieval. Enable provisioned retrieval capacity for the workload.",
        "Deploy AWS Storage Gateway using cached volumes. Use Storage Gateway to store data in Amazon S3 while retaining copies of frequently accessed data subsets locally.",
        "Deploy AWS Storage Gateway using stored volumes to store data locally. Use Storage Gateway to asynchronously back up point-in-time snapshots of the data to Amazon S3.",
        "Deploy AWS Direct Connect to connect with the on-premises data center. Configure AWS Storage Gateway to store data locally. Use Storage Gateway to asynchronously back up point-in-time snapshots of the data to Amazon S3."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy AWS Storage Gateway using cached volumes. Use Storage Gateway to store data in Amazon S3 while retaining copies of frequently accessed data subsets locally."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "107",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is processing data on a daily basis. The results of the operations are stored in an Amazon S3 bucket, analyzed daily for one week, and then must remain immediately accessible for occasional analysis. What is the MOST cost-effective storage solution alternative to the current configuration?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure a lifecycle policy to delete the objects after 30 days.",
        "Configure a lifecycle policy to transition the objects to Amazon S3 Glacier after 30 days.",
        "Configure a lifecycle policy to transition the objects to Amazon S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA) after 30 days.",
        "Configure a lifecycle policy to transition the objects to Amazon S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA) after 30 days."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure a lifecycle policy to transition the objects to Amazon S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA) after 30 days."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "108",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company delivers files in Amazon S3 to certain users who do not have AWS credentials. These users must be given access for a limited lime. What should a solutions architect do to securely meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Enable public access on an Amazon S3 bucket.",
        "Generate a presigned URL to share with the users.",
        "Encrypt files using AWS KMS and provide keys to the users.",
        "Create and assign IAM roles that will grant GetObject permissions to the users."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Generate a presigned URL to share with the users."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "109",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company wants to run a hybrid workload for data processing. The data needs to be accessed by on-premises applications for local data processing using an NFS protocol, and must also be accessible from the AWS Cloud for further analytics and batch processing. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Use an AWS Storage Gateway file gateway to provide file storage to AWS, then perform analytics on this data in the AWS Cloud.",
        "Use an AWS storage Gateway tape gateway to copy the backup of the local data to AWS, then perform analytics on this data in the AWS cloud.",
        "Use an AWS Storage Gateway volume gateway in a stored volume configuration to regularly take snapshots of the local data, then copy the data to AWS.",
        "Use an AWS Storage Gateway volume gateway in a cached volume configuration to back up all the local storage in the AWS cloud, then perform analytics on this data in the cloud."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use an AWS Storage Gateway file gateway to provide file storage to AWS, then perform analytics on this data in the AWS Cloud."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "110",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company plans to store sensitive user data on Amazon S3. Internal security compliance requirement mandate encryption of data before sending it to Amazon S3. What should a solution architect recommend to satisfy these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Server-side encryption with customer-provided encryption keys",
        "Client-side encryption with Amazon S3 managed encryption keys",
        "Server-side encryption with keys stored in AWS key Management Service (AWS KMS)",
        "Client-side encryption with a master key stored in AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Client-side encryption with a master key stored in AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "111",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A solutions architect is moving the static content from a public website hosted on Amazon EC2 instances to an Amazon S3 bucket. An Amazon CloudFront distribution will be used to deliver the static assets. The security group used by the EC2 instances restricts access to a limited set of IP ranges. Access to the static content should be similarly restricted. Which combination of steps will meet these requirements? (Choose two.) ",
      "answers": [
        "Create an origin access identity (OAI) and associate it with the distribution. Change the permissions in the bucket policy so that only the OAI can read the objects.",
        "Create an AWS WAF web ACL that includes the same IP restrictions that exist in the EC2 security group. Associate this new web ACL with the CloudFront distribution.",
        "Create a new security group that includes the same IP restrictions that exist in the current EC2 security group. Associate this new security group with the CloudFront distribution.",
        "Create a new security group that includes the same IP restrictions that exist in the current EC2 security group. Associate this new security group with the S3 bucket hosting the static content.",
        "Create a new IAM role and associate the role with the distribution. Change the permissions either on the S3 bucket or on the files within the S3 bucket so that only the newly created IAM role has read and download permissions."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an origin access identity (OAI) and associate it with the distribution. Change the permissions in the bucket policy so that only the OAI can read the objects.",
        "Create an AWS WAF web ACL that includes the same IP restrictions that exist in the EC2 security group. Associate this new web ACL with the CloudFront distribution."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "112",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is investigating potential solutions that would collect, process, and store users' service usage data. The business objective is to create an analytics capability that will enable the company to gather operational insights quickly using standard SQL queries. The solution should be highly available and ensure Atomicity, Consistency, Isolation, and Durability (ACID) compliance in the data tier. Which solution should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon DynamoDB transactions",
        "Create an Amazon Neptune database in a Multi AZ design",
        "Use a fully managed Amazon RDS for MySQL database in a Multi-AZ design",
        "Deploy PostgreSQL on an Amazon EC2 instance that uses Amazon EBS Throughput Optimized HDD storage."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use a fully managed Amazon RDS for MySQL database in a Multi-AZ design"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "113",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company recently launched its website to serve content to its global user base. The company wants to store and accelerate the delivery of static content to its users by leveraging Amazon CloudFront with an Amazon EC2 instance attached as its origin. How should a solutions architect optimize high availability for the application?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Lambda@Edge for CloudFront.",
        "Use Amazon S3 Transfer Acceleration for CloudFront.",
        "Configure another EC2 instance in a different Availability Zone as part of the origin group.",
        "Configure another EC2 instance as part of the origin server cluster in the same Availability Zone."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure another EC2 instance in a different Availability Zone as part of the origin group."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "114",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An application running on an Amazon EC2 instance in VPC-A needs to access files in another EC2 instance in VPC-B. Both are in separate. AWS accounts. The network administrator needs to design a solution to enable secure access to EC2 instance in VPC-B from VPC-A. The connectivity should not have a single point of failure or bandwidth concerns. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Set up a VPC peering connection between VPC-A and VPC-B.",
        "Set up VPC gateway endpoints for the EC2 instance running in VPC-B.",
        "Attach a virtual private gateway to VPC-B and enable routing from VPC-A.",
        "Create a private virtual interface (VIF) for the EC2 instance running in VPC-B and add appropriate routes from VPC-B."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Set up a VPC peering connection between VPC-A and VPC-B."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "115",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company currently stores symmetric encryption keys in a hardware security module (HSM). A solution architect must design a solution to migrate key management to AWS. The solution should allow for key rotation and support the use of customer provided keys. Where should the key material be stored to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon S3",
        "AWS Secrets Manager",
        "AWS Systems Manager Parameter store",
        "AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "116",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A recent analysis of a company's IT expenses highlights the need to reduce backup costs. The company's chief information officer wants to simplify the on- premises backup infrastructure and reduce costs by eliminating the use of physical backup tapes. The company must preserve the existing investment in the on- premises backup applications and workflows. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Set up AWS Storage Gateway to connect with the backup applications using the NFS interface.",
        "Set up an Amazon EFS file system that connects with the backup applications using the NFS interface.",
        "Set up an Amazon EFS file system that connects with the backup applications using the iSCSI interface.",
        "Set up AWS Storage Gateway to connect with the backup applications using the iSCSI-virtual tape library (VTL) interface."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Set up AWS Storage Gateway to connect with the backup applications using the iSCSI-virtual tape library (VTL) interface."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "117",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company hosts an application on an Amazon EC2 instance that requires a maximum of 200 GB storage space. The application is used infrequently, with peaks during mornings and evenings. Disk I/O varies, but peaks at 3,000 IOPS. The chief financial officer of the company is concerned about costs and has asked a solutions architect to recommend the most cost-effective storage option that does not sacrifice performance. Which solution should the solutions architect recommend? ",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon EBS Cold HDD (sc1)",
        "Amazon EBS General Purpose SSD (gp2)",
        "Amazon EBS Provisioned IOPS SSD (io1)",
        "Amazon EBS Throughput Optimized HDD (st1)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon EBS General Purpose SSD (gp2)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "118",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company's application hosted on Amazon EC2 instances needs to access an Amazon S3 bucket. Due to data sensitivity, traffic cannot traverse the internet How should a solutions architect configure access?",
      "answers": [
        "Create a private hosted zone using Amazon Route 53.",
        "Configure a VPC gateway endpoint for Amazon S3 in the VPC.",
        "Configure AWS PrivateLink between the EC2 instance and the S3 bucket.",
        "Set up a site-to-site VPN connection between the VPC and the S3 bucket."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure a VPC gateway endpoint for Amazon S3 in the VPC."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "119",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has two applications it wants to migrate to AWS. Both applications process a large set of files by accessing the same files at the same time. Both applications need to read the files with low latency. Which architecture should a solutions architect recommend for this situation?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure two AWS Lambda functions to run the applications. Create an Amazon EC2 instance with an instance store volume to store the data.",
        "Configure two AWS Lambda functions to run the applications. Create an Amazon EC2 instance with an Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume to store the data.",
        "Configure one memory optimized Amazon EC2 instance to run both applications simultaneously. Create an Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume with Provisioned IOPS to store the data.",
        "Configure two Amazon EC2 instances to run both applications. Configure Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) with General Purpose performance mode and Bursting Throughput mode to store the data."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure two Amazon EC2 instances to run both applications. Configure Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) with General Purpose performance mode and Bursting Throughput mode to store the data."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "120",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An ecommerce company has noticed performance degradation of its Amazon RDS based web application. The performance degradation is attributed to an increase in the number of read-only SQL queries triggered by business analysts. A solution architect needs to solve the problem with minimal changes to the existing web application. What should the solution architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Export the data to Amazon DynamoDB and have the business analysts run their queries.",
        "Load the data into Amazon ElastiCache and have the business analysts run their queries.",
        "Create a read replica of the primary database and have the business analysts run their queries.",
        "Copy the data into an Amazon Redshift cluster and have the business analysts run their queries."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a read replica of the primary database and have the business analysts run their queries."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "121",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is running a highly sensitive application on Amazon EC2 backed by an Amazon RDS database. Compliance regulations mandate that all personally identifiable information (PII) be encrypted at rest. Which solution should a solutions architect recommend to meet this requirement with the LEAST amount of changes to the infrastructure?",
      "answers": [
        "Deploy AWS Certificate Manager to generate certificates. Use the certificates to encrypt the database volume.",
        "Deploy AWS CloudHSM, generate encryption keys, and use the customer master key (CMK) to encrypt database volumes.",
        "Configure SSL encryption using AWS Key Management Service customer master keys (AWS KMS CMKs) to encrypt database volumes.",
        "Configure Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) encryption and Amazon RDS encryption with AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) keys to encrypt instance and database volumes."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) encryption and Amazon RDS encryption with AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) keys to encrypt instance and database volumes."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "122",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company running an on-premises application is migrating the application to AWS to increase its elasticity and availability. The current architecture uses a Microsoft SQL Server database with heavy read activity. The company wants to explore alternate database options and migrate database engines, if needed. Every 4 hours, the development team does a full copy of the production database to populate a test database. During this period, users experience latency. What should a solution architect recommend as replacement database? ",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon Aurora with Multi-AZ Aurora Replicas and restore from mysqldump for the test database.",
        "Use Amazon Aurora with Multi-AZ Aurora Replicas and restore snapshots from Amazon RDS for the test database.",
        "Use Amazon RDS for MySQL with a Multi-AZ deployment and read replicas, and use the standby instance for the test database.",
        "Use Amazon RDS for SQL Server with a Multi-AZ deployment and read replicas, and restore snapshots from RDS for the test database."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon RDS for SQL Server with a Multi-AZ deployment and read replicas, and restore snapshots from RDS for the test database."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "123",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has enabled AWS CloudTrail logs to deliver log files to an Amazon S3 bucket for each of its developer accounts. The company has created a central AWS account for streamlining management and audit reviews. An internal auditor needs to access the CloudTrail logs, yet access needs to be restricted for all developer account users. The solution must be secure and optimized. How should a solutions architect meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure an AWS Lambda function in each developer account to copy the log files to the central account. Create an IAM role in the central account for the auditor. Attach an IAM policy providing read-only permissions to the bucket.",
        "Configure CloudTrail from each developer account to deliver the log files to an S3 bucket in the central account. Create an IAM user in the central account for the auditor. Attach an IAM policy providing full permissions to the bucket.",
        "Configure CloudTrail from each developer account to deliver the log files to an S3 bucket in the central account. Create an IAM role in the central account for the auditor. Attach an IAM policy providing read-only permissions to the bucket.",
        "Configure an AWS Lambda function in the central account to copy the log files from the S3 bucket in each developer account. Create an IAM user in the central account for the auditor. Attach an IAM policy providing full permissions to the bucket."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure CloudTrail from each developer account to deliver the log files to an S3 bucket in the central account. Create an IAM role in the central account for the auditor. Attach an IAM policy providing read-only permissions to the bucket."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "124",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A company has several business systems that require access to data stored in a file share. the business systems will access the file share using the Server Message Block (SMB) protocol. The file share solution should be accessible from both of the company's legacy on-premises environment and with AWS. Which services mod the business requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon EBS",
        "Amazon EFS",
        "Amazon FSx for Windows",
        "Amazon S3",
        "AWS Storage Gateway file gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon FSx for Windows",
        "AWS Storage Gateway file gateway"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "125",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is using Amazon EC2 to run its big data analytics workloads. These variable workloads run each night, and it is critical they finish by the start of business the following day. A solutions architect has been tasked with designing the MOST cost-effective solution. Which solution will accomplish this? ",
      "answers": [
        "Spot Fleet",
        "Spot Instances",
        "Reserved Instances",
        "On-Demand Instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Spot Fleet"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "126",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a Microsoft Windows-based application that must be migrated to AWS. This application requires the use of a shared Windows file system attached to multiple Amazon EC2 Windows instances. What should a solution architect do to accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure a volume using Amazon EFS. Mount the EPS volume to each Windows Instance.",
        "Configure AWS Storage Gateway in Volume Gateway mode. Mount the volume to each Windows Instance.",
        "Configure Amazon FSx for Windows File Server. Mount the Amazon FSx volume to each Windows Instance.",
        "Configure an Amazon EBS volume with the required size. Attach each EC2 instance to the volume. Mount the file system within the volume to each Windows instance."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure Amazon FSx for Windows File Server. Mount the Amazon FSx volume to each Windows Instance."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "127",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has created an isolated backup of its environment in another Region. The application is running in warm standby mode and is fronted by an Application Load Balancer (ALB). The current failover process is manual and requires updating a DNS alias record to point to the secondary ALB in another Region. What should a solution architect do to automate the failover process?",
      "answers": [
        "Enable an ALB health check",
        "Enable an Amazon Route 53 health check.",
        "Crate an CNAME record on Amazon Route 53 pointing to the ALB endpoint.",
        "Create conditional forwarding rules on Amazon Route 53 pointing to an internal BIND DNS server."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Enable an Amazon Route 53 health check."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "128",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a mobile chat application with a data store based in Amazon DynamoDB. Users would like new messages to be read with as little latency as possible. A solutions architect needs to design an optimal solution that requires minimal application changes. Which method should the solutions architect select?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure Amazon DynamoDB Accelerator (DAX) for the new messages table. Update the code to use the DAX endpoint.",
        "Add DynamoDB read replicas to handle the increased read load. Update the application to point to the read endpoint for the read replicas.",
        "Double the number of read capacity units for the new messages table in DynamoDB. Continue to use the existing DynamoDB endpoint.",
        "Add an Amazon ElastiCache for Redis cache to the application stack. Update the application to point to the Redis cache endpoint instead of DynamoDB."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure Amazon DynamoDB Accelerator (DAX) for the new messages table. Update the code to use the DAX endpoint."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "129",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is creating an architecture for a mobile app that requires minimal latency for its users. The company's architecture consists of Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer running in an Auto Scaling group. The EC2 instances connect to Amazon RDS. Application beta testing showed there was a slowdown when reading the data. However the metrics indicate that the EC2 instances do not cross any CPU utilization thresholds. How can this issue be addressed?",
      "answers": [
        "Reduce the threshold for CPU utilization in the Auto Scaling group.",
        "Replace the Application Load Balancer with a Network Load Balancer.",
        "Add read replicas for the RDS instances and direct read traffic to the replica.",
        "Add Multi-AZ support to the RDS instances and direct read traffic to the new EC2 instance."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Add read replicas for the RDS instances and direct read traffic to the replica."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "130",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has implemented one of its microservices on AWS Lambda that accesses an Amazon DynamoDB table named Books. A solutions architect is designing an IAM policy to be attached to the Lambda function's IAM role, giving it access to put, update, and delete items in the Books table. The IAM policy must prevent function from performing any other actions on the Books table or any other. Which IAM policy would fulfill these needs and provide the LEAST privileged access?",
      "answers": [
        "policy: Sid: PutUpdateDeleteOnBooks, Effect: Allow, Action: dynamodb: PutItem, dynamodb: UpdateItem, dynamodb: DeleteItem, Resource: arn:...:table/Books",
        "policy: Sid: PutUpdateDeleteOnBooks, Effect: Allow, Action: dynamodb: PutItem, dynamodb: UpdateItem, dynamodb: DeleteItem, Resource: arn:...:table/*",
        "policy: Sid: PutUpdateDeleteOnBooks, Effect: Allow, Action: dynamodb: *, Resource: arn:...:table/Books",
        "policy: Sid: PutUpdateDeleteOnBooks, Effect: Allow, Action: dynamodb: *, Resource: arn:...:table/Books AND policy: Sid: PutUpdateDeleteOnBooks, Effect: Deny, Action: dynamodb: *, Resource: arn:...:table/Books"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["policy: Sid: PutUpdateDeleteOnBooks, Effect: Allow, Action: dynamodb: PutItem, dynamodb: UpdateItem, dynamodb: DeleteItem, Resource: arn:...:table/Books"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "131",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company hosts its website on Amazon S3. The website serves petabytes of outbound traffic monthly, which accounts for most of the company's AWS costs. What should a solutions architect do to reduce costs?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure Amazon CloudFront with the existing website as the origin.",
        "Move the website to Amazon EC2 with Amazon EBS volumes for storage.",
        "Use AWS Global Accelerator and specify the existing website as the endpoint.",
        "Rearchitect the website to run on a combination of Amazon API Gateway and AWS Lambda."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure Amazon CloudFront with the existing website as the origin."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "132",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company runs a website on Amazon EC2 instances behind an ELB Application Load Balancer. Amazon Route 53 is used for the DNS. The company wants to set up a backup website with a message including a phone number and email address that users can reach if the primary website is down. How should the company deploy this solution?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon S3 website hosting for the backup website and Route 53 failover routing policy.",
        "Use Amazon S3 website hosting for the backup website and Route 53 latency routing policy.",
        "Deploy the application in another AWS Region and use ELB health checks for failover routing.",
        "Deploy the application in another AWS Region and use server-side redirection on the primary website."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon S3 website hosting for the backup website and Route 53 failover routing policy."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "133",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A media company is evaluating the possibility of moving its systems to the AWS Cloud. The company needs at least 10 TB of storage with the maximum possible I/O performance for video processing. 300 TB of very durable storage for storing media content, and 900 TB of storage to meet requirements for archival media that is not in use anymore. Which set of services should a solutions architect recommend to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon EBS for maximum performance, Amazon S3 for durable data storage, and Amazon S3 Glacier for archival storage.",
        "Amazon EBS for maximum performance. Amazon EFS for durable data storage, and Amazon S3 Glacier for archival storage",
        "Amazon EC2 instance store for maximum performance, Amazon EFS for durable data storage, and Amazon S3 for archival storage",
        "Amazon EC2 instance store for maximum performance, Amazon S3 for durable data storage, and Amazon S3 Glacier for archival storage"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon EBS for maximum performance, Amazon S3 for durable data storage, and Amazon S3 Glacier for archival storage."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "134",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company uses Amazon S3 as its object storage solution. The company has thousands of S3 buckets it uses to store data. Some of the S3 bucket have data that is accessed less frequently than others. A solutions architect found that lifecycle policies are not consistently implemented or are implemented partially? resulting in data being stored in high-cost storage. Which solution will lower costs without compromising the availability of objects? ",
      "answers": [
        "Use S3 ACLs.",
        "Use Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS) automated snapshots.",
        "Use S3 Intelligent-Tiering storage.",
        "Use S3 One Zone-infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA)."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use S3 Intelligent-Tiering storage."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "135",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "An application is running on Amazon EC2 instances. Sensitive information required for the application is stored in an Amazon S3 bucket. The bucket needs to be protected from internet access while only allowing services within the VPC access to the bucket. Which combination of actions should solutions archived take to accomplish this? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Create a VPC endpoint for Amazon S3.",
        "Enable server access logging on the bucket.",
        "Apply a bucket policy to restrict access to the S3 endpoint.",
        "Add an S3 ACL to the bucket that has sensitive information.",
        "Restrict users using the IAM policy to use the specific bucket."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a VPC endpoint for Amazon S3.",
        "Apply a bucket policy to restrict access to the S3 endpoint."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "136",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A web application runs on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer. The application allows users to create custom reports of historical weather data. Generating a report can take up to 5 minutes. These long-running requests use many of the available incoming connections, making the system unresponsive to other users. How can a solutions architect make the system more responsive?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon SQS with AWS Lambda to generate reports.",
        "Increase the idle timeout on the Application Load Balancer to 5 minutes.",
        "Update the client-side application code to increase its request timeout to 5 minutes.",
        "Publish the reports to Amazon S3 and use Amazon CloudFront for downloading to the user."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon SQS with AWS Lambda to generate reports."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "137",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect must create a highly available bastion host architecture. The solution needs to be resilient within a single AWS Region and should require only minimal effort to maintain. What should the solutions architect do to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Create a Network Load Balancer backed by an Auto Scaling group with a UDP listener.",
        "Create a Network Load Balancer backed by a Spot Fleet with instances in a group with instances in a partition placement group.",
        "Create a Network Load Balancer backed by the existing serves in different Availability Zones as the target.",
        "Create a Network Load Balancer backed by an Auto Scaling with instances in multiple Availability zones as the target"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a Network Load Balancer backed by an Auto Scaling with instances in multiple Availability zones as the target"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "138",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A three-tier web application processes orders from customers. The web tier consists of Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer, a middle tier of three EC2 instances decoupled from the web tier using Amazon SQS. and an Amazon DynamoDB backend. At peak times, customers who submit orders using the site have to wait much longer than normal to receive confirmations due to lengthy processing times. A solutions architect needs to reduce these processing times. Which action will be MOST effective in accomplishing this?",
      "answers": [
        "Replace the SQS queue with Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose.",
        "Use Amazon ElastiCache for Redis in front of the DynamoDB backend tier.",
        "Add an Amazon CloudFront distribution to cache the responses for the web tier.",
        "Use Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling to scale out the middle tier instances based on the SOS queue depth."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling to scale out the middle tier instances based on the SOS queue depth."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "139",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company relies on an application that needs at least 4 Amazon EC2 instances during regular traffic and must scale up to 12 EC2 instances during peak loads. The application is critical to the business and must be highly available. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Deploy the EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group Set the minimum to 4 and the maximum to M, with 2 in Availability Zone A and 2 in Availability Zone B.",
        "Deploy the EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group Set the minimum to 4 and the maximum to 12, with all 4 in Availability Zone A.",
        "Deploy the EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group Set the minimum to 8 and the maximum to 12, with 4 in Availability Zone A and 4 in Availability Zone B.",
        "Deploy the EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group Set the minimum to 8 and the maximum to 12 with all 8 in Availability Zone A."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy the EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group Set the minimum to 8 and the maximum to 12, with 4 in Availability Zone A and 4 in Availability Zone B."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "140",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect must design a solution for a persistent database that is being migrated from on-premises to AWS. The database requires 64,000 IOPS according to the database administrator. If possible, the database administrator wants to use a single Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume to host the database instance. Which solution effectively meets the database administrator's criteria? ",
      "answers": [
        "Use an instance from the I3 I/O optimized family and leverage local ephemeral storage to achieve the IOPS requirement.",
        "Create an Nitro-based Amazon EC2 instance with an Amazon EBS Provisioned IOPS SSD (io1) volume attached. Configure the volume to have 64,000 IOPS.",
        "Create and map an Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) volume to the database instance and use the volume to achieve the required IOPS for the database.",
        "Provision two volumes and assign 32,000 IOPS to each. Create a logical volume at the operating system level that aggregates both volumes to achieve the IOPS requirements."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Nitro-based Amazon EC2 instance with an Amazon EBS Provisioned IOPS SSD (io1) volume attached. Configure the volume to have 64,000 IOPS."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "141",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing an architecture for a new application that requires low network latency and high network throughput between Amazon EC2 instances. Which component should be included in the architectural design?",
      "answers": [
        "An Auto Scaling group with Spot Instance types.",
        "A placement group using a cluster placement strategy.",
        "A placement group using a partition placement strategy.",
        "An Auto Scaling group with On-Demand instance types."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["A placement group using a cluster placement strategy."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "142",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has global users accessing an application deployed in different AWS Regions, exposing public static IP addresses. The users are experiencing poor performance when accessing the application over the internet. What should a solutions architect recommend to reduce internet latency? ",
      "answers": [
        "Set up AWS Global Accelerator and add endpoints.",
        "Set up AWS Direct Connect locations in multiple Regions.",
        "Set up an Amazon CloudFront distribution to access an application.",
        "Set up an Amazon Route 53 geoproximity routing policy to route traffic."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Set up AWS Global Accelerator and add endpoints."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "143",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate a workload to AWS. The chief information security officer requires that all data be encrypted at rest when stored in the cloud. The company wants complete control of encryption key lifecycle management. The company must be able to immediately remove the key material and audit key usage independently of AWS CloudTrail. The chosen services should integrate with other storage services that will be used on AWS. Which services satisfies these security requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "AWS CloudHSM with the CloudHSM client",
        "AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) with AWS CloudHSM",
        "AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) with an external key material origin",
        "AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) with AWS managed customer master keys (CMKs)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) with AWS CloudHSM"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "144",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company recently deployed a two-tier application in two Availability Zones in the us-east-1 Region. The databases are deployed in a private subnet while the web servers are deployed in a public subnet. An internet gateway is attached to the VPC. The application and database run on Amazon EC2 instances. The database servers are unable to access patches on the internet. A solutions architect needs to design a solution that maintains database security with the least operational overhead. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Deploy a NAT gateway inside the public subnet for each Availability Zone and associate it with an Elastic IP address. Update the routing table of the private subnet to use it as the default route.",
        "Deploy a NAT gateway inside the private subnet for each Availability Zone and associate it with an Elastic IP address. Update the routing table of the private subnet to use it as the default route.",
        "Deploy two NAT instances inside the public subnet for each Availability Zone and associate them with Elastic IP addresses. Update the routing table of the private subnet to use it as the default route.",
        "Deploy two NAT instances inside the private subnet for each Availability Zone and associate them with Elastic IP addresses. Update the routing table of the private subnet to use it as the default route."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy a NAT gateway inside the public subnet for each Availability Zone and associate it with an Elastic IP address. Update the routing table of the private subnet to use it as the default route."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "145",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has an application with a REST-based Interface that allows data to be received in near-real time from a third-party vendor Once received, the application processes and stores the data for further analysis. The application Is running on Amazon EC2 instances. The third-party vendor has received many 503 Service Unavailable Errors when sending data to the application. When the data volume spikes, the compute capacity reaches its maximum limit and the application is unable to process all requests. Which design should a solutions architect recommend to provide a more scalable solution?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon Kinesis Data Streams to ingest the data. Process the data using AWS Lambda functions.",
        "Use Amazon API Gateway on top of the existing application. Create a usage plan with a quota limit for the third-party vendor.",
        "Use Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) to ingest the data. Put the EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group behind an Application Load Balancer.",
        "Repackage the application as a container. Deploy the application using Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) using the EC2 launch type with an Auto Scaling group."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon Kinesis Data Streams to ingest the data. Process the data using AWS Lambda functions."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "146",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A solutions architect needs to design a low-latency solution for a static single-page application accessed by users utilizing a custom domain name. The solution must be serverless, encrypted in transit, and cost-effective. Which combination of AWS services and features should the solutions architect use? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon S3",
        "Amazon EC2",
        "AWS Fargate",
        "Amazon CloudFront",
        "Elastic Load Balancer"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon S3",
        "Amazon CloudFront"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "147",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is migrating to the AWS Cloud. A file server is the first workload to migrate. Users must be able to access the file share using the Server Message Block (SMB) protocol. Which AWS managed service meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon EBS",
        "Amazon EC2",
        "Amazon FSx",
        "Amazon S3"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon FSx"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "148",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a customer-facing application. The application is expected to have a variable amount of reads and writes depending on the time of year and clearly defined access patterns throughout the year. Management requires that database auditing and scaling be managed in the AWS Cloud. The Recovery Point Objective (RPO) must be less than 5 hours. Which solutions can accomplish this? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon DynamoDB with auto scaling. Use on-demand backups and AWS CloudTrail.",
        "Use Amazon DynamoDB with auto scaling. Use on-demand backups and Amazon DynamoDB Streams.",
        "Use Amazon Redshift Configure concurrency scaling. Enable audit logging. Perform database snapshots every 4 hours.",
        "Use Amazon RDS with Provisioned IOPS. Enable the database auditing parameter. Perform database snapshots every 5 hours.",
        "Use Amazon RDS with auto scaling. Enable the database auditing parameter. Configure the backup retention period to at least 1 day."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon DynamoDB with auto scaling. Use on-demand backups and AWS CloudTrail.",
        "Use Amazon RDS with auto scaling. Enable the database auditing parameter. Configure the backup retention period to at least 1 day."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "149",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has migrated an on-premises Oracle database to an Amazon RDS for Oracle Multi-AZ DB instance in the us-east-l Region. A solutions architect is designing a disaster recovery strategy to have the database provisioned in the us-west-2 Region in case the database becomes unavailable in the us-east-1 Region. The design must ensure the database is provisioned in the us-west-2 Region in a maximum of 2 hours, with a data loss window of no more than 3 hours. How can these requirements be met?",
      "answers": [
        "Edit the DB instance and create a read replica in us-west-2. Promote the read replica to master in us-west-2 in case the disaster recovery environment needs to be activated.",
        "Select the multi-Region option to provision a standby instance in us-west-2. The standby instance will be automatically promoted to master in us-west-2 in case the disaster recovery environment needs to be created.",
        "Take automated snapshots of the database instance and copy them to us-west-2 every 3 hours. Restore the latest snapshot to provision another database instance in us-west-2 in case the disaster recovery environment needs to be activated.",
        "Create a multimaster read/write instances across multiple AWS Regions Select VPCs in us-east-1 and us-west-2 to make that deployment. Keep the master read/write instance in us-west-2 available to avoid having to activate a disaster recovery environment."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Edit the DB instance and create a read replica in us-west-2. Promote the read replica to master in us-west-2 in case the disaster recovery environment needs to be activated."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "150",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A monolithic application was recently migrated to AWS and is now running on a single Amazon EC2 instance. Due to application limitations, it is not possible to use automatic scaling to scale out the application. The chief technology officer (CTO) wants an automated solution to restore the EC2 instance in the unlikely event the underlying hardware fails. What would allow for automatic recovery of the EC2 instance as quickly as possible?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure an Amazon CloudWatch alarm that triggers the recovery of the EC2 instance if it becomes impaired.",
        "Configure an Amazon CloudWatch alarm to trigger an SNS message that alerts the CTO when the EC2 instance is impaired.",
        "Configure AWS CloudTrail to monitor the health of the EC2 instance, and if it becomes impaired, triggered instance recovery.",
        "Configure an Amazon EventBridge event to trigger an AWS Lambda function once an hour that checks the health of the EC2 instance and triggers instance recovery if the EC2 instance is unhealthy."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure an Amazon CloudWatch alarm that triggers the recovery of the EC2 instance if it becomes impaired."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "151",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is working on optimizing a legacy document management application running on Microsoft Windows Server in an on-premises data center. The application stores a large number of files on a network file share. The chief information officer wants to reduce the on-premises data center footprint and minimize storage costs by moving on-premises storage to AWS. What should the solutions architect do to meet these requirements? ",
      "answers": [
        "Set up an AWS Storage Gateway file gateway.",
        "Set up Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
        "Set up AWS Storage Gateway as a volume gateway",
        "Set up an Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Set up an AWS Storage Gateway file gateway."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "152",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solution architect is designing a hybrid application using the AWS cloud. The network between the on-premises data center and AWS will use an AWS Direct Connect (DX) connection. The application connectivity between AWS and the on-premises data center must be highly resilient. Which DX configuration should be implemented to meet these requirements? ",
      "answers": [
        "Configure a DX connection with a VPN on top of it.",
        "Configure DX connections at multiple DX locations.",
        "Configure a DX connection using the most reliable DX partner.",
        "Configure multiple virtual interfaces on top of a DX connection."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure DX connections at multiple DX locations."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "153",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company runs an application on Amazon EC2 Instances. The application is deployed in private subnets in three Availability Zones of the us-east-1 Region. The instances must be able to connect to the internet to download files. The company wants a design that is highly available across the Region. Which solution should be implemented to ensure that there are no disruptions to Internet connectivity? ",
      "answers": [
        "Deploy a NAT Instance in a private subnet of each Availability Zone.",
        "Deploy a NAT gateway in a public subnet of each Availability Zone.",
        "Deploy a transit gateway in a private subnet of each Availability Zone.",
        "Deploy an internet gateway in a public subnet of each Availability Zone."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy a NAT gateway in a public subnet of each Availability Zone."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "154",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Application developers have noticed that a production application is very slow when business reporting users run large production reports against the Amazon RDS instance backing the application. The CPU and memory utilization metrics for the RDS instance do not exceed 60% while the reporting queries are running. The business reporting users must be able to generate reports without affecting the applications performance. Which action will accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Increase the size of the RDS instance",
        "Create a read replica and connect the application to it.",
        "Enable multiple Availability Zones on the RDS instance",
        "Create a read replication and connect the business reports to it."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a read replication and connect the business reports to it."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "155",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is running a two-tier ecommerce website using services. The current architect uses a publish-facing Elastic Load Balancer that sends traffic to Amazon EC2 instances in a private subnet. The static content is hosted on EC2 instances, and the dynamic content is retrieved from a MYSQL database. The application is running in the United States. The company recently started selling to users in Europe and Australia. A solution architect needs to design solution so their international users have an improved browsing experience. Which solution is MOST cost-effective?",
      "answers": [
        "Host the entire website on Amazon S3.",
        "Use Amazon CloudFront and Amazon S3 to host static images.",
        "Increase the number of public load balancers and EC2 instances.",
        "Deploy the two-tier website in AWS Regions in Europe and Australia."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon CloudFront and Amazon S3 to host static images."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "156",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys website provides users with downloadable historical performance reports. The website needs a solution that will scale to meet the companys website demands globally. The solution should be cost effective, limit the provisioning of infrastructure resources and provide the fastest possible response time. Which combination should a solutions architect recommend to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon CloudFront and Amazon S3",
        "AWS Lambda and Amazon DynamoDB",
        "Application Load Balancer with Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling",
        "Amazon Route 53 with internal Application Load Balances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon CloudFront and Amazon S3"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "157",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company wants to deploy a shared file system for its .NET application servers and Microsoft SQL Server database running on Amazon EC2 instance with Windows Server 2016. The solution must be able to be integrated in to the corporate Active Directory domain, be highly durable, be managed by AWS, and provided levels of throughput and IOPS. Which solution meets these requirements? ",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon FSx for Windows File Server",
        "Use Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
        "Use AWS Storage Gateway in file gateway mode.",
        "Deploy a Windows file server on two On Demand instances across two Availability Zones."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon FSx for Windows File Server"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "158",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company that develops web applications has launched hundreds of Application Load Balancers (ALBs) in multiple Regions. The company wants to create an allow list (or the IPs of all the load balancers on its firewall device. A solutions architect is looking for a one-time, highly available solution to address this request, which will also help reduce the number of IPs that need to be allowed by the firewall. What should the solutions architect recommend to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Create a AWS Lambda function to keep track of the IPs for all the ALBs in different Regions Keep refreshing this list.",
        "Set up a Network Load Balancer (NLB) with Elastic IPs. Register the private IPs of all the ALBs as targets to this NLB.",
        "Launch AWS Global Accelerator and create endpoints for all the Regions. Register all the ALBs in different Regions to the corresponding endpoints.",
        "Set up an Amazon EC2 instance, assign an Elastic IP to this EC2 instance, and configure the instance as a proxy to forward traffic to all the ALBs."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Launch AWS Global Accelerator and create endpoints for all the Regions. Register all the ALBs in different Regions to the corresponding endpoints."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "159",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company runs an application using Amazon ECS. The application creates resized versions of an original image and then makes Amazon S3 API calls to store the resized images in Amazon S3. How can a solutions architect ensure that the application has permission to access Amazon S3? ",
      "answers": [
        "Update the S3 role in AWS IAM to allow read/write access from Amazon ECS, and then relaunch the container.",
        "Create an IAM role with S3 permissions, and then specify that role as the taskRoleArn in the task definition.",
        "Create a security group that allows access from Amazon ECS to Amazon S3, and update the launch configuration used by the ECS cluster.",
        "Create an IAM user with S3 permissions, and then relaunch the Amazon EC2 instances for the ECS cluster while logged in as this account."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an IAM role with S3 permissions, and then specify that role as the taskRoleArn in the task definition."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "160",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A company is planning to migrate its virtual server-based workloads to AWS. The company has internet-facing load balancers backed by application servers. The application servers rely on patches from an internet-hosted repository Which services should a solutions architect recommend be hosted on the public subnet? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "NAT gateway",
        "Amazon RDS DB instances",
        "Application Load Balancers",
        "Amazon EC2 application servers",
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) volumes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["NAT gateway",
        "Application Load Balancers"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "161",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has established a new AWS account. The account is newly provisioned and no changed have been made to the default settings. The company is concerned about the security of the AWS account root user. What should be done to secure the root user?",
      "answers": [
        "Create IAM users for daily administrative tasks. Disable the root user.",
        "Create IAM users for daily administrative tasks. Enable multi-factor authentication on the root user.",
        "Generate an access key for the root user. Use the access key for daily administration tasks instead of the AWS Management Console.",
        "Provide the root user credentials to the most senior solution architect. Have the solution architect use the root user for daily administration tasks."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create IAM users for daily administrative tasks. Enable multi-factor authentication on the root user."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "162",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is using a tape backup solution to store its key application data offsite. The daily data volume is around 50 TB. The company needs to retain the backups for 7 years for regulatory purposes. The backups are rarely accessed and a weeks notice is typically given if a backup needs to be restored. The company is now considering a cloud-based option to reduce the storage costs and operational burden of managing tapes. The company also wants to make sure that the transition from tape backups to the cloud minimizes disruptions. Which storage solution is MOST cost-effective?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon Storage Gateway to back up to Amazon Glacier Deep Archive.",
        "Use AWS Snowball Edge to directly integrate the backups with Amazon S3 Glacier.",
        "Copy the backup data to Amazon S3 and create a lifecycle policy to move the data to Amazon S3 Glacier.",
        "Use Amazon Storage Gateway to back up to Amazon S3 and create a lifecycle policy to move the backup to Amazon S3 Glacier."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon Storage Gateway to back up to Amazon Glacier Deep Archive."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "163",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company requires a durable backup storage solution for its on-premises database servers while ensuring on-premises applications maintain access to these backups for quick recovery. The company will use AWS storage services as the destination for these backups. A solutions architect is designing a solution with minimal operational overhead. Which solution should the solutions architect implement? ",
      "answers": [
        "Deploy an AWS Storage Gateway file gateway on-premises and associate it with an Amazon S3 bucket.",
        "Back up the databases to an AWS Storage Gateway volume gateway and access it using the Amazon S3 API.",
        "Transfer the database backup files to an Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume attached to an Amazon EC2 instance.",
        "Back up the database directly to an AWS Snowball device and uss lifecycle rules to move the data to Amazon S3 Glacier Deep Archive."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy an AWS Storage Gateway file gateway on-premises and associate it with an Amazon S3 bucket."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "164",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company decides to migrate its three-tier web application from on-premises to the AWS Cloud. The new database must be capable of dynamically scaling storage capacity and performing table joins. Which AWS service meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Aurora",
        "Amazon RDS for SqlServer",
        "Amazon DynamoDB Streams",
        "Amazon DynamoDB on-demand"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Aurora"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "165",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company mandates that an Amazon S3 gateway endpoint must allow traffic to trusted buckets only. Which method should a solutions architect implement to meet this requirement?",
      "answers": [
        "Create a bucket policy for each of the companys trusted S3 buckets that allows traffic only from the companys trusted VPCs.",
        "Create a bucket policy for each of the companys trusted S3 buckets that allows traffic only from the companys S3 gateway endpoint IDs.",
        "Create an S3 endpoint policy for each of the companys S3 gateway endpoints that blocks access from any VPC other than the companys trusted VPCs.",
        "Create an S3 endpoint policy for each of the companys S3 gateway endpoints that provides access to the Amazon Resource Name (ARN) of the trusted S3 buckets."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an S3 endpoint policy for each of the companys S3 gateway endpoints that provides access to the Amazon Resource Name (ARN) of the trusted S3 buckets."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "166",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is using a VPC peering strategy to connect its VPCs in a single Region to allow for cross-communication. A recent increase in account creations and VPCs has made it difficult to maintain the VPC peering strategy, and the company expects to grow to hundreds of VPCs. There are also new requests to create site-to-site VPNs with some of the VPCs. A solutions architect has been tasked with creating a centrally networking setup for multiple accounts, VPCs, and VPNs. Which networking solution meets these requirements? ",
      "answers": [
        "Configure shared VPCs and VPNs and share to each other ",
        "Configure a hub-and-spoke and route all traffic through VPC peering.",
        "Configure an AWS Direct Connect between all VPCs and VPNs.",
        "Configure a transit gateway with AWS Transit Gateway and connected all VPCs and VPNs."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure a transit gateway with AWS Transit Gateway and connected all VPCs and VPNs."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "167",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is helping a developer design a new ecommerce shopping cart application using AWS services. The developer is unsure of the current database schema and expects to make changes as the ecommerce site grows. The solution needs to be highly resilient and capable of automatically scaling read and write capacity. Which database solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL",
        "Amazon DynamoDB with on-demand enabled",
        "Amazon DynamoDB with DynamoDB Streams enabled",
        "Amazon SQS and Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon DynamoDB with on-demand enabled"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "168",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solution architect must migrate a Windows internet information Services (IIS) web application to AWS. The application currently relies on a file share hosted in the users on-premises network-attached storage (NAS).The solution architected has proposed migrating the IIS web servers Which replacement to the on-promises file share is MOST resilient and durable?",
      "answers": [
        "Migrate the file Share to Amazon RDS.",
        "Migrate the tile Share to AWS Storage Gateway",
        "Migrate the file Share to Amazon FSx for Windows File Server.",
        "Migrate the tile share to Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Migrate the file Share to Amazon FSx for Windows File Server."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "169",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company needs to implement a relational database with a multi-Region disaster recovery Recovery Point Objective (RPO) of 1 second and an Recovery Time Objective (RTO) of 1 minute. Which AWS solution can achieve this?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Aurora Global Database",
        "Amazon DynamoDB global tables.",
        "Amazon RDS for MySQL with Multi-AZ enabled.",
        "Amazon RDS for MySQL with a cross-Region snapshot copy."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Aurora Global Database"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "170",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company runs a web service on Amazon CC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer. The instances run in an Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling group across two Availability Zones. The company needs a minimum of tour instances a! all limes to meet the required service level agreement (SLA) while keeping costs low. If an Availability Zone tails, how can the company remain compliant with the SLA?",
      "answers": [
        "Add a target tracking scaling policy with a short cooldown period.",
        "Change the Auto Scaling group launch configuration to use a larger instance type",
        "Change the Auto Scaling group to use six servers across three Availability Zones",
        "Change the Auto Scaling group to use eight servers across two Availability Zones"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Change the Auto Scaling group to use six servers across three Availability Zones"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "171",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is reviewing its AWS Cloud deployment to ensure its data is not accessed by anyone without appropriate authorization. A solutions architect is tasked with identifying all open Amazon S3 buckets and recording any S3 bucket configuration changes. What should the solutions architect do to accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Enable AWS Config service with the appropriate rules",
        "Enable AWS Trusted Advisor with the appropriate checks.",
        "Write a script using an AWS SDK to generate a bucket report",
        "Enable Amazon S3 server access logging and configure Amazon CloudWatch Events."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Enable AWS Config service with the appropriate rules"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "172",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is planning to build a new web application on AWS. The company expects predictable traffic most of the year and very high traffic on occasion. The web application needs to be highly available and fault tolerant with minimal latency. What should a solutions architect recommend to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Use an Amazon Route 53 routing policy to distribute requests to two AWS Regions, each with one Amazon EC2 instance.",
        "Use Amazon EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group with an Application Load Balancer across multiple Availability Zones.",
        "Use Amazon EC2 instances in a cluster placement group with an Application Load Balancer across multiple Availability Zones.",
        "Use Amazon EC2 instances in a cluster placement group and include the cluster placement group within a new Auto Scaling group."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group with an Application Load Balancer across multiple Availability Zones."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "173",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is designing a web application using AWS that processes insurance quotes. Users will request quotes from the application. Quotes must be separated by quote type must be responded to within 24 hours, and must not be lost. The solution should be simple to set up and maintain. Which solution meets these requirements",
      "answers": [
        "Create multiple Amazon Kinesis data streams based on the quote type. Configure the web application to send messages to the proper data stream. Configure each backend group of application servers to pool messages from its own data stream using the Kinesis Client Library (KCL).",
        "Create multiple Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topics and register Amazon SQS queues to their own SNS topic based on the quote type. Configure the web application to publish messages to the SNS topic queue. Configure each backend application server to work its own SQS queue.",
        "Create a single Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topic and subscribe the Amazon SQS queues to the SNS topic. Configure SNS message filtering to publish messages to the proper SQS queue based on the quote type. Configure each backend application server to work its own SQS queue.",
        "Create multiple Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose delivery streams based on the quote type to deliver data streams to an Amazon Elasticsearch Service (Amazon ES) cluster. Configure the web application to send messages to the proper delivery stream. Configure each backend group of application servers to search for the messages from Amazon ES and process them accordingly."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a single Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topic and subscribe the Amazon SQS queues to the SNS topic. Configure SNS message filtering to publish messages to the proper SQS queue based on the quote type. Configure each backend application server to work its own SQS queue."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "174",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect has configured the following IAM policy: Effect: Allow, Action: lambda, Resource: *; Effect: Deny, Action: lambda:CreateFunction, lambda:DeleteFunction, Resource: *, Condition: IpAddress: aws:SourceIp: 220.100.16.0/20. Which action will be allowed by the policy?",
      "answers": [
        "An AWS Lambda function can be deleted from any network.",
        "An AWS Lambda function can be created from any network.",
        "An AWS Lambda function can be deleted from the 100.220.0.0/20 network",
        "An AWS Lambda function can be deleted from the 220 100.16 0 20 network"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["An AWS Lambda function can be deleted from the 100.220.0.0/20 network"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "175",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is using Amazon S3 to design the storage architecture of a new digital media application. The media files must be resilient to the loss of an Availability Zone. Some files are accessed frequently while other files are rarely accessed in an unpredictable pattern. The solutions architect must minimize the costs of storing and retrieving the media files. Which storage option meets these requirements? ",
      "answers": [
        "S3 Standard",
        "S3 Intelligent-Tiering",
        "S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA)",
        "S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["S3 Intelligent-Tiering"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "176",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys operations team has an existing Amazon S3 bucket configured to notify an Amazon SQS queue when new objects are created within the bucket. The development team also wants to receive events when new objects are created. The existing operations team workflow must remain intact. Which solution would satisfy these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Create another SQS queue. Update the S3 events in the bucket to also update the new queue when a new object is created.",
        "Create a new SQS queue that only allows Amazon S3 access the queue. Update Amazon S3 to update tis queue written a new object is created.",
        "Create an Amazon SNS topic and SAS queue for the bucket updates. Update the bucket to send events to the new topic. Updates queues to poll Amazon SNS.",
        "Create an Amazon SNS topic and SQS queue for the bucket updates. Update the bucket to send events to the new topic. Add subscription for both queues in the topic."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Amazon SNS topic and SQS queue for the bucket updates. Update the bucket to send events to the new topic. Add subscription for both queues in the topic."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "177",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A media company stores video content in an Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume. A certain video file has become popular and a large number of users across the world are accessing this content. This has resulted in a cost increase. Which action will DECREASE cost without compromising user accessibility?",
      "answers": [
        "Change the EBS volume to Provisioned IOPS (PIOPS).",
        "Store the video in an Amazon S3 bucket and create an Amazon CloudFront distribution.",
        "Split the video into multiple, smaller segments so users are routed to the requested video segments only.",
        "Clear an Amazon S3 bucket in each Region and upload the videos so users are routed to the nearest S3 bucket."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Store the video in an Amazon S3 bucket and create an Amazon CloudFront distribution."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "178",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing the cloud architecture for a new application being deployed to AWS. The application allows users to interactively download and upload files. Files older than 2 years will be accessed less frequently. The solutions architect needs to ensure that the application can scale to any number of files while maintaining high availability and durability. Which scalable solutions should the solutions architect recommend? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Store the files on Amazon S3 with a lifecycle policy that moves objects older than 2 years to S3 Glacier.",
        "Store the files on Amazon S3 with a lifecycle policy that moves objects older than 2 years to S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA)",
        "Store the files on Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) with a lifecycle policy that moves objects older than 2 years to EFS Infrequent Access (EFS IA).",
        "Store the files in Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volumes. Schedule snapshots of the volumes. Use the snapshots to archive data older than 2 years.",
        "Store the files in RAID-striped Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volumes. Schedule snapshots of the volumes. Use the snapshots to archive data older than 2 years."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Store the files on Amazon S3 with a lifecycle policy that moves objects older than 2 years to S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA)",
        "Store the files on Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) with a lifecycle policy that moves objects older than 2 years to EFS Infrequent Access (EFS IA)."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "179",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has recently updated its internal security standards. The company must now ensure all Amazon S3 buckets and Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volumes are encrypted with keys created and periodically rotated by internal security specialists. The company is looking for a native, software-based AWS service to accomplish this goal. What should a solutions architect recommend as a solution?",
      "answers": [
        "Use AWS Secrets Manager with customer master keys (CMKs) to store master key material and apply a routine to create a new CMK periodically and replace it in AWS Secrets Manager.",
        "Use AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) with customer master keys (CMKs) to store master key material and apply a routine to re-create a new key periodically and replace it in AWS KMS.",
        "Use an AWS CloudHSM cluster with customer master keys (CMKs) to store master key material and apply a routine to re-create a new key periodically and replace it in the CloudHSM cluster nodes.",
        "Use AWS Systems Manager Parameter Store with customer master keys (CMKs) to store master key material and apply a routine to re-create a new key periodically and replace it in the Parameter Store."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) with customer master keys (CMKs) to store master key material and apply a routine to re-create a new key periodically and replace it in AWS KMS."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "180",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys dynamic website is hosted using on-premises servers in the United States. The company is launching its product in Europe, and it wants to optimize site loading times for new European users. The sites backend must remain in the United States. The product is being launched in a few days, and an immediate solution is needed. What should the solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Launch an Amazon EC2 instance in us-east-1 and migrate the site to it.",
        "Move the website to Amazon S3. Use cross-Region replication between Regions.",
        "Use Amazon CloudFront with a custom origin pointing to the on-premises servers",
        "Use an Amazon Route 53 geo-proximity routing policy pointing to on-premises servers."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon CloudFront with a custom origin pointing to the on-premises servers"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "181",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A development team needs to host a website that will be accessed by other teams. The website contents consist of HTML, CSS, client-side JavaScript, and images. Which method is the MOST cost-effective for hosting the website? ",
      "answers": [
        "Containerize the website and host it in AWS Fargate.",
        "Create an Amazon S3 bucket and host the website there.",
        "Deploy a web server on an Amazon EC2 instance to host the website.",
        "Configure an Application Load Balancer with an AWS Lambda target that uses the Express.js framework."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Amazon S3 bucket and host the website there."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "182",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A company is hosting multiple websites for several lines of business under its registered parent domain. Users accessing these websites will be routed to appropriate backend Amazon EC2 instances based on the subdomain. The websites host static webpages, images, and server-side scripts like PHP and JavaScript. Some of the websites experience peak access during the first two hours of business with constant usage throughout the rest of the day. A solutions architect needs to design a solution that will automatically adjust capacity to these traffic patterns while keeping costs low. Which combination of AWS services or features will meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "AWS Batch",
        "Network Load Balancer",
        "Application Load Balancer",
        "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling",
        "Amazon S3 website hosting"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Application Load Balancer",
        "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "183",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A company uses an Amazon S3 bucket to store static images for its website. The company configured permissions to allow access to Amazon S3 objects by privileged users only. What should a solutions architect do to protect against data loss? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Enable versioning on the S3 bucket.",
        "Enable access logging on the S3 bucket.",
        "Enable server-side encryption on the S3 bucket.",
        "Configure an S3 lifecycle rule to transition objects to Amazon S3 Glacier.",
        "Use MFA Delete to require multi-factor authentication to delete an object."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Enable versioning on the S3 bucket.",
        "Use MFA Delete to require multi-factor authentication to delete an object."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "184",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An application running on AWS uses an Amazon Aurora Multi-AZ deployment for its database. When evaluating performance metrics, a solutions architect discovered that the database reads are causing high I/O and adding latency to the write requests against the database. What should the solutions architect do to separate the read requests from the write requests? ",
      "answers": [
        "Enable read-through caching on the Amazon Aurora database.",
        "Update the application to read from the Multi-AZ standby instance.",
        "Create a read replica and modify the application to use the appropriate endpoint.",
        "Create a second Amazon Aurora database and link it to the primary database as a read replica. "
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Update the application to read from the Multi-AZ standby instance."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "185",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has been storing analytics data in an Amazon RDS instance for the past few years. The company asked a solutions architect to find a solution that allows users to access this data using an API. The expectation is that the application will experience periods of inactivity but could receive bursts of traffic within seconds. Which solution should the solutions architect suggest?",
      "answers": [
        "Set up an Amazon API Gateway and use Amazon ECS.",
        "Set up an Amazon API Gateway and use AWS Elastic Beanstalk.",
        "Set up an Amazon API Gateway and use AWS Lambda functions.",
        "Set up an Amazon API Gateway and use Amazon EC2 with Auto Scaling."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Set up an Amazon API Gateway and use AWS Lambda functions."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "186",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company must generate sales reports at the beginning of every month. The reporting process launches 20 Amazon EC2 instances on the first of the month. The process runs for 7 days and cannot be interrupted. The company wants to minimize costs. Which pricing model should the company choose?",
      "answers": [
        "Reserved Instances",
        "Spot Block Instances",
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Scheduled Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["On-Demand Instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "187",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys web application is using multiple Linux Amazon EC2 instances and storing data on Amazon EBS volumes. The company is looking for a solution to increase the resiliency of the application in case of a failure and to provide storage that complies with atomicity, consistency, isolation, and durability (ACID). What should a solutions architect do to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Launch the application on EC2 instances in each Availability Zone. Attach EBS volumes to each EC2 instance.",
        "Create an Application Load Balancer with Auto Scaling groups across multiple Availability Zones. Mount an instance store on each EC2 instance.",
        "Create an Application Load Balancer with Auto Scaling groups across multiple Availability Zones. Store data on Amazon EFS and mount a target on each instance.",
        "Create an Application Load Balancer with Auto Scaling groups across multiple Availability Zones. Store data using Amazon S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA)."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Application Load Balancer with Auto Scaling groups across multiple Availability Zones. Store data on Amazon EFS and mount a target on each instance."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "188",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is hosting a web application on AWS using a single Amazon EC2 instance that stores user-uploaded documents in an Amazon EBS volume. For better scalability and availability, the company duplicated the architecture and created a second EC2 instance and EBS volume in another Availability Zone, placing both behind an Application Load Balancer. After completing this change, users reported that, each time they refreshed the website, they could see one subset of their documents or the other, but never all of the documents at the same time. What should a solutions architect propose to ensure users see all of their documents at once?",
      "answers": [
        "Copy the data so both EBS volumes contain all the documents.",
        "Configure the Application Load Balancer to direct a user to the server with the documents.",
        "Copy the data from both EBS volumes to Amazon EFS. Modify the application to save new documents to Amazon EFS.",
        "Configure the Application Load Balancer to send the request to both servers. Return each document from the correct server."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Copy the data from both EBS volumes to Amazon EFS. Modify the application to save new documents to Amazon EFS."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "189",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is tasked with transferring 750 TB of data from a network-attached file system located at a branch office Amazon S3 Glacier. The solution must avoid saturating the branch offices low-bandwidth internet connection. What is the MOST cost-effective solution? ",
      "answers": [
        "Create a site-to-site VPN tunnel to an Amazon S3 bucket and transfer the files directly. Create a bucket VPC endpoint.",
        "Order 10 AWS Snowball appliances and select an S3 Glacier vault as the destination. Create a bucket policy to enforce VPC endpoint.",
        "Mount the network-attached file system to Amazon S3 and copy the files directly. Create a lifecycle policy to S3 objects to Amazon S3 Glacier.",
        "Order 10 AWS Snowball appliances and select an Amazon S3 bucket as the destination. Create a lifecycle policy to transition the S3 objects to Amazon S3 Glacier."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Order 10 AWS Snowball appliances and select an Amazon S3 bucket as the destination. Create a lifecycle policy to transition the S3 objects to Amazon S3 Glacier."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "190",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An application running on AWS uses an Amazon Aurora Multi-AZ deployment for its database. When evaluating performance metrics, a solutions architect discovered that the database reads are causing high I/O and adding latency to the write requests against the database. What should the solutions architect do to separate the read requests from the write requests? ",
      "answers": [
        "Enable read-through caching on the Amazon Aurora database.",
        "Update the application to read from the Multi-AZ standby instance.",
        "Create a read replica and modify the application to use the appropriate endpoint.",
        "Create a second Amazon Aurora database and link it to the primary database as a read replica."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Update the application to read from the Multi-AZ standby instance."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "191",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has been storing analytics data in an Amazon RDS instance for the past few years. The company asked a solutions architect to find a solution that allows users to access this data using an API. The expectation is that the application will experience periods of inactivity but could receive bursts of traffic within seconds. Which solution should the solutions architect suggest?",
      "answers": [
        "Set up an Amazon API Gateway and use Amazon ECS.",
        "Set up an Amazon API Gateway and use AWS Elastic Beanstalk.",
        "Set up an Amazon API Gateway and use AWS Lambda functions.",
        "Set up an Amazon API Gateway and use Amazon EC2 with Auto Scaling."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Set up an Amazon API Gateway and use AWS Lambda functions."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "192",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company must generate sales reports at the beginning of every month. The reporting process launches 20 Amazon EC2 instances on the first of the month. The process runs for 7 days and cannot be interrupted. The company wants to minimize costs. Which pricing model should the company choose?",
      "answers": [
        "Reserved Instances",
        "Spot Block Instances",
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Scheduled Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["On-Demand Instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "193",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys web application is using multiple Linux Amazon EC2 instances and storing data on Amazon EBS volumes. The company is looking for a solution to increase the resiliency of the application in case of a failure and to provide storage that complies with atomicity, consistency, isolation, and durability (ACID). What should a solutions architect do to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Launch the application on EC2 instances in each Availability Zone. Attach EBS volumes to each EC2 instance.",
        "Create an Application Load Balancer with Auto Scaling groups across multiple Availability Zones. Mount an instance store on each EC2 instance.",
        "Create an Application Load Balancer with Auto Scaling groups across multiple Availability Zones. Store data on Amazon EFS and mount a target on each instance.",
        "Create an Application Load Balancer with Auto Scaling groups across multiple Availability Zones. Store data using Amazon S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA)."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Application Load Balancer with Auto Scaling groups across multiple Availability Zones. Store data on Amazon EFS and mount a target on each instance."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "194",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is hosting a web application on AWS using a single Amazon EC2 instance that stores user-uploaded documents in an Amazon EBS volume. For better scalability and availability, the company duplicated the architecture and created a second EC2 instance and EBS volume in another Availability Zone, placing both behind an Application Load Balancer. After completing this change, users reported that, each time they refreshed the website, they could see one subset of their documents or the other, but never all of the documents at the same time. What should a solutions architect propose to ensure users see all of their documents at once?",
      "answers": [
        "Copy the data so both EBS volumes contain all the documents.",
        "Configure the Application Load Balancer to direct a user to the server with the documents.",
        "Copy the data from both EBS volumes to Amazon EFS. Modify the application to save new documents to Amazon EFS.",
        "Configure the Application Load Balancer to send the request to both servers. Return each document from the correct server."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Copy the data from both EBS volumes to Amazon EFS. Modify the application to save new documents to Amazon EFS."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "195",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is tasked with transferring 750 TB of data from a network-attached file system located at a branch office Amazon S3 Glacier. The solution must avoid saturating the branch offices low-bandwidth internet connection. What is the MOST cost-effective solution?",
      "answers": [
        "Create a site-to-site VPN tunnel to an Amazon S3 bucket and transfer the files directly. Create a bucket VPC endpoint.",
        "Order 10 AWS Snowball appliances and select an S3 Glacier vault as the destination. Create a bucket policy to enforce VPC endpoint.",
        "Mount the network-attached file system to Amazon S3 and copy the files directly. Create a lifecycle policy to S3 objects to Amazon S3 Glacier.",
        "Order 10 AWS Snowball appliances and select an Amazon S3 bucket as the destination. Create a lifecycle policy to transition the S3 objects to Amazon S3 Glacier."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Order 10 AWS Snowball appliances and select an Amazon S3 bucket as the destination. Create a lifecycle policy to transition the S3 objects to Amazon S3 Glacier."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "196",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An operations team has a standard that states IAM policies should not be applied directly to users. Some new members have not been following this standard. The operation manager needs a way to easily identify the users with attached policies. What should a solutions architect do to accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Monitor using AWS CloudTrail.",
        "Create an AWS Config rule to run daily.",
        "Publish IAM user changes to Amazon SNS.",
        "Run AWS Lambda when a user is modified."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an AWS Config rule to run daily."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "197",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company wants to use an AWS Region as a disaster recovery location for its on-premises infrastructure. The company has 10 TB of existing data, and the on- premise data center has a 1 Gbps internet connection. A solutions architect must find a solution so the company can have its existing data on AWS in 72 hours without transmitting it using an unencrypted channel. Which solution should the solutions architect select?",
      "answers": [
        "Send the initial 10 TB of data to AWS using FTP.",
        "Send the initial 10 TB of data to AWS using AWS Snowball.",
        "Establish a VPN connection between Amazon VPC and the companys data center.",
        "Establish an AWS Direct Connect connection between Amazon VPC and the companys data center."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Establish a VPN connection between Amazon VPC and the companys data center."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "198",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is building applications in containers. The company wants to migrate its on-premises development and operations services from its on-premises data center to AWS. Management states that production system must be cloud agnostic and use the same configuration and administrator tools across production systems. A solutions architect needs to design a managed solution that will align open-source software. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Launch the containers on Amazon EC2 with EC2 instance worker nodes.",
        "Launch the containers on Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) and EKS workers nodes.",
        "Launch the containers on Amazon Elastic Containers service (Amazon ECS) with AWS Fargate instances.",
        "Launch the containers on Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) with Amazon EC2 instance worker nodes."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Launch the containers on Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) and EKS workers nodes."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "199",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company hosts its website on AWS. To address the highly variable demand, the company has implemented Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling. Management is concerned that the company is over-provisioning its infrastructure, especially at the front end of the three-tier application. A solutions architect needs to ensure costs are optimized without impacting performance. What should the solutions architect do to accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Auto Scaling with Reserved Instances.",
        "Use Auto Scaling with a scheduled scaling policy.",
        "Use Auto Scaling with the suspend-resume feature",
        "Use Auto Scaling with a target tracking scaling policy."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Auto Scaling with a target tracking scaling policy."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "200",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solution architect is performing a security review of a recently migrated workload. The workload is a web application that consists of Amazon EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group behind an Application Load balancer. The solution architect must improve the security posture and minimize the impact of a DDoS attack on resources. Which solution is MOST effective?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure an AWS WAF ACL with rate-based rules. Create an Amazon CloudFront distribution that points to the Application Load Balancer. Enable the EAF ACL on the CloudFront distribution.",
        "Create a custom AWS Lambda function that adds identified attacks into a common vulnerability pool to capture a potential DDoS attack. Use the identified information to modify a network ACL to block access.",
        "Enable VPC Flow Logs and store then in Amazon S3. Create a custom AWS Lambda functions that parses the logs looking for a DDoS attack. Modify a network ACL to block identified source IP addresses.",
        "Enable Amazon GuardDuty and, configure findings written 10 Amazon CloudWatch. Create an event with Cloud Watch Events for DDoS alerts that triggers Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS). Have Amazon SNS invoke a custom AWS lambda function that parses the logs looking for a DDoS attack. Modify a network ACL to block identified source IP addresses"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure an AWS WAF ACL with rate-based rules. Create an Amazon CloudFront distribution that points to the Application Load Balancer. Enable the EAF ACL on the CloudFront distribution."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "201",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has multiple AWS accounts, for various departments. One of the departments wants to share an Amazon S3 bucket with all other department. Which solution will require the LEAST amount of effort?",
      "answers": [
        "Enable cross-account S3 replication for the bucket.",
        "Create a pre-signed URL for the bucket and share it with other departments.",
        "Set the S3 bucket policy to allow cross-account access to other departments.",
        "Create IAM users for each of the departments and configure a read-only IAM policy."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Set the S3 bucket policy to allow cross-account access to other departments."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "202",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company needs to share an Amazon S3 bucket with an external vendor. The bucket owner must be able to access all objects. Which action should be taken to share the S3 bucket? ",
      "answers": [
        "Update the bucket to be a Requester Pays bucket.",
        "Update the bucket to enable cross-origin resource sharing (CORS).",
        "Create a bucket policy to require users to grant bucket-owner-full-control when uploading objects.",
        "Create an IAM policy to require users to grant bucket-owner-full-control when uploading objects."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a bucket policy to require users to grant bucket-owner-full-control when uploading objects."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "203",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is developing a real-time multiplier game that uses UDP for communications between client and servers in an Auto Scaling group. Spikes in demand are anticipated during the day, so the game server platform must adapt accordingly. Developers want to store gamer scores and other non-relational data in a database solution that will scale without intervention. Which solution should a solution architect recommend? ",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon Route 53 for traffic distribution and Amazon Aurora Serverless for data storage.",
        "Use a Network Load Balancer for traffic distribution and Amazon DynamoDB on demand for data storage.",
        "Use a Network Load Balancer for traffic distribution and Amazon Aura Global for data storage.",
        "Use an Application Load Balancer for traffic distribution and Amazon DynamoDB global tables for data storage."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use a Network Load Balancer for traffic distribution and Amazon DynamoDB on demand for data storage."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "204",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company collects temperature, humidity, and atmospheric pressure data in cities across multiple continents. The average volume of data collected per site each day is 500 GB. Each site has a high-speed internet connection. The companys weather forecasting applications are based in a single Region and analyze the data daily. What is the FASTEST way to aggregate data for all of these global sites?",
      "answers": [
        "Enable Amazon S3 Transfer Acceleration on the destination bucket. Use multipart uploads to directly upload site data to the destination bucket.",
        "Upload site data to an Amazon S3 bucket in the closest AWS Region. Use S3 cross-Region replication to copy objects to the destination bucket.",
        "Schedule AWS Snowball jobs daily to transfer data to the closest AWS Region. Use S3 cross-Region replication to copy objects to the destination bucket.",
        "Upload the data to an Amazon EC2 instance in the closes Region. Store the data in an Amazon EBS volume. One a day take an EBS snapshot and copy it to the centralize Region. Restore the EBS volume in the centralized Region and run an analysis on the data daily."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Enable Amazon S3 Transfer Acceleration on the destination bucket. Use multipart uploads to directly upload site data to the destination bucket."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "205",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a custom application running on an Amazon EC instance that: 1)Reads a large amount of data from Amazon S3  2)Performs a multi-stage analysis  3)Writes the results to Amazon DynamoDB. The application writes a significant number of large temporary files during the multi-stage analysis. The process performance depends on the temporary storage performance. What would be the fastest storage option for holding the temporary files?",
      "answers": [
        "Multiple Amazon S3 buckets with Transfer Acceleration for storage.",
        "Multiple Amazon EBS drives with Provisioned IOPS and EBS optimization.",
        "Multiple Amazon EFS volumes using the Network I lie System version 4.1 (NFSv4.1) protocol.",
        "Multiple instance store volumes with software RAID 0."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Multiple instance store volumes with software RAID 0."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "206",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A leasing company generates and emails PDF statements every month for all its customers. Each statement is about 400 KB in size. Customers can download their statements from the website for up to 30 days from when the statements were generated. At the end of their 3-year lease, the customers are emailed a ZIP file that contains all the statements. What is the MOST cost-effective storage solution for this situation?",
      "answers": [
        "Store the statements using the Amazon S3 Standard storage class. Create a lifecycle policy to move the statements to Amazon S3 Glacier storage after 1 day.",
        "Store the statements using the Amazon S3 Glacier storage class. Create a lifecycle policy to move the statements to Amazon S3 Glacier Deep Archive storage after 30 days.",
        "Store the statements using the Amazon S3 Standard storage class. Create a lifecycle policy to move the statements to Amazon S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA) storage after 30 days.",
        "Store the statements using the Amazon S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA) storage class. Create a lifecycle policy to move the statements to Amazon S3 Glacier storage after 30 days."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Store the statements using the Amazon S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA) storage class. Create a lifecycle policy to move the statements to Amazon S3 Glacier storage after 30 days."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "207",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company recently released a new type of internet-connected sensor. The company is expecting to sell thousands of sensors, which are designed to stream high volumes of data each second to a central location. A solutions architect must design a solution that ingests and stores data so that engineering teams can analyze it in near-real time with millisecond responsiveness. Which solution should the solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Use an Amazon SQS queue to ingest the data. Consume the data with an AWS Lambda function, which then stores the data in Amazon Redshift.",
        "Use an Amazon SOS queue to ingest the data. Consume the data with an AWS Lambda function, which then stores the data in Amazon DynamoDB.",
        "Use Amazon Kinesis Data Streams to ingest the data. Consume the data with an AWS Lambda function, which then stores the data in Amazon Redshift.",
        "Use Amazon Kinesis Data Streams to ingest the data. Consume the data with an AWS Lambda function, which then stores the data in Amazon DynamoDB."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon Kinesis Data Streams to ingest the data. Consume the data with an AWS Lambda function, which then stores the data in Amazon DynamoDB."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "208",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A website runs a web application that receives a burst of traffic each day at noon. The users upload new pictures and content daily, but have been complaining of timeouts. The architecture uses Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling groups, and the custom application consistently takes 1 minute to initiate upon boot up before responding to user requests. How should a solutions architect redesign the architecture to better respond to changing traffic?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure a Network Load Balancer with a slow start configuration.",
        "Configure AWS ElastiCache for Redis to offload direct requests to the servers.",
        "Configure an Auto Scaling step scaling policy with an instance warmup condition.",
        "Configure Amazon CloudFront to use an Application Load Balancer as the origin."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure an Auto Scaling step scaling policy with an instance warmup condition."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "209",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is concerned that two NAT instances in use will no longer be able to support the traffic needed for the companys application. A solutions architect wants to implement a solution that is highly available fault tolerant, and automatically scalable. What should the solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Remove the two NAT instances and replace them with two NAT gateways in the same Availability Zone.",
        "Use Auto Scaling groups with Network Load Balancers for the NAT instances in different Availability Zones.",
        "Remove the two NAT instances and replace them with two NAT gateways in different Availability Zones.",
        "Replace the two NAT instances with Spot Instances in different Availability Zones and deploy a Network Load Balancer."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Remove the two NAT instances and replace them with two NAT gateways in different Availability Zones."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "210",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company operates a website on Amazon EC2 Linux instances. Some of the instances are failing. Troubleshooting points to insufficient swap space on the failed instances. The operations team lead needs a solution to monitor this. What should a solutions architect recommend? ",
      "answers": [
        "Configure an Amazon CloudWatch Swap Usage metric dimension. Monitor the Swap Usage dimension in the EC2 metrics in CloudWatch.",
        "Use EC2 metadata to collect information, then publish it to Amazon CloudWatch custom metrics. Monitor Swap Usage metrics in CloudWatch.",
        "Install an Amazon CloudWatch agent on the instances. Run an appropriate script on a set schedule. Monitor Swap Utilization metrics in CloudWatch.",
        "Enable detailed monitoring in the EC2 console. Create an Amazon CloudWatch Swap Utilization custom metric. Monitor Swap Utilization metrics in CloudWatch."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Install an Amazon CloudWatch agent on the instances. Run an appropriate script on a set schedule. Monitor Swap Utilization metrics in CloudWatch."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "211",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A company has a web server running on an Amazon EC2 instance in a public subnet with an Elastic IP address. The default security group is assigned to the EC2 instance. The default network ACL has been modified to block all traffic. A solutions architect needs to make the web server accessible from everywhere on port 443. Which combination of steps will accomplish this task? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Create a security group with a rule to allow TCP port 443 from source 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Create a security group with a rule to allow TCP port 443 to destination 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Update the network ACL to allow TCP port 443 from source 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Update the network ACL to allow inbound/outbound TCP port 443 from source 0.0.0.0/0 and to destination 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Update the network ACL to allow inbound TCP port 443 from source 0.0.0.0/0 and outbound TCP port 32768-65535 to destination 0/0.0.0/0."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a security group with a rule to allow TCP port 443 from source 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Update the network ACL to allow inbound TCP port 443 from source 0.0.0.0/0 and outbound TCP port 32768-65535 to destination 0/0.0.0/0."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "212",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company must re-evaluate its need for the Amazon EC2 instances it currently has provisioned in an Auto Scaling group. At present, the Auto Scaling group is configured for a minimum of two instances and a maximum of four instances across two Availability Zones. A Solutions architect reviewed Amazon CloudWatch metrics and found that CPU utilization is consistently low for all the EC2 instances. What should the solutions architect recommend to maximize utilization while ensuring the application remains fault tolerant?",
      "answers": [
        "Remove some EC2 instances to increase the utilization of remaining instances.",
        "Increase the Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) capacity of instances with less CPU utilization.",
        "Modify the Auto Scaling group scaling policy to scale in and out based on a higher CPU utilization metric.",
        "Create a new launch configuration that uses smaller instance types. Update the existing Auto Scaling group."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a new launch configuration that uses smaller instance types. Update the existing Auto Scaling group."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "213",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has an application that posts messages to Amazon SQS. Another application polls the queue and processes the messages in an I/O-intensive operation. The company has a service level agreement (SLA) that specifies the maximum amount of time that can elapse between receiving the messages and responding to the users. Due to an increase in the number of messages the company has difficulty meeting its SLA consistently. What should a solutions architect do to help improve the applications processing time and ensure it can handle the load at any level?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) from the instance used for processing. Terminate the instance and replace it with a larger size.",
        "Create an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) from the instance used for processing. Terminate the instance and replace it with an Amazon EC2 Dedicated Instance.",
        "Create an Amazon Machine image (AMI) from the instance used for processing. Create an Auto Scaling group using this image in its launch configuration. Configure the group with a target tracking policy to keep us aggregate CPU utilization below 70%.",
        "Create an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) from the instance used for processing. Create an Auto Scaling group using this image in its launch configuration. Configure the group with a target tracking policy based on the age of the oldest message in the SQS queue."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) from the instance used for processing. Create an Auto Scaling group using this image in its launch configuration. Configure the group with a target tracking policy based on the age of the oldest message in the SQS queue."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "214",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is designing a new service that will run on Amazon EC2 instance behind an Elastic Load Balancer. However, many of the web service clients can only reach IP addresses whitelisted on their firewalls. What should a solution architect recommend to meet the clients needs?",
      "answers": [
        "A Network Load Balancer with an associated Elastic IP address.",
        "An Application Load Balancer with an associated Elastic IP address",
        "An A record in an Amazon Route 53 hosted zone pointing to an Elastic IP address",
        "An EC2 instance with a public IP address running as a proxy in front of the load balancer"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["A Network Load Balancer with an associated Elastic IP address."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "215",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company wants to host a web application on AWS that will communicate to a database within a VPC. The application should be highly available. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Create two Amazon EC2 instances to host the web servers behind a load balancer, and then deploy the database on a large instance.",
        "Deploy a load balancer in multiple Availability Zones with an Auto Scaling group for the web servers, and then deploy Amazon RDS in multiple Availability Zones.",
        "Deploy a load balancer in the public subnet with an Auto Scaling group for the web servers, and then deploy the database on an Amazon EC2 instance in the private subnet.",
        "Deploy two web servers with an Auto Scaling group, configure a domain that points to the two web servers, and then deploy a database architecture in multiple Availability Zones."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy a load balancer in multiple Availability Zones with an Auto Scaling group for the web servers, and then deploy Amazon RDS in multiple Availability Zones."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "216",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys packaged application dynamically creates and returns single-use text files in response to user requests. The company is using Amazon CloudFront for distribution, but wants to future reduce data transfer costs. The company cannot modify the applications source code. What should a solution architect do to reduce costs?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Lambda@Edge to compress the files as they are sent to users.",
        "Enable Amazon S3 Transfer Acceleration to reduce the response times.",
        "Enable caching on the CloudFront distribution to store generated files at the edge.",
        "Use Amazon S3 multipart uploads to move the files to Amazon S3 before returning them to users."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Lambda@Edge to compress the files as they are sent to users."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "217",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A database is on an Amazon RDS MySQL 5.6 Multi-AZ DB instance that experience highly dynamic reads. Application developers notice a significant slowdown when testing read performance from a secondary AWS Region. The developers want a solution that provides less than 1 second of read replication latency. What should the solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Install MySQL on Amazon EC2 in the secondary Region.",
        "Migrate the database to Amazon Aurora with cross-Region replicas.",
        "Create another RDS for MySQL read replica in the secondary.",
        "Implement Amazon ElastiCache to improve database query performance."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Migrate the database to Amazon Aurora with cross-Region replicas."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "218",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is planning to deploy an Amazon RDS DB instance running Amazon Aurora. The company has a backup retention policy requirement of 90 days. Which solution should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Set the backup retention period to 90 days when creating the RDS DB instance.",
        "Configure RDS to copy automated snapshots to a user-managed Amazon S3 bucket with a lifecycle policy set to delete after 90 days.",
        "Create an AWS Backup plan to perform a daily snapshot of the RDS database with the retention set to 90 days. Create an AWS Backup job to schedule the execution of the backup plan daily.",
        "Use a daily scheduled event with Amazon CloudWatch Events to execute a custom AWS Lambda function that makes a copy of the RDS automated snapshot. Purge snapshots older than 90 days."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an AWS Backup plan to perform a daily snapshot of the RDS database with the retention set to 90 days. Create an AWS Backup job to schedule the execution of the backup plan daily."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "219",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company currently has 250 TB of backup files stored in Amazon S3 in a vendors proprietary format. Using a Linux-based software application provided by the vendor, the company wants to retrieve files from Amazon S3, transform the files to an industry-standard format, and re-upload them to Amazon S3. The company wants to minimize the data transfer charges associated with this conversation. What should a solution architect do to accomplish this? ",
      "answers": [
        "Install the conversion software as an Amazon S3 batch operation so the data is transformed without leaving Amazon S3.",
        "Install the conversion software onto an on-premises virtual machine. Perform the transformation and re-upload the files to Amazon S3 from the virtual machine.",
        "Use AWS Snowball Edge device to expert the data and install the conversion software onto the devices. Perform the data transformation and re-upload the files to Amazon S3 from the Snowball Edge devices.",
        "Launch an Amazon EC2 instance in the same Region as Amazon S3 and install the conversion software onto the instance. Perform the transformation and re- upload the files to Amazon S3 from the EC2 instance."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Launch an Amazon EC2 instance in the same Region as Amazon S3 and install the conversion software onto the instance. Perform the transformation and re- upload the files to Amazon S3 from the EC2 instance."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "220",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is migrating a NoSQL database cluster to Amazon EC2. The database automatically replicates data to maintain at least three copies of the data. I/O throughput of the servers is the highest priority. Which instance type should a solutions architect recommend for the migration?",
      "answers": [
        "Storage optimized instances with instance store",
        "Burstable general purpose instances with an Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume",
        "Memory optimized instances with Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) optimization enabled",
        "Compute optimized instances with Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) optimization enabled"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Storage optimized instances with instance store"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "221",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a large Microsoft SharePoint deployment running on-premises that requires Microsoft Windows shared file storage. The company wants to migrate this workload to the AWS Cloud and is considering various storage options. The storage solution must be highly available and integrated with Active Directory for access control. Which solution will satisfy these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure Amazon EFS storage and set the Active Directory domain for authentication.",
        "Create an SMB file share on an AWS Storage Gateway file gateway in two Availability Zones.",
        "Create an Amazon S3 bucket and configure Microsoft Windows Server to mount it as a volume.",
        "Create an Amazon FSx for Windows File Server file system on AWS and set the Active Directory domain for authentication."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Amazon FSx for Windows File Server file system on AWS and set the Active Directory domain for authentication."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "222",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a web application with sporadic usage patterns. There is heavy usage at the beginning of each month, moderate usage at the start of each week, and unpredictable usage during the week. The application consists of a web server and a MySQL database server running inside the data center. The company would like to move the application to the AWS Cloud, and needs to select a cost-effective database platform that will not require database modifications. Which solution will meet these requirements? ",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "Amazon RDS for MySQL",
        "MySQL-compatible Amazon Aurora Serverless",
        "MySQL deployed on Amazon EC2 in an Auto Scaling group"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["MySQL-compatible Amazon Aurora Serverless"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "223",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing the storage architecture for a new web application used for storing and viewing engineering drawings. All application components will be deployed on the AWS infrastructure. The application design must support caching to minimize the amount of time that users wait for the engineering drawings to load. The application must be able to store petabytes of data. Which combination of storage and caching should the solutions architect use?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon S3 with Amazon CloudFront",
        "Amazon S3 Glacier with Amazon ElastiCache",
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volumes with Amazon CloudFront",
        "AWS Storage Gateway with Amazon ElastiCache"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon S3 with Amazon CloudFront"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "224",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company hosts its core network services, including directory services and DNS, in its on promises data center. The data center is connected to the AWS Cloud using AWS Direct Connect (DX). Additional AWS accounts are planned that will require quick, cost-effective, and consistent access to these network services. What should a solutions architect implement to meet these requirements with the LEAST amount of operational overhead?",
      "answers": [
        "Create a DX connection in each new account. Route the network traffic to the on-premises servers.",
        "Configure VPC endpoints in the DX VPC for all required services. Route the network traffic to the on-premises servers.",
        "Create a VPN connection between each new account and the DX VPC. Route the network traffic to the on-premises servers.",
        "Configure AWS Transit Gateway between the accounts. Assigns DX to the transit gateway and route network traffic to the on-premises servers."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure AWS Transit Gateway between the accounts. Assigns DX to the transit gateway and route network traffic to the on-premises servers."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "225",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A-company receives structured and semi-structured data from various sources once every day. A solutions architect needs to design a solution that leverages big data processing frameworks. The data should be accessible using SQL queries and business intelligence tools. What should the solutions architect recommend to build the MOST high-performing solution?",
      "answers": [
        "Use AWS Glue to process data and Amazon S3 to store data.",
        "Use Amazon EMR to process data and Amazon Redshift to store data.",
        "Use Amazon EC2 to process data and Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) to store data.",
        "Use Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics to process data and Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) to store data."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon EMR to process data and Amazon Redshift to store data."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "226",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is creating an application that will handle batch processing of large amounts of data. The input data will be held in Amazon S3 and the output data will be stored in a different S3 bucket. For processing, the application will transfer the data over the network between multiple Amazon EC2 instances. What should the solutions architect do to reduce the overall data transfer costs?",
      "answers": [
        "Place all the EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group.",
        "Place all the EC2 instances in the same AWS Region.",
        "Place all the EC2 instances in the same Availability Zone.",
        "Place all the EC2 instances in private subnets in multiple Availability Zones."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Place all the EC2 instances in the same Availability Zone."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "227",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company operates an ecommerce website on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB) in an Auto Scaling group. The site is experiencing performance issues related to a high request rate from illegitimate external systems with changing IP addresses. The security team is worried about potential DDoS attacks against the website. The company must block the illegitimate incoming requests in a way that has a minimal impact on legitimate users. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Deploy Amazon Inspector and associate it with the ALB.",
        "Deploy AWS WAF, associate it with the ALB, and configure a rate-limiting rule.",
        "Deploy rules to the network ACLs associated with the ALB to block the incoming traffic.",
        "Deploy Amazon GuardDuty and enable rate-limiting protection when configuring GuardDuty."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy AWS WAF, associate it with the ALB, and configure a rate-limiting rule."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "228",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is hosting an election reporting website on AWS for users around the world. The website uses Amazon EC2 instances for the web and application tiers in an Auto Scaling group with Application Load Balancers. The database tier uses an Amazon RDS for MySQL database. The website is updated with election results once an hour and has historically observed hundreds of users accessing the reports. The company is expecting a significant increase in demand because of upcoming elections in different countries. A solutions architect must improve the websites ability to handle additional demand while minimizing the need for additional EC2 instances. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Launch an Amazon ElastiCache cluster to cache common database queries.",
        "Launch an Amazon CloudFront web distribution to cache commonly requested website content.",
        "Enable disk-based caching on the EC2 instances to cache commonly requested website content.",
        "Deploy a reverse proxy into the design using an EC2 instance with caching enabled for commonly requested website content."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Launch an Amazon CloudFront web distribution to cache commonly requested website content."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "229",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is running a three-tier web application to process credit card payments. The front-end user interface consists of static webpages. The application tier can have long-running processes. The database tier uses MySQL. The application is currently running on a single, general purpose large Amazon EC2 instance. A solutions architect needs to decouple the services to make the web application highly available. Which solution would provide the HIGHEST availability?",
      "answers": [
        "Move static assets to Amazon CloudFront. Leave the application in EC2 in an Auto Scaling group. Move the database to Amazon RDS to deploy Multi-AZ.",
        "Move static assets and the application into a medium EC2 instance. Leave the database on the large instance. Place both instances in an Auto Scaling group.",
        "Move static assets to Amazon S3, Move the application to AWS Lambda with the concurrency limit set. Move the database to Amazon DynamoDB with on- demand enabled.",
        "Move static assets to Amazon S3. Move the application to Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) containers with Auto Scaling enabled, Move the database to Amazon RDS to deploy Multi-AZ."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Move static assets to Amazon S3. Move the application to Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) containers with Auto Scaling enabled, Move the database to Amazon RDS to deploy Multi-AZ."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "230",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a two-tier web application. The application consists of a public-facing web tier hosted on Amazon EC2 in public subnets. The database tier consists of Microsoft SQL Server running on Amazon EC2 in a private subnet. Security is a high priority for the company. How should security groups be configured in this situation? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Configure the security group for the web tier to allow inbound traffic on port 443 from 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Configure the security group for the web tier to allow outbound traffic on port 443 from 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Configure the security group for the database tier to allow inbound traffic on port 1433 from the security group for the web tier.",
        "Configure the security group for the database tier to allow outbound traffic on ports 443 and 1433 to the security group for the web tier.",
        "Configure the security group for the database tier to allow inbound traffic on ports 443 and 1433 from the security group for the web tier."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure the security group for the web tier to allow inbound traffic on port 443 from 0.0.0.0/0.",
        "Configure the security group for the database tier to allow inbound traffic on port 1433 from the security group for the web tier."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "231",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is building a website that relies on reading and writing to an Amazon DynamoDB database. The traffic associated with the website predictably peaks during business hours on weekdays and declines overnight and during weekends. A solutions architect needs to design a cost-effective solution that can handle the load. What should the solutions architect do to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Enable DynamoDB Accelerator (DAX) to cache the data.",
        "Enable Multi-AZ replication for the DynamoDB database.",
        "Enable DynamoDB auto scaling when creating the tables.",
        "Enable DynamoDB On-Demand capacity allocation when creating the tables."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Enable DynamoDB auto scaling when creating the tables."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "232",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company uses Amazon Redshift for its data warehouse. The company wants to ensure high durability for its data in case of any component failure. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Enable concurrency scaling.",
        "Enable cross-Region snapshots.",
        "Increase the data retention period.",
        "Deploy Amazon Redshift in Multi-AZ."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Enable cross-Region snapshots."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "233",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has data stored in an on-premises data center that is used by several on-premises applications. The company wants to maintain its existing application environment and be able to use AWS services for data analytics and future visualizations. Which storage service should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Redshift",
        "AWS Storage Gateway for files",
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)",
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Storage Gateway for files"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "234",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect must design a solution that uses Amazon CloudFront with an Amazon S3 origin to store a static website. The companys security policy requires that all website traffic be inspected by AWS WAF. How should the solutions architect comply with these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure an S3 bucket policy to accept requests coming from the AWS WAF Amazon Resource Name (ARN) only.",
        "Configure Amazon CloudFront to forward all incoming requests to AWS WAF before requesting content from the S3 origin.",
        "Configure a security group that allows Amazon CloudFront IP addresses to access Amazon S3 only. Associate AWS WAF to CloudFront.",
        "Configure Amazon CloudFront and Amazon S3 to use an origin access identity (OAI) to restrict access to the S3 bucket. Enable AWS WAF on the distribution."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure Amazon CloudFront and Amazon S3 to use an origin access identity (OAI) to restrict access to the S3 bucket. Enable AWS WAF on the distribution."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "235",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a 143 TB MySQL database that it wants to migrate to AWS. The plan is to use Amazon Aurora MySQL as the platform going forward. The company has a 100 Mbps AWS Direct Connect connection to Amazon VPC. Which solution meets the companys needs and takes the LEAST amount of time?",
      "answers": [
        "Use a gateway endpoint for Amazon S3. Migrate the data to Amazon S3. Import the data into Aurora.",
        "Upgrade the Direct Connect link to 500 Mbps. Copy the data to Amazon S3. Import the data into Aurora.",
        "Order an AWS Snowmobile and copy the database backup to it. Have AWS import the data into Amazon S3. Import the backup into Aurora.",
        "Order four 50-TB AWS Snowball devices and copy the database backup onto them. Have AWS import the data into Amazon S3. Import the data into Aurora."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Order four 50-TB AWS Snowball devices and copy the database backup onto them. Have AWS import the data into Amazon S3. Import the data into Aurora."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "236",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company hosts an online shopping application that stores all orders in an Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL Single-AZ DB instance. Management wants to eliminate single points of failure and has asked a solutions architect to recommend an approach to minimize database downtime without requiring any changes to the application code. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Convert the existing database instance to a Multi-AZ deployment by modifying the database instance and specifying the Multi-AZ option.",
        "Create a new RDS Multi-AZ deployment. Take a snapshot of the current RDS instance and restore the new Multi-AZ deployment with the snapshot.",
        "Create a read-only replica of the PostgreSQL database in another Availability Zone. Use Amazon Route 53 weighted record sets to distribute requests across the databases.",
        "Place the RDS for PostgreSQL database in an Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling group with a minimum group size of two. Use Amazon Route 53 weighted record sets to distribute requests across instances."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Convert the existing database instance to a Multi-AZ deployment by modifying the database instance and specifying the Multi-AZ option."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "237",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a 10 Gbps AWS Direct Connect connection from its on-premises servers to AWS. The workloads using the connection are critical. The company requires a disaster recovery strategy with maximum resiliency that maintains the current connection bandwidth at a minimum. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Set up a new Direct Connect connection in another AWS Region.",
        "Set up a new AWS managed VPN connection in another AWS Region.",
        "Set up two new Direct Connect connections: one in the current AWS Region and one in another Region.",
        "Set up two new AWS managed VPN connections: one in the current AWS Region and one in another Region."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Set up two new Direct Connect connections: one in the current AWS Region and one in another Region."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "238",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a VPC with public and private subnets. The VPC and subnets use IPv4 CIDR blocks. There is one public subnet and one private subnet in each of three Availability Zones (AZs) for high availability. An internet gateway is used to provide internet access for the public subnets. The private subnets require access to the internet to allow Amazon EC2 instances to download software updates. What should the solutions architect do to enable internet access for the private subnets?",
      "answers": [
        "Create three NAT gateways, one for each public subnet in each AZ. Create a private route table for each AZ that forwards non-VPC traffic to the NAT gateway in its AZ.",
        "Create three NAT instances, one for each private subnet in each AZ. Create a private route table for each AZ that forwards non-VPC traffic to the NAT instance in its AZ.",
        "Create a second internet gateway on one of the private subnets. Update the route table for the private subnets that forward non-VPC traffic to the private internet gateway.",
        "Create an egress-only internet gateway on one of the public subnets. Update the route table for the private subnets that forward non-VPC traffic to the egress- only internet gateway."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create three NAT gateways, one for each public subnet in each AZ. Create a private route table for each AZ that forwards non-VPC traffic to the NAT gateway in its AZ."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "239",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "As part of budget planning, management wants a report of AWS billed items listed by user. The data will be used to create department budgets. A solutions architect needs to determine the most efficient way to obtain this report information. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Run a query with Amazon Athena to generate the report.",
        "Create a report in Cost Explorer and download the report.",
        "Access the bill details from the billing dashboard and download the bill.",
        "Modify a cost budget in AWS Budgets to alert with Amazon Simple Email Service (Amazon SES)."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a report in Cost Explorer and download the report."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "240",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company with facilities in North America, Europe, and Asia is designing new distributed application to optimize its global supply chain and manufacturing process. The orders booked on one continent should be visible to all Regions in a second or less. The database should be able to support failover with a short Recovery Time Objective (RTO). The uptime of the application is important to ensure that manufacturing is not impacted. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon DynamoDB global tables.",
        "Use Amazon Aurora Global Database.",
        "Use Amazon RDS for MySQL with a cross-Region read replica.",
        "Use Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL with a cross-Region read replica."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon Aurora Global Database."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "241",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A companys near-real-time streaming application is running on AWS. As the data is ingested, a job runs on the data and takes 30 minutes to complete. The workload frequently experiences high latency due to large amounts of incoming data. A solutions architect needs to design a scalable and serverless solution to enhance performance. Which combination of steps should the solutions architect take? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose to ingest the data.",
        "Use AWS Lambda with AWS Step Functions to process the data.",
        "Use AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS) to ingest the data.",
        "Use Amazon EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group to process the data.",
        "Use AWS Fargate with Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) to process the data."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose to ingest the data.",
        "Use AWS Fargate with Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) to process the data."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "242",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An application running on an Amazon EC2 instance needs to access an Amazon DynamoDB table. Both the EC2 instance and the DynamoDB table are in the same AWS account. A solutions architect must configure the necessary permissions. Which solution will allow least privilege access to the DynamoDB table from the EC2 instance?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an IAM role with the appropriate policy to allow access to the DynamoDB table. Create an instance profile to assign this IAM role to the EC2 instance.",
        "Create an IAM role with the appropriate policy to allow access to the DynamoDB table. Add the EC2 instance to the trust relationship policy document to allow it to assume the role.",
        "Create an IAM user with the appropriate policy to allow access to the DynamoDB table. Store the credentials in an Amazon S3 bucket and read them from within the application code directly.",
        "Create an IAM user with the appropriate policy to allow access to the DynamoDB table. Ensure that the application stores the IAM credentials securely on local storage and uses them to make the DynamoDB calls."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an IAM role with the appropriate policy to allow access to the DynamoDB table. Create an instance profile to assign this IAM role to the EC2 instance."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "243",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a solution that involves orchestrating a series of Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) task types running on Amazon EC2 instances that are part of an ECS cluster. The output and state data for all tasks needs to be stored. The amount of data output by each task is approximately 10 MB, and there could be hundreds of tasks running at a time. The system should be optimized for high-frequency reading and writing. As old outputs are archived and deleted, the storage size is not expected to exceed 1 TB. Which storage solution should the solutions architect recommend? ",
      "answers": [
        "An Amazon DynamoDB table accessible by all ECS cluster instances.",
        "An Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) with Provisioned Throughput mode.",
        "An Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) file system with Bursting Throughput mode.",
        "An Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume mounted to the ECS cluster instances."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["An Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) with Provisioned Throughput mode."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "244",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An online photo application lets users upload photos and perform image editing operations. The application offers two classes of service: free and paid. Photos submitted by paid users are processed before those submitted by free users. Photos are uploaded to Amazon S3 and the job information is sent to Amazon SQS. Which configuration should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Use one SQS FIFO queue. Assign a higher priority to the paid photos so they are processed first.",
        "Use two SQS FIFO queues: one for paid and one for free. Set the free queue to use short polling and the paid queue to use long polling.",
        "Use two SQS standard queues: one for paid and one for free. Configure Amazon EC2 instances to prioritize polling for the paid queue over the free queue.",
        "Use one SQS standard queue. Set the visibility timeout of the paid photos to zero. Configure Amazon EC2 instances to prioritize visibility settings so paid photos are processed first."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use two SQS standard queues: one for paid and one for free. Configure Amazon EC2 instances to prioritize polling for the paid queue over the free queue."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "245",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate its MySQL database from on premises to AWS. The company recently experienced a database outage that significantly impacted the business. To ensure this does not happen again, the company wants a reliable database solution on AWS that minimizes data loss and stores every transaction on at least two nodes. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an Amazon RDS DB instance with synchronous replication to three nodes in three Availability Zones.",
        "Create an Amazon RDS MySQL DB instance with Multi-AZ functionality enabled to synchronously replicate the data.",
        "Create an Amazon RDS MySQL DB instance and then create a read replica in a separate AWS Region that synchronously replicates the data.",
        "Create an Amazon EC2 instance with a MySQL engine installed that triggers an AWS Lambda function to synchronously replicate the data to an Amazon RDS MySQL DB instance."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Amazon RDS MySQL DB instance with Multi-AZ functionality enabled to synchronously replicate the data."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "246",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company stores user data in AWS. The data is used continuously with peak usage during business hours. Access patterns vary, with some data not being used for months at a time. A solutions architect must choose a cost-effective solution that maintains the highest level of durability while maintaining high availability. Which storage solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon S3 Standard",
        "Amazon S3 Intelligent-Tiering",
        "Amazon S3 Glacier Deep Archive",
        "Amazon S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon S3 Intelligent-Tiering"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "247",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company receives inconsistent service from its data center provider because the company is headquartered in an area affected by natural disasters. The company is not ready to fully migrate to the AWS Cloud, but it wants a failure environment on AWS in case the on-premises data center fails. The company runs web servers that connect to external vendors. The data available on AWS and on premises must be uniform. Which solution should a solutions architect recommend that has the LEAST amount of downtime?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure an Amazon Route 53 failover record. Run application servers on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer in an Auto Scaling group. Set up AWS Storage Gateway with stored volumes to back up data to Amazon S3.",
        "Configure an Amazon Route 53 failover record. Execute an AWS CloudFormation template from a script to create Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer. Set up AWS Storage Gateway with stored volumes to back up data to Amazon S3.",
        "Configure an Amazon Route 53 failover record. Set up an AWS Direct Connect connection between a VPC and the data center. Run application servers on Amazon EC2 in an Auto Scaling group. Run an AWS Lambda function to execute an AWS CloudFormation template to create an Application Load Balancer.",
        "Configure an Amazon Route 53 failover record. Run an AWS Lambda function to execute an AWS CloudFormation template to launch two Amazon EC2 instances. Set up AWS Storage Gateway with stored volumes to back up data to Amazon S3. Set up an AWS Direct Connect connection between a VPC and the data center."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure an Amazon Route 53 failover record. Run application servers on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer in an Auto Scaling group. Set up AWS Storage Gateway with stored volumes to back up data to Amazon S3."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "248",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has three VPCs named Development, Testing, and Production in the us-east-1 Region. The three VPCs need to be connected to an on-premises data center and are designed to be separate to maintain security and prevent any resource sharing. A solutions architect needs to find a scalable and secure solution. What should the solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an AWS Direct Connect connection and a VPN connection for each VPC to connect back to the data center.",
        "Create VPC peers from all the VPCs to the Production VPC. Use an AWS Direct Connect connection from the Production VPC back to the data center.",
        "Connect VPN connections from all the VPCs to a VPN in the Production VPC. Use a VPN connection from the Production VPC back to the data center.",
        "Create a new VPC called Network. Within the Network VPC, create an AWS Transit Gateway with an AWS Direct Connect connection back to the data center. Attach all the other VPCs to the Network VPC."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a new VPC called Network. Within the Network VPC, create an AWS Transit Gateway with an AWS Direct Connect connection back to the data center. Attach all the other VPCs to the Network VPC."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "249",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What should a solutions architect do to ensure that all objects uploaded to an Amazon S3 bucket are encrypted? ",
      "answers": [
        "Update the bucket policy to deny if the PutObject does not have an s3:x-amz-acl header set.",
        "Update the bucket policy to deny if the PutObject does not have an s3:x-amz-acl header set to private.",
        "Update the bucket policy to deny if the PutObject does not have an aws:SecureTransport header set to true.",
        "Update the bucket policy to deny if the PutObject does not have an x-amz-server-side-encryption header set."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Update the bucket policy to deny if the PutObject does not have an x-amz-server-side-encryption header set."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "250",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company needs a secure connection between its on-premises environment and AWS. This connection does not need high bandwidth and will handle a small amount of traffic. The connection should be set up quickly. What is the MOST cost-effective method to establish this type of connection? ",
      "answers": [
        "Implement a client VPN.",
        "Implement AWS Direct Connect.",
        "Implement a bastion host on Amazon EC2.",
        "Implement an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Implement an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "251",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company uses Application Load Balancers (ALBs) in different AWS Regions. The ALBs receive inconsistent traffic that can spike and drop throughout the year. The companys networking team needs to allow the IP addresses of the ALBs in the on-premises firewall to enable connectivity. Which solution is the MOST scalable with minimal configuration changes?",
      "answers": [
        "Write an AWS Lambda script to get the IP addresses of the ALBs in different Regions. Update the on-premises firewalls rule to allow the IP addresses of the ALBs.",
        "Migrate all ALBs in different Regions to the Network Load Balancer (NLBs). Update the on-premises firewalls rule to allow the Elastic IP addresses of all the NLBs.",
        "Launch AWS Global Accelerator. Register the ALBs in different Regions to the accelerator. Update the on-premises firewalls rule to allow static IP addresses associated with the accelerator.",
        "Launch a Network Load Balancer (NLB) in one Region. Register the private IP addresses of the ALBs in different Regions with the NLB. Update the on- premises firewalls rule to allow the Elastic IP address attached to the NLB."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Launch AWS Global Accelerator. Register the ALBs in different Regions to the accelerator. Update the on-premises firewalls rule to allow static IP addresses associated with the accelerator."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "252",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company runs a high performance computing (HPC) workload on AWS. The workload required low-latency network performance and high network throughput with tightly coupled node-to-node communication. The Amazon EC2 instances are properly sized for compute and storage capacity, and are launched using default options. What should a solutions architect propose to improve the performance of the workload?",
      "answers": [
        "Choose a cluster placement group while launching Amazon EC2 instances.",
        "Choose dedicated instance tenancy while launching Amazon EC2 instances.",
        "Choose an Elastic Inference accelerator while launching Amazon EC2 instances.",
        "Choose the required capacity reservation while launching Amazon EC2 instances."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Choose a cluster placement group while launching Amazon EC2 instances."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "253",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company uses a legacy on-premises analytics application that operates on gigabytes of .csv files and represents months of data. The legacy application cannot handle the growing size of .csv files. New .csv files are added daily from various data sources to a central on-premises storage location. The company wants to continue to support the legacy application while users learn AWS analytics services. To achieve this, a solutions architect wants to maintain two synchronized copies of all the .csv files on-premises and in Amazon S3. Which solution should the solutions architect recommend? ",
      "answers": [
        "Deploy AWS DataSync on-premises. Configure DataSync to continuously replicate the .csv files between the company's on-premises storage and the company's S3 bucket.",
        "Deploy an on-premises file gateway. Configure data sources to write the .csv files to the file gateway. Point the legacy analytics application to the file gateway. The file gateway should replicate the .csv files to Amazon S3.",
        "Deploy an on-premises volume gateway. Configure data sources to write the .csv files to the volume gateway. Point the legacy analytics application to the volume gateway. The volume gateway should replicate data to Amazon S3.",
        "Deploy AWS DataSync on-premises. Configure DataSync to continuously replicate the .csv files between on-premises and Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS). Enable replication from Amazon EFS to the company's S3 bucket."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy AWS DataSync on-premises. Configure DataSync to continuously replicate the .csv files between the company's on-premises storage and the company's S3 bucket."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "254",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has media and application files that need to be shared internally. Users currently are authenticated using Active Directory and access files from a Microsoft Windows platform. The chief executive officer wants to keep the same user permissions, but wants the company to improve the process as the company is reaching its storage capacity limit. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Set up a corporate Amazon S3 bucket and move all media and application files.",
        "Configure Amazon FSx for Windows File Server and move all the media and application files.",
        "Configure Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) and move all media and application files.",
        "Set up Amazon EC2 on Windows, attach multiple Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volumes, and move all media and application files."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure Amazon FSx for Windows File Server and move all the media and application files."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "255",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is deploying a web portal. The company wants to ensure that only the web portion of the application is publicly accessible. To accomplish this, the VPC was designed with two public subnets and two private subnets. The application will run on several Amazon EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group. SSL termination must be offloaded from the EC2 instances. What should a solutions architect do to ensure these requirements are met?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure the Network Load Balancer in the public subnets. Configure the Auto Scaling group in the private subnets and associate it with the Application Load Balancer.",
        "Configure the Network Load Balancer in the public subnets. Configure the Auto Scaling group in the public subnets and associate it with the Application Load Balancer.",
        "Configure the Application Load Balancer in the public subnets. Configure the Auto Scaling group in the private subnets and associate it with the Application Load Balancer.",
        "Configure the Application Load Balancer in the private subnets. Configure the Auto Scaling group in the private subnets and associate it with the Application Load Balancer."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure the Application Load Balancer in the public subnets. Configure the Auto Scaling group in the private subnets and associate it with the Application Load Balancer."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "256",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is experiencing growth as demand for its product has increased. The company's existing purchasing application is slow when traffic spikes. The application is a monolithic three-tier application that uses synchronous transactions and sometimes sees bottlenecks in the application tier. A solutions architect needs to design a solution that can meet required application response times while accounting for traffic volume spikes. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Vertically scale the application instance using a larger Amazon EC2 instance size.",
        "Scale the application's persistence layer horizontally by introducing Oracle RAC on AWS.",
        "Scale the web and application tiers horizontally using Auto Scaling groups and an Application Load Balancer.",
        "Decouple the application and data tiers using Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) with asynchronous AWS Lambda calls."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Scale the web and application tiers horizontally using Auto Scaling groups and an Application Load Balancer."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "257",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company hosts an application used to upload files to an Amazon S3 bucket. Once uploaded, the files are processed to extract metadata, which takes less than 5 seconds. The volume and frequency of the uploads varies from a few files each hour to hundreds of concurrent uploads. The company has asked a solutions architect to design a cost-effective architecture that will meet these requirements. What should the solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure AWS CloudTrail trails to log S3 API calls. Use AWS AppSync to process the files.",
        "Configure an object-created event notification within the S3 bucket to invoke an AWS Lambda function to process the files.",
        "Configure Amazon Kinesis Data Streams to process and send data to Amazon S3. Invoke an AWS Lambda function to process the files.",
        "Configure an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topic to process the files uploaded to Amazon S3. Invoke an AWS Lambda function to process the files."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure an object-created event notification within the S3 bucket to invoke an AWS Lambda function to process the files."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "258",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has copied 1 PB of data from a colocation facility to an Amazon S3 bucket in the us-east-1 Region using an AWS Direct Connect link. The company now wants to copy the data to another S3 bucket in the us-west-2 Region. The colocation facility does not allow the use of AWS Snowball. What should a solutions architect recommend to accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Order a Snowball Edge device to copy the data from one Region to another Region.",
        "Transfer contents from the source S3 bucket to a target S3 bucket using the S3 console.",
        "Use the aws S3 sync command to copy data from the source bucket to the destination bucket.",
        "Add a cross-Region replication configuration to copy objects across S3 buckets in different Regions."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use the aws S3 sync command to copy data from the source bucket to the destination bucket."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "259",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is using a fleet of Amazon EC2 instances to ingest data from on-premises data sources. The data is in JSON format and ingestion rates can be as high as 1 MB/s. When an EC2 instance is rebooted, the data in-flight is lost. The company's data science team wants to query ingested data in near-real time. Which solution provides near-real-time data querying that is scalable with minimal data loss?",
      "answers": [
        "Publish data to Amazon Kinesis Data Streams. Use Kinesis Data Analytics to query the data.",
        "Publish data to Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose with Amazon Redshift as the destination. Use Amazon Redshift to query the data.",
        "Store ingested data in an EC2 instance store. Publish data to Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose with Amazon S3 as the destination. Use Amazon Athena to query the data.",
        "Store ingested data in an Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume. Publish data to Amazon ElastiCache for Redis. Subscribe to the Redis channel to query the data."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Publish data to Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose with Amazon Redshift as the destination. Use Amazon Redshift to query the data."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "260",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is deploying a multi-instance application within AWS that requires minimal latency between the instances. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Use an Auto Scaling group with a cluster placement group.",
        "Use an Auto Scaling group with single Availability Zone in the same AWS Region.",
        "Use an Auto Scaling group with multiple Availability Zones in the same AWS Region.",
        "Use a Network Load Balancer with multiple Amazon EC2 Dedicated Hosts as the targets."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use an Auto Scaling group with a cluster placement group."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "261",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is developing a mobile game that streams score updates to a backend processor and then posts results on a leaderboard. A solutions architect needs to design a solution that can handle large traffic spikes, process the mobile game updates in order of receipt, and store the processed updates in a highly available database. The company also wants to minimize the management overhead required to maintain the solution. What should the solutions architect do to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Push score updates to Amazon Kinesis Data Streams. Process the updates in Kinesis Data Streams with AWS Lambda. Store the processed updates in Amazon DynamoDB.",
        "Push score updates to Amazon Kinesis Data Streams. Process the updates with a fleet of Amazon EC2 instances set up for Auto Scaling. Store the processed updates in Amazon Redshift.",
        "Push score updates to an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topic. Subscribe an AWS Lambda function to the SNS topic to process the updates. Store the processed updates in a SQL database running on Amazon EC2.",
        "Push score updates to an Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) queue. Use a fleet of Amazon EC2 instances with Auto Scaling to process the updates in the SQS queue. Store the processed updates in an Amazon RDS Multi-AZ DB instance."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Push score updates to Amazon Kinesis Data Streams. Process the updates in Kinesis Data Streams with AWS Lambda. Store the processed updates in Amazon DynamoDB."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "262",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is building a document storage application on AWS. The application runs on Amazon EC2 instances in multiple Availability Zones. The company requires the document store to be highly available. The documents need to be returned immediately when requested. The lead engineer has configured the application to use Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) to store the documents, but is willing to consider other options to meet the availability requirement. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Snapshot the EBS volumes regularly and build new volumes using those snapshots in additional Availability Zones.",
        "Use Amazon EBS for the EC2 instance root volumes. Configure the application to build the document store on Amazon S3.",
        "Use Amazon EBS for the EC2 instance root volumes. Configure the application to build the document store on Amazon S3 Glacier.",
        "Use at least three Provisioned IOPS EBS volumes for EC2 instances. Mount the volumes to the EC2 instances in a RAID 5 configuration."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon EBS for the EC2 instance root volumes. Configure the application to build the document store on Amazon S3."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "263",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a security solution for a company that wants to provide developers with individual AWS accounts through AWS Organizations, while also maintaining standard security controls. Because the individual developers will have AWS account root user-level access to their own accounts, the solutions architect wants to ensure that the mandatory AWS CloudTrail configuration that is applied to new developer accounts is not modified. Which action meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an IAM policy that prohibits changes to CloudTrail, and attach it to the root user.",
        "Create a new trail in CloudTrail from within the developer accounts with the organization trails option enabled.",
        "Create a service control policy (SCP) the prohibits changes to CloudTrail, and attach it the developer accounts.",
        "Create a service-linked role for CloudTrail with a policy condition that allows changes only from an Amazon Resource Name (ARN) in the master account."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a service control policy (SCP) the prohibits changes to CloudTrail, and attach it the developer accounts."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "264",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company wants to share forensic accounting data that is stored in an Amazon RDS DB instance with an external auditor. The auditor has its own AWS account and requires its own copy of the database. How should the company securely share the database with the auditor?",
      "answers": [
        "Create a read replica of the database and configure IAM standard database authentication to grant the auditor access.",
        "Copy a snapshot of the database to Amazon S3 and assign an IAM role to the auditor to grant access to the object in that bucket.",
        "Export the database contents to text files, store the files in Amazon S3, and create a new IAM user for the auditor with access to that bucket.",
        "Make an encrypted snapshot of the database, share the snapshot, and allow access to the AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) encryption key."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Make an encrypted snapshot of the database, share the snapshot, and allow access to the AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) encryption key."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "265",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has an automobile sales website that stores its listings in a database on Amazon RDS. When an automobile is sold, the listing needs to be removed from the website and the data must be sent to multiple target systems. Which design should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an AWS Lambda function triggered when the database on Amazon RDS is updated to send the information to an Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) queue for the targets to consume.",
        "Create an AWS Lambda function triggered when the database on Amazon RDS is updated to send the information to an Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) FIFO queue for the targets to consume.",
        "Subscribe to an RDS event notification and send an Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) queue fanned out to multiple Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topics. Use AWS Lambda functions to update the targets.",
        "Subscribe to an RDS event notification and send an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topic fanned out to multiple Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) queues. Use AWS Lambda functions to update the targets."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Subscribe to an RDS event notification and send an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topic fanned out to multiple Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) queues. Use AWS Lambda functions to update the targets."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "266",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is building a media sharing application and decides to use Amazon S3 for storage. When a media file is uploaded, the company starts a multi-step process to create thumbnails, identify objects in the images, transcode videos into standard formats and resolutions, and extract and store the metadata to an Amazon DynamoDB table. The metadata is used for searching and navigation. The amount of traffic is variable. The solution must be able to scale to handle spikes in load without unnecessary expenses. What should a solutions architect recommend to support this workload?",
      "answers": [
        "Build the processing into the website or mobile app used to upload the content to Amazon S3. Save the required data to the DynamoDB table when the objects are uploaded.",
        "Trigger AWS Step Functions when an object is stored in the S3 bucket. Have the Step Functions perform the steps needed to process the object and then write the metadata to the DynamoDB table.",
        "Trigger an AWS Lambda function when an object is stored in the S3 bucket. Have the Lambda function start AWS Batch to perform the steps to process the object. Place the object data in the DynamoDB table when complete.",
        "Trigger an AWS Lambda function to store an initial entry in the DynamoDB table when an object is uploaded to Amazon S3. Use a program running on an Amazon EC2 instance in an Auto Scaling group to poll the index for unprocessed items, and use the program to perform the processing."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Trigger an AWS Lambda function when an object is stored in the S3 bucket. Have the Lambda function start AWS Batch to perform the steps to process the object. Place the object data in the DynamoDB table when complete."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "267",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company provides an API to its users that automates inquiries for tax computations based on item prices. The company experiences a larger number of inquiries during the holiday season only that cause slower response times. A solutions architect needs to design a solution that is scalable and elastic. What should the solutions architect do to accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Provide an API hosted on an Amazon EC2 instance. The EC2 instance performs the required computations when the API request is made.",
        "Design a REST API using Amazon API Gateway that accepts the item names. API Gateway passes item names to AWS Lambda for tax computations.",
        "Create an Application Load Balancer that has two Amazon EC2 instances behind it. The EC2 instances will compute the tax on the received item names.",
        "Design a REST API using Amazon API Gateway that connects with an API hosted on an Amazon EC2 instance. API Gateway accepts and passes the item names to the EC2 instance for tax computations."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Design a REST API using Amazon API Gateway that accepts the item names. API Gateway passes item names to AWS Lambda for tax computations."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "268",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "An application is running on an Amazon EC2 instance and must have millisecond latency when running the workload. The application makes many small reads and writes to the file system, but the file system itself is small. Which Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume type should a solutions architect attach to their EC2 instance? ",
      "answers": [
        "Cold HDD (sc1)",
        "General Purpose SSD (gp2)",
        "Provisioned IOPS SSD (io1)",
        "Throughput Optimized HDD (st1)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["General Purpose SSD (gp2)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "269",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a multi-Region disaster recovery solution for an application that will provide public API access. The application will use Amazon EC2 instances with a userdata script to load application code and an Amazon RDS for MySQL database. The Recovery Time Objective (RTO) is 3 hours and the Recovery Point Objective (RPO) is 24 hours. Which architecture would meet these requirements at the LOWEST cost?",
      "answers": [
        "Use an Application Load Balancer for Region failover. Deploy new EC2 instances with the userdata script. Deploy separate RDS instances in each Region.",
        "Use Amazon Route 53 for Region failover. Deploy new EC2 instances with the userdata script. Create a read replica of the RDS instance in a backup Region.",
        "Use Amazon API Gateway for the public APIs and Region failover. Deploy new EC2 instances with the userdata script. Create a MySQL read replica of the RDS instance in a backup Region.",
        "Use Amazon Route 53 for Region failover. Deploy new EC2 instances with the userdata script for APIs, and create a snapshot of the RDS instance daily for a backup. Replicate the snapshot to a backup Region."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon Route 53 for Region failover. Deploy new EC2 instances with the userdata script for APIs, and create a snapshot of the RDS instance daily for a backup. Replicate the snapshot to a backup Region."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "270",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect needs to ensure that all Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volumes restored from unencrypted EBC snapshots are encrypted. What should the solutions architect do to accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Enable EBS encryption by default for the AWS Region.",
        "Enable EBS encryption by default for the specific volumes.",
        "Create a new volume and specify the symmetric customer master key (CMK) to use for encryption.",
        "Create a new volume and specify the asymmetric customer master key (CMK) to use for encryption."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a new volume and specify the symmetric customer master key (CMK) to use for encryption."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "271",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company runs a static website through its on-premises data center. The company has multiple servers that handle all of its traffic, but on busy days, services are interrupted and the website becomes unavailable. The company wants to expand its presence globally and plans to triple its website traffic. What should a solutions architect recommend to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Migrate the website content to Amazon S3 and host the website on Amazon CloudFront.",
        "Migrate the website content to Amazon EC2 instances with public Elastic IP addresses in multiple AWS Regions.",
        "Migrate the website content to Amazon EC2 instances and vertically scale as the load increases.",
        "Use Amazon Route 53 to distribute the loads across multiple Amazon CloudFront distributions for each AWS Region that exists globally."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Migrate the website content to Amazon S3 and host the website on Amazon CloudFront."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "272",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a highly dynamic batch processing job that uses many Amazon EC2 instances to complete it. The job is stateless in nature, can be started and stopped at any given time with no negative impact, and typically takes upwards of 60 minutes total to complete. The company has asked a solutions architect to design a scalable and cost-effective solution that meets the requirements of the job. What should the solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Implement EC2 Spot Instances.",
        "Purchase EC2 Reserved Instances.",
        "Implement EC2 On-Demand Instances.",
        "Implement the processing on AWS Lambda."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Implement EC2 Spot Instances."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "273",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is hosting its static website in an Amazon S3 bucket, which is the origin for Amazon CloudFront. The company has users in the United States, Canada, and Europe and wants to reduce costs. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Adjust the CloudFront caching time to live (TTL) from the default to a longer timeframe.",
        "Implement CloudFront events with Lambda@Edge to run the website's data processing.",
        "Modify the CloudFront price class to include only the locations of the countries that are served.",
        "Implement a CloudFront Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) certificate to push security closer to the locations of the countries that are served."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Modify the CloudFront price class to include only the locations of the countries that are served."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "274",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is planning to migrate a commercial off-the-shelf application from its on-premises data center to AWS. The software has a software licensing model using sockets and cores with predictable capacity and uptime requirements. The company wants to use its existing licenses, which were purchased earlier this year. Which Amazon EC2 pricing option is the MOST cost-effective?",
      "answers": [
        "Dedicated Reserved Hosts",
        "Dedicated On-Demand Hosts",
        "Dedicated Reserved Instances",
        "Dedicated On-Demand Instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Dedicated Reserved Hosts"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "275",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is designing a website that uses an Amazon S3 bucket to store static images. The company wants all future requests to have faster response times while reducing both latency and cost. Which service configuration should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Deploy a NAT server in front of Amazon S3.",
        "Deploy Amazon CloudFront in front of Amazon S3.",
        "Deploy a Network Load Balancer in front of Amazon S3.",
        "Configure Auto Scaling to automatically adjust the capacity of the website."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy Amazon CloudFront in front of Amazon S3."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "276",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has an on-premises MySQL database used by the global sales team with infrequent access patterns. The sales team requires the database to have minimal downtime. A database administrator wants to migrate this database to AWS without selecting a particular instance type in anticipation of more users in the future. Which service should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Aurora MySQL",
        "Amazon Aurora Serverless for MySQL",
        "Amazon Redshift Spectrum",
        "Amazon RDS for MySQL"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Aurora Serverless for MySQL"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "277",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company needs to comply with a regulatory requirement that states all emails must be stored and archived externally for 7 years. An administrator has created compressed email files on premises and wants a managed service to transfer the files to AWS storage. Which managed service should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
        "Amazon S3 Glacier",
        "AWS Backup",
        "AWS Storage Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Storage Gateway"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "278",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company that hosts its web application on AWS wants to ensure all Amazon EC2 instances, Amazon RDS DB instances, and Amazon Redshift clusters are configured with tags. The company wants to minimize the effort of configuring and operating this check. What should a solutions architect do to accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Use AWS Config rules to define and detect resources that are not properly tagged.",
        "Use Cost Explorer to display resources that are not properly tagged. Tag those resources manually.",
        "Write API calls to check all resources for proper tag allocation. Periodically run the code on an EC2 instance.",
        "Write API calls to check all resources for proper tag allocation. Schedule an AWS Lambda function through Amazon CloudWatch to periodically run the code."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use AWS Config rules to define and detect resources that are not properly tagged."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "279",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a live chat application running on its on-premises servers that use WebSockets. The company wants to migrate the application to AWS. Application traffic is inconsistent, and the company expects there to be more traffic with sharp spikes in the future. The company wants a highly scalable solution with no server maintenance nor advanced capacity planning. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon API Gateway and AWS Lambda with an Amazon DynamoDB table as the data store. Configure the DynamoDB table for provisioned capacity.",
        "Use Amazon API Gateway and AWS Lambda with an Amazon DynamoDB table as the data store. Configure the DynamoDB table for on-demand capacity.",
        "Run Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer in an Auto Scaling group with an Amazon DynamoDB table as the data store. Configure the DynamoDB table for on-demand capacity.",
        "Run Amazon EC2 instances behind a Network Load Balancer in an Auto Scaling group with an Amazon DynamoDB table as the data store. Configure the DynamoDB table for provisioned capacity."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon API Gateway and AWS Lambda with an Amazon DynamoDB table as the data store. Configure the DynamoDB table for on-demand capacity."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "280",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A company hosts its static website content from an Amazon S3 bucket in the us-east-1 Region. Content is made available through an Amazon CloudFront origin pointing to that bucket. Cross-Region replication is set to create a second copy of the bucket in the ap-southeast-1 Region. Management wants a solution that provides greater availability for the website. Which combination of actions should a solutions architect take to increase availability? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Add both buckets to the CloudFront origin.",
        "Configure failover routing in Amazon Route 53.",
        "Create a record in Amazon Route 53 pointing to the replica bucket.",
        "Create an additional CloudFront origin pointing to the ap-southeast-1 bucket.",
        "Set up a CloudFront origin group with the us-east-1 bucket as the primary and the ap-southeast-1 bucket as the secondary."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an additional CloudFront origin pointing to the ap-southeast-1 bucket.",
        "Set up a CloudFront origin group with the us-east-1 bucket as the primary and the ap-southeast-1 bucket as the secondary."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "281",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company hosts a training site on a fleet of Amazon EC2 instances. The company anticipates that its new course, which consists of dozens of training videos on the site, will be extremely popular when it is released in 1 week.\nWhat should a solutions architect do to minimize the anticipated server load?",
      "answers": [
        "Store the videos in Amazon ElastiCache for Redis. Update the web servers to serve the videos using the ElastiCache API.",
        "Store the videos in Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS). Create a user data script for the web servers to mount the EFS volume.",
        "Store the videos in an Amazon S3 bucket. Create an Amazon CloudFront distribution with an origin access identity (OAI) of that S3 bucket. Restrict Amazon S3 access to the OAI.",
        "Store the videos in an Amazon S3 bucket. Create an AWS Storage Gateway file gateway to access the S3 bucket. Create a user data script for the web servers to mount the file gateway."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Store the videos in an Amazon S3 bucket. Create an Amazon CloudFront distribution with an origin access identity (OAI) of that S3 bucket. Restrict Amazon S3 access to the OAI."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "282",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company runs a production application on a fleet of Amazon EC2 instances. The application reads the data from an Amazon SQS queue and processes the messages in parallel. The message volume is unpredictable and often has intermittent traffic. This application should continually process messages without any downtime. Which solution meets these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Spot Instances exclusively to handle the maximum capacity required.",
        "Use Reserved Instances exclusively to handle the maximum capacity required.",
        "Use Reserved Instances for the baseline capacity and use Spot Instances to handle additional capacity.",
        "Use Reserved Instances for the baseline capacity and use On-Demand Instances to handle additional capacity."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Reserved Instances for the baseline capacity and use On-Demand Instances to handle additional capacity."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "283",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a hybrid application hosted on multiple on-premises servers with static IP addresses. There is already a VPN that provides connectivity between the VPC and the on-premises network. The company wants to distribute TCP traffic across the on-premises servers for internet users. What should a solutions architect recommend to provide a highly available and scalable solution?",
      "answers": [
        "Launch an internet-facing Network Load Balancer (NLB) and register on-premises IP addresses with the NLB.",
        "Launch an internet-facing Application Load Balancer (ALB) and register on-premises IP addresses with the ALB.",
        "Launch an Amazon EC2 instance, attach an Elastic IP address, and distribute traffic to the on-premises servers.",
        "Launch an Amazon EC2 instance with public IP addresses in an Auto Scaling group and distribute traffic to the on-premises servers."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Launch an internet-facing Network Load Balancer (NLB) and register on-premises IP addresses with the NLB."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "284",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Management has decided to deploy all AWS VPCs with IPv6 enabled. After some time, a solutions architect tries to launch a new instance and receives an error stating that there is not enough IP address space available in the subnet. What should the solutions architect do to fix this?",
      "answers": [
        "Check to make sure that only IPv6 was used during the VPC creation.",
        "Create a new IPv4 subnet with a larger range, and then launch the instance.",
        "Create a new IPv6-only subnet with a large range, and then launch the instance.",
        "Disable the IPv4 subnet and migrate all instances to IPv6 only. Once that is complete, launch the instance."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a new IPv4 subnet with a larger range, and then launch the instance."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "285",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has a build server that is in an Auto Scaling group and often has multiple Linux instances running. The build server requires consistent and mountable shared NFS storage for jobs and configurations. Which storage option should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Amazon S3",
        "Amazon FSx",
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)",
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "286",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect must migrate a Windows internet information Services (IIS) web application to AWS. The application currently relies on a file share hosted in the users on-premises network-attached storage (NAS). The solutions architected has proposed migrating the IIS web servers to Amazon EC2 instances in multiple Availability Zones that are connected to the storage solution, and configuring an Elastic Load Balancer attached to the instances. Which replacement to the on-premises file share is MOST resilient and durable?",
      "answers": [
        "Migrate the file Share to Amazon RDS.",
        "Migrate the file Share to AWS Storage Gateway",
        "Migrate the file Share to Amazon FSx for Windows File Server.",
        "Migrate the file share to Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Migrate the file Share to Amazon FSx for Windows File Server."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "287",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A companys website hosted on Amazon EC2 instances processes classified data stored in Amazon S3. Due to security concerns, the company requires a private and secure connection between its EC2 resources and Amazon S3. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Set up S3 bucket policies to allow access from a VPC endpoint.",
        "Set up an IAM policy to grant read-write access to the S3 bucket.",
        "Set up a NAT gateway to access resources outside the private subnet.",
        "Set up an access key ID and a secret access key to access the S3 bucket."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Set up S3 bucket policies to allow access from a VPC endpoint."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "288",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has two applications: a sender application that sends messages with payloads to be processed and a processing application intended to receive messages with payloads. The company wants to implement an AWS service to handle messages between the two applications. The sender application can send about 1,000 messages each hour. The messages may take up to 2 days to be processed. If the messages fail to process, they must be retained so that they do not impact the processing of any remaining messages. Which solution meets these requirements and is the MOST operationally efficient?",
      "answers": [
        "Set up an Amazon EC2 instance running a Redis database. Configure both applications to use the instance. Store, process, and delete the messages, respectively.",
        "Use an Amazon Kinesis data stream to receive the messages from the sender application. Integrate the processing application with the Kinesis Client Library (KCL).",
        "Integrate the sender and processor applications with an Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) queue. Configure a dead-letter queue to collect the messages that failed to process.",
        "Subscribe the processing application to an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topic to receive notifications to process. Integrate the sender application to write to the SNS topic."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Integrate the sender and processor applications with an Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) queue. Configure a dead-letter queue to collect the messages that failed to process."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "289",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has an application that is hosted on Amazon EC2 instances in two private subnets. A solutions architect must make the application available on the public internet with the least amount of administrative effort. What should the solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Create a load balancer and associate two public subnets from the same Availability Zones as the private instances. Add the private instances to the load balancer.",
        "Create a load balancer and associate two private subnets from the same Availability Zones as the private instances. Add the private instances to the load balancer.",
        "Create an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) of the instances in the private subnet and restore in the public subnet. Create a load balancer and associate two public subnets from the same Availability Zones as the public instances.",
        "Create an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) of the instances in the private subnet and restore in the public subnet. Create a load balancer and associate two private subnets from the same Availability Zones as the public instances."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a load balancer and associate two public subnets from the same Availability Zones as the private instances. Add the private instances to the load balancer."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "290",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A user wants to list the IAM role that is attached to their Amazon EC2 instance. The user has login access to the EC2 instance but does not have IAM permissions. What should a solutions architect do to retrieve this information?",
      "answers": [
        "Run the following EC2 command: curl http://169.254.169.254/latest/meta-data/iam/info",
        "Run the following EC2 command: curl http://169.254.169.254/latest/user-data/iam/info",
        "Run the following EC2 command: http://169.254.169.254/latest/dynamic/instance-identity/",
        "Run the following AWS CLI command: aws iam get-instance-profile --instance-profile-name ExampleInstanceProfile"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Run the following EC2 command: curl http://169.254.169.254/latest/meta-data/iam/info"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "291",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A software vendor is deploying a new software-as-a-service (SaaS) solution that will be utilized by many AWS users. The service is hosted in a VPC behind a Network Load Balancer. The software vendor wants to provide access to this service to users with the least amount of administrative overhead and without exposing the service to the public internet. What should a solutions architect do to accomplish this goal?",
      "answers": [
        "Create a peering VPC connection from each users VPC to the software vendors VPC.",
        "Deploy a transit VPC in the software vendors AWS account. Create a VPN connection with each user account.",
        "Connect the service in the VPC with an AWS Private Link endpoint. Have users subscribe to the endpoint.",
        "Deploy a transit VPC in the software vendors AWS account. Create an AWS Direct Connect connection with each user account."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Connect the service in the VPC with an AWS Private Link endpoint. Have users subscribe to the endpoint."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "292",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company serves a multilingual website from a fleet of Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). This architecture is currently running in the us-west-1 Region but is exhibiting high request latency for users located in other parts of the world. The website needs to serve requests quickly and efficiently regardless of a users location. However, the company does not want to recreate the existing architecture across multiple Regions. How should a solutions architect accomplish this?",
      "answers": [
        "Replace the existing architecture with a website served from an Amazon S3 bucket. Configure an Amazon CloudFront distribution with the S3 bucket as the origin. ",
        "Configure an Amazon CloudFront distribution with the ALB as the origin. Set the cache behavior settings to only cache based on the Accept-Language request header.",
        "Set up Amazon API Gateway with the ALB as an integration. Configure API Gateway to use an HTTP integration type. Set up an API Gateway stage to enable the API cache.",
        "Launch an EC2 instance in each additional Region and configure NGINX to act as a cache server for that Region. Put all the instances plus the ALB behind an Amazon Route 53 record set with a geolocation routing policy."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure an Amazon CloudFront distribution with the ALB as the origin. Set the cache behavior settings to only cache based on the Accept-Language request header."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "293",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company wants to move a multi-tiered application from on premises to the AWS Cloud to improve the applications performance. The application consists of application tiers that communicate with each other by way of RESTful services. Transactions are dropped when one tier becomes overloaded. A solutions architect must design a solution that resolves these issues and modernizes the application. Which solution meets these requirements and is the MOST operationally efficient?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon API Gateway and direct transactions to the AWS Lambda functions as the application layer. Use Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) as the communication layer between application services.",
        "Use Amazon CloudWatch metrics to analyze the application performance history to determine the servers peak utilization during the performance failures. Increase the size of the application servers Amazon EC2 instances to meet the peak requirements.",
        "Use Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) to handle the messaging between application servers running on Amazon EC2 in an Auto Scaling group. Use Amazon CloudWatch to monitor the SNS queue length and scale up and down as required.",
        "Use Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) to handle the messaging between application servers running on Amazon EC2 in an Auto Scaling group. Use Amazon CloudWatch to monitor the SQS queue length and scale up when communication failures are detected."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon API Gateway and direct transactions to the AWS Lambda functions as the application layer. Use Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) as the communication layer between application services."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "294",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect needs to design a resilient solution for Windows users home directories. The solution must provide fault tolerance, file-level backup and recovery, and access control, based upon the companys Active Directory. Which storage solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure Amazon S3 to store the users home directories. Join Amazon S3 to Active Directory.",
        "Configure a Multi-AZ file system with Amazon FSx for Windows File Server. Join Amazon FSx to Active Directory.",
        "Configure Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) for the users home directories. Configure AWS Single Sign-On with Active Directory.",
        "Configure Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EFS) to store the users home directories. Configure AWS Single Sign-On with Active Directory."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure a Multi-AZ file system with Amazon FSx for Windows File Server. Join Amazon FSx to Active Directory."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "295",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is building an application on Amazon EC2 instances that generates temporary transactional data. The application requires access to data storage that can provide configurable and consistent IOPS. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Provision an EC2 instance with a Throughput Optimized HDD (st1) root volume and a Cold HDD (sc1) data volume.",
        "Provision an EC2 instance with a Throughput Optimized HDD (st1) volume that will serve as the root and data volume.",
        "Provision an EC2 instance with a General Purpose SSD (gp2) root volume and Provisioned IOPS SSD (io1) data volume.",
        "Provision an EC2 instance with a General Purpose SSD (gp2) root volume. Configure the application to store its data in an Amazon S3 bucket."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Provision an EC2 instance with a General Purpose SSD (gp2) root volume and Provisioned IOPS SSD (io1) data volume."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "296",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is launching a new application deployed on an Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) cluster and is using the Fargate launch type for ECS tasks. The company is monitoring CPU and memory usage because it is expecting high traffic to the application upon its launch. However, the company wants to reduce costs when utilization decreases. What should a solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Use Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling to scale at certain periods based on previous traffic patterns.",
        "Use an AWS Lambda function to scale Amazon ECS based on metric breaches that trigger an Amazon CloudWatch alarm. ",
        "Use Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling with simple scaling policies to scale when ECS metric breaches trigger an Amazon CloudWatch alarm.",
        "Use AWS Application Auto Scaling with target tracking policies to scale when ECS metric breaches trigger an Amazon CloudWatch alarm."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use AWS Application Auto Scaling with target tracking policies to scale when ECS metric breaches trigger an Amazon CloudWatch alarm."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "297",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is moving its on-premises applications to Amazon EC2 instances. However, as a result of fluctuating compute requirements, the EC2 instances must always be ready to use between 8 AM and 5 PM in specific Availability Zones. Which EC2 instances should the company choose to run the applications?",
      "answers": [
        "Scheduled Reserved Instances",
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Spot Instances as part of a Spot Fleet",
        "EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Scheduled Reserved Instances"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "298",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company owns an asynchronous API that is used to ingest user requests and, based on the request type, dispatch requests to the appropriate microservice for processing. The company is using Amazon API Gateway to deploy the API front end, and an AWS Lambda function that invokes Amazon DynamoDB to store user requests before dispatching them to the processing microservices. The company provisioned as much DynamoDB throughput as its budget allows, but the company is still experiencing availability issues and is losing user requests. What should a solutions architect do to address this issue without impacting existing users?",
      "answers": [
        "Add throttling on the API Gateway with server-side throttling limits.",
        "Use DynamoDB Accelerator (DAX) and Lambda to buffer writes to DynamoDB.",
        "Create a secondary index in DynamoDB for the table with the user requests.",
        "Use the Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) queue and Lambda to buffer writes to DynamoDB."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use the Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) queue and Lambda to buffer writes to DynamoDB."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "299",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company hosts historical weather records in Amazon S3. The records are downloaded from the companys website by a way of a URL that resolves to a domain name. Users all over the world access this content through subscriptions. A third-party provider hosts the companys root domain name, but the company recently migrated some of its services to Amazon Route 53. The company wants to consolidate contracts, reduce latency for users, and reduce costs related to serving the application to subscribers. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Create a web distribution on Amazon CloudFront to serve the S3 content for the application. Create a CNAME record in a Route 53 hosted zone that points to the CloudFront distribution, resolving to the applications URL domain name.",
        "Create a web distribution on Amazon CloudFront to serve the S3 content for the application. Create an ALIAS record in the Amazon Route 53 hosted zone that points to the CloudFront distribution, resolving to the applications URL domain name.",
        "Create an A record in a Route 53 hosted zone for the application. Create a Route 53 traffic policy for the web application, and configure a geolocation rule. Configure health checks to check the health of the endpoint and route DNS queries to other endpoints if an endpoint is unhealthy.",
        "Create an A record in a Route 53 hosted zone for the application. Create a Route 53 traffic policy for the web application, and configure a geoproximity rule. Configure health checks to check the health of the endpoint and route DNS queries to other endpoints if an endpoint is unhealthy."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a web distribution on Amazon CloudFront to serve the S3 content for the application. Create an ALIAS record in the Amazon Route 53 hosted zone that points to the CloudFront distribution, resolving to the applications URL domain name."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "300",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is creating a new VPC design. There are two public subnets for the load balancer, two private subnets for web servers, and two private subnets for MySQL. The web servers use only HTTPS. The solutions architect has already created a security group for the load balancer allowing port 443 from 0.0.0.0/0. Company policy requires that each resource has the least access required to still be able to perform its tasks. Which additional configuration strategy should the solutions architect use to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Create a security group for the web servers and allow port 443 from 0.0.0.0/0. Create a security group for the MySQL servers and allow port 3306 from the web servers security group.",
        "Create a network ACL for the web servers and allow port 443 from 0.0.0.0/0. Create a network ACL for the MySQL servers and allow port 3306 from the web servers security group.",
        "Create a security group for the web servers and allow port 443 from the load balancer. Create a security group for the MySQL servers and allow port 3306 from the web servers security group.",
        "Create a network ACL for the web servers and allow port 443 from the load balancer. Create a network ACL for the MySQL servers and allow port 3306 from the web servers security group."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create a security group for the web servers and allow port 443 from the load balancer. Create a security group for the MySQL servers and allow port 3306 from the web servers security group."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "301",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company runs an application on an Amazon EC2 instance backed by Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS). The instance needs to be available for 12 hours daily. The company wants to save costs by making the instance unavailable outside the window required for the application. However, the contents of the instances memory must be preserved whenever the instance is unavailable. What should a solutions architect do to meet this requirement?",
      "answers": [
        "Stop the instance outside the applications availability window. Start up the instance again when required.",
        "Hibernate the instance outside the applications availability window. Start up the instance again when required.",
        "Use Auto Scaling to scale down the instance outside the applications availability window. Scale up the instance when required.",
        "Terminate the instance outside the applications availability window. Launch the instance by using a preconfigured Amazon Machine Image (AMI) when required."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Hibernate the instance outside the applications availability window. Start up the instance again when required."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "302",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a solution that requires frequent updates to a website that is hosted on Amazon S3 with versioning enabled. For compliance reasons, the older versions of the objects will not be accessed frequently and will need to be deleted after 2 years. What should the solutions architect recommend to meet these requirements at the LOWEST cost?",
      "answers": [
        "Use S3 batch operations to replace object tags. Expire the objects based on the modified tags.",
        "Configure an S3 Lifecycle policy to transition older versions of objects to S3 Glacier. Expire the objects after 2 years.",
        "Enable S3 Event Notifications on the bucket that sends older objects to the Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) queue for further processing.",
        "Replicate older object versions to a new bucket. Use an S3 Lifecycle policy to expire the objects in the new bucket after 2 years."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure an S3 Lifecycle policy to transition older versions of objects to S3 Glacier. Expire the objects after 2 years."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "303",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A business application is hosted on Amazon EC2 and uses Amazon S3 for encrypted object storage. The chief information security officer has directed that no application traffic between the two services should traverse the public internet. Which capability should the solutions architect use to meet the compliance requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS)",
        "VPC endpoint",
        "Private subnet",
        "Virtual private gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["VPC endpoint"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "304",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company hosts its application in the AWS Cloud. The application runs on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Elastic Load Balancer in an Auto Scaling group and with an Amazon DynamoDB table. The company wants to ensure the application can be made available in another AWS Region with minimal downtime. What should a solutions architect do to meet these requirements with the LEAST amount of downtime?",
      "answers": [
        "Create an Auto Scaling group and a load balancer in the disaster recovery Region. Configure the DynamoDB table as a global table. Configure DNS failover to point to the new disaster recovery Regions load balancer.",
        "Create an AWS CloudFormation template to create EC2 instances, load balancers, and DynamoDB tables to be executed when needed. Configure DNS failover to point to the new disaster recovery Regions load balancer.",
        "Create an AWS CloudFormation template to create EC2 instances and a load balancer to be executed when needed. Configure the DynamoDB table as a global table. Configure DNS failover to point to the new disaster recovery Regions load balancer.",
        "Create an Auto Scaling group and load balancer in the disaster recovery Region. Configure the DynamoDB table as a global table. Create an Amazon CloudWatch alarm to trigger and AWS Lambda function that updates Amazon Route 53 pointing to the disaster recovery load balancer."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Auto Scaling group and a load balancer in the disaster recovery Region. Configure the DynamoDB table as a global table. Configure DNS failover to point to the new disaster recovery Regions load balancer."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "305",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing a new API using Amazon API Gateway that will receive requests from users. The volume of requests is highly variable; several hours can pass without receiving a single request. The data processing will take place asynchronously, but should be completed within a few seconds after a request is made. Which compute service should the solutions architect have the API invoke to deliver the requirements at the lowest cost?",
      "answers": [
        "An AWS Glue job",
        "An AWS Lambda function",
        "A containerized service hosted in Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS)",
        "A containerized service hosted in Amazon ECS with Amazon EC2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["An AWS Lambda function"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "306",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company uses Amazon S3 to store its confidential audit documents. The S3 bucket uses bucket policies to restrict access to audit team IAM user credentials according to the principle of least privilege. Company managers are worried about accidental deletion of documents in the S3 bucket and want a more secure solution. What should a solutions architect do to secure the audit documents?",
      "answers": [
        "Enable the versioning and MFA Delete features on the S3 bucket.",
        "Enable multi-factor authentication (MFA) on the IAM user credentials for each audit team IAM user account.",
        "Add an S3 Lifecycle policy to the audit teams IAM user accounts to deny the s3:DeleteObject action during audit dates.",
        "Use AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) to encrypt the S3 bucket and restrict audit team IAM user accounts from accessing the KMS key."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Enable the versioning and MFA Delete features on the S3 bucket."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "307",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is hosting 60 TB of production-level data in an Amazon S3 bucket. A solution architect needs to bring that data on premises for quarterly audit requirements. This export of data must be encrypted while in transit. The company has low network bandwidth in place between AWS and its on-premises data center. What should the solutions architect do to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Deploy AWS Migration Hub with 90-day replication windows for data transfer.",
        "Deploy an AWS Storage Gateway volume gateway on AWS. Enable a 90-day replication window to transfer the data.",
        "Deploy Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS), with lifecycle policies enabled, on AWS. Use it to transfer the data.",
        "Deploy an AWS Snowball device in the on-premises data center after completing an export job request in the AWS Snowball console."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy an AWS Snowball device in the on-premises data center after completing an export job request in the AWS Snowball console."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "308",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has developed a microservices application. It uses a client-facing API with Amazon API Gateway and multiple internal services hosted on Amazon EC2 instances to process user requests. The API is designed to support unpredictable surges in traffic, but internal services may become overwhelmed and unresponsive for a period of time during surges. A solutions architect needs to design a more reliable solution that reduces errors when internal services become unresponsive or unavailable. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Use AWS Auto Scaling to scale up internal services when there is a surge in traffic.",
        "Use different Availability Zones to host internal services. Send a notification to a system administrator when an internal service becomes unresponsive.",
        "Use an Elastic Load Balancer to distribute the traffic between internal services. Configure Amazon CloudWatch metrics to monitor traffic to internal services.",
        "Use Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) to store user requests as they arrive. Change the internal services to retrieve the requests from the queue for processing."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) to store user requests as they arrive. Change the internal services to retrieve the requests from the queue for processing."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "309",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is backing up on-premises databases to local file server shares using the SMB protocol. The company requires immediate access to 1 week of backup files to meet recovery objectives. Recovery after a week is less likely to occur, and the company can tolerate a delay in accessing those older backup files. What should a solutions architect do to meet these requirements with the LEAST operational effort?",
      "answers": [
        "Deploy Amazon FSx for Windows File Server to create a file system with exposed file shares with sufficient storage to hold all the desired backups.",
        "Deploy an AWS Storage Gateway file gateway with sufficient storage to hold 1 week of backups. Point the backups to SMB shares from the file gateway.",
        "Deploy Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS) to create a file system with exposed NFS shares with sufficient storage to hold all the desired backups.",
        "Continue to back up to the existing file shares. Deploy AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS) and define a copy task to copy backup files older than 1 week to Amazon S3, and delete the backup files from the local file store."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy an AWS Storage Gateway file gateway with sufficient storage to hold 1 week of backups. Point the backups to SMB shares from the file gateway."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "310",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has created a multi-tier application for its ecommerce website. The website uses an Application Load Balancer that resides in the public subnets, a web tier in the public subnets, and a MySQL cluster hosted on Amazon EC2 instances in the private subnets. The MySQL database needs to retrieve product catalog and pricing information that is hosted on the internet by a third-party provider. A solutions architect must devices a strategy that maximizes security without increasing operational overhead. What should the solutions architect do to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Deploy a NAT instance in the VPC. Route all the internet-based traffic through the NAT instance.",
        "Deploy a NAT gateway in the public subnets. Modify the private subnet route table to direct all internet-bound traffic to the NAT gateway.",
        "Configure an internet gateway and attach it to the VPC. Modify the private subnet route table to direct internet-bound traffic to the internet gateway.",
        "Configure a virtual private gateway and attach it to the VPC. Modify the private subnet route table to direct internet-bound traffic to the virtual private gateway."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy a NAT gateway in the public subnets. Modify the private subnet route table to direct all internet-bound traffic to the NAT gateway."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "311",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A solutions architect is designing the cloud architecture for a company that needs to host hundreds of machine learning models for its users. During startup, the models need to load up to 10 GB of data from Amazon S3 into memory, but they do not need disk access. Most of the models are used sporadically, but the users expect all of them to be highly available and accessible with low latency. Which solution meets the requirements and is MOST cost-effective?",
      "answers": [
        "Deploy models as AWS Lambda functions behind an Amazon API Gateway for each model.",
        "Deploy models as Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) services behind an Application Load Balancer for each model.",
        "Deploy models as AWS Lambda functions behind a single Amazon API Gateway with path-based routing where one path corresponds to each model.",
        "Deploy models as Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) services behind a single Application Load Balancer with path-based routing where one path corresponds to each model."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Deploy models as AWS Lambda functions behind a single Amazon API Gateway with path-based routing where one path corresponds to each model."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "312",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has an application that ingests incoming messages. These messages are then quickly consumed by dozens of other applications and microservices. The number of messages varies drastically and sometimes spikes as high as 100,000 each second. The company wants to decouple the solution and increase scalability. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Persist the messages to Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics. All the applications will read and process the messages.",
        "Deploy the application on Amazon EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group, which scales the number of EC2 instances based on CPU metrics.",
        "Deploy models as AWS Lambda functions behind a single Amazon API Gateway with path-based routing where one path corresponds to each model.",
        "Publish the messages to an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topic with one or more Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) subscriptions. All applications then process the messages from the queues."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Publish the messages to an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topic with one or more Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) subscriptions. All applications then process the messages from the queues."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "313",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has an ecommerce application that stores data in an on-premises SQL database. The company has decided to migrate this database to AWS. However, as part of the migration, the company wants to find a way to attain sub-millisecond responses to common read requests. A solutions architect knows that the increase in speed is paramount and that a small percentage of stale data returned in the database reads is acceptable. What should the solutions architect recommend?",
      "answers": [
        "Build Amazon RDS read replicas.",
        "Build the database as a larger instance type.",
        "Build a database cache using Amazon ElastiCache.",
        "Build a database cache using Amazon Elasticsearch Service (Amazon ES)."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Build a database cache using Amazon ElastiCache."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "314",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "A company is developing an ecommerce application that will consist of a load-balanced front end, a container-based application, and a relational database. A solutions architect needs to create a highly available solution that operates with as little manual intervention as possible. Which solutions meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "answers": [
        "Create an Amazon RDS DB instance in Multi-AZ mode.",
        "Create an Amazon RDS DB instance and one or more replicas in another Availability Zone.",
        "Create an Amazon EC2 instance-based Docker cluster to handle the dynamic application load.",
        "Create an Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) cluster with a Fargate launch type to handle the dynamic application load.",
        "Create an Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) cluster with an Amazon EC2 launch type to handle the dynamic application load."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Create an Amazon RDS DB instance in Multi-AZ mode.",
        "Create an Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) cluster with a Fargate launch type to handle the dynamic application load."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "315",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company is using a third-party vendor to manage its marketplace analytics. The vendor needs limited programmatic access to resources in the companys account. All the needed policies have been created to grant appropriate access. Which additional component will provide the vendor with the MOST secure access to the account? ",
      "answers": [
        "Create an IAM user.",
        "Implement a service control policy (SCP)",
        "Use a cross-account role with an external ID.",
        "Configure a single sign-on (SSO) identity provider."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use a cross-account role with an external ID."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "316",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has an on-premises volume backup solution that has reached its end of life. The company wants to use AWS as part of a new backup solution and wants to maintain local access to all the data while it is backed up on AWS. The company wants to ensure that the data backed up on AWS is automatically and securely transferred. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Use AWS Snowball to migrate data out of the on-premises solution to Amazon S3. Configure on-premises systems to mount the Snowball S3 endpoint to provide local access to the data.",
        "Use AWS Snowball Edge to migrate data out of the on-premises solution to Amazon S3. Use the Snowball Edge file interface to provide on-premises systems with local access to the data.",
        "Use AWS Storage Gateway and configure a cached volume gateway. Run the Storage Gateway software appliance on premises and configure a percentage of data to cache locally. Mount the gateway storage volumes to provide local access to the data.",
        "Use AWS Storage Gateway and configure a stored volume gateway. Run the Storage Gateway software appliance on premises and map the gateway storage volumes to on-premises storage. Mount the gateway storage volumes to provide local access to the data."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use AWS Storage Gateway and configure a stored volume gateway. Run the Storage Gateway software appliance on premises and map the gateway storage volumes to on-premises storage. Mount the gateway storage volumes to provide local access to the data."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "317",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "The financial application at a company stores monthly reports in an Amazon S3 bucket. The vice president of finance has mandated that all access to these reports be logged and that any modifications to the log files be detected. Which actions can a solutions architect take to meet these requirements?",
      "answers": [
        "Use S3 server access logging on the bucket that houses the reports with the read and write data events and log file validation options enabled.",
        "Use S3 server access logging on the bucket that houses the reports with the read and write management events and log file validation options enabled.",
        "Use AWS CloudTrail to create a new trail. Configure the trail to log read and write data events on the S3 bucket that houses the reports. Log these events to a new bucket, and enable log file validation.",
        "Use AWS CloudTrail to create a new trail. Configure the trail to log read and write management events on the S3 bucket that houses the reports. Log these events to a new bucket, and enable log file validation."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Use AWS CloudTrail to create a new trail. Configure the trail to log read and write data events on the S3 bucket that houses the reports. Log these events to a new bucket, and enable log file validation."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "318",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Test Example Questions",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A company has an image processing workload running on Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) in two private subnets. Each private subnet uses a NAT instance for internet access. All images are stored in Amazon S3 buckets. The company is concerned about the data transfer costs between Amazon ECS and Amazon S3. What should a solutions architect do to reduce costs?",
      "answers": [
        "Configure a NAT gateway to replace the NAT instances.",
        "Configure a gateway endpoint for traffic destined to Amazon S3.",
        "Configure an interface endpoint for traffic destined to Amazon S3.",
        "Configure Amazon CloudFront for the S3 bucket storing the images."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Configure a gateway endpoint for traffic destined to Amazon S3."]
    }
  }
]